<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:anchor="https://anchor.fm/xmlns" xmlns:podcast="https://podcastindex.org/namespace/1.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:psc="http://podlove.org/simple-chapters">
  <channel>
    <title>stdout security</title>
    <description>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.
      
      Note: This is an AI-generated summary of News Articles from the past 24 hours. I take no credit for the research or analysis in said articles - this podcast only exists as a simple audio summary to help busy, sleep-deprivd Cyber Nerds like myself keep on top of developments while wranging kids and brushing teeth.
    </description>
    <link>https://opalsec.io</link>
    <generator>Anchor Podcasts</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 05:06:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <author>Opalsec</author>
    <copyright>Opalsec</copyright>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="https://anchor.fm/s/109797ef8/podcast/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/>
    <itunes:author>Opalsec</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Opalsec</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>opalsec.integrate@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:category text="News">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:image href="https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_nologo/44439246/44439246-1758158096542-bb2824b85de8c.jpg"/>
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, February 20, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[**stdout: Daily Cyber Intelligence Briefing**

<p>Stay ahead of the curve with "stdout", your essential daily briefing for Cyber Security Analysts. We cut through the noise, delivering critical insights on the last 24 hours of cyber developments.</p>

<p>🚨 <b>Active Threats & Breaches:</b> Unpack the latest ransomware attacks on Japanese semiconductor supplier Advantest and the Booking.com phishing campaign targeting the hotel and retail sector. We delve into over $20 million stolen via ATM jackpotting, with over 700 incidents reported in 2025, the sentencing of a North Korea IT worker scheme facilitator, and Interpol's massive $4.3 million recovery operation. Plus, a supply chain attack on the Cline AI npm package, a Microsoft 365 Copilot bug exposing confidential emails, and the ongoing threat of China's Volt Typhoon embedded in US critical infrastructure. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>🛠️ <b>New Techniques & Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b> Discover cutting-edge threats like PromptSpy, the first Android malware leveraging Google Gemini for persistence, and "Starkiller," a sophisticated Phishing-as-a-Service tool bypassing MFA. We analyse advanced LockBit 5.0 evasion tactics, the surge in RMM abuse (up 277% in 2025), and how threat actors are combining device code phishing with vishing to compromise Microsoft Entra accounts. Learn about new Remcos RAT variants, MetaMask wallet tampering via JavaScript backdoors, and the risks of Kerberos delegation for machine accounts. 🕵️‍♀️</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Critical Patches & Zero-Days:</b> CISA mandates urgent patching for actively exploited vulnerabilities in Dell RecoverPoint (CVE-2026-22769) and Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340), with evidence of exploitation since summer 2025. We cover critical RCE flaws in Grandstream VoIP phones (CVE-2026-2329), OpenSSL stack buffer overflows, and 16 vulnerabilities (including zero-days) found in Foxit and Apryse PDF platforms. 💥</p>

<p>🌍 <b>Threat Landscape & Regulatory Watch:</b> Get the lowdown on AI agent safety concerns, significant security risks in IoT devices, and a 49% increase in ransomware targeting industrial organisations in 2025. We also cover major data privacy exposures, regulatory actions against TP-Link, and Poland's ban on Chinese-made vehicles in military facilities. Stay informed on the push for post-quantum encryption transition and secure AI development. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:24:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1YghcX_v75Oz6vMF3jH7RW7xD4r3f_phN" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1771586695515</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, February 16, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats with stdout! 🇦🇺 This episode unpacks the evolving 'ClickFix' social engineering tactic, a pervasive threat technique dominating the last 24 hours. We reveal how attackers are leveraging this method across diverse platforms and attack chains to compromise systems and exfiltrate sensitive data.</p>

<p>Discover a new DNS-based ClickFix attack targeting Windows, tricking users into executing <code>nslookup</code> commands to deploy <strong>ModeloRAT</strong> via a lightweight DNS staging channel. 💻 Concurrently, <strong>Lumma Stealer</strong> activity surges, often delivered through fake CAPTCHA campaigns utilising <strong>CastleLoader</strong> and other resilient loaders like RenEngine and Hijack Loader. We also examine campaigns deploying <strong>StealC</strong> and <strong>Stealerium</strong> via PowerShell, and the novel abuse of generative AI services like Anthropic Claude to stage malicious ClickFix instructions, distributing <strong>Atomic Stealer</strong> and <strong>MacSync Stealer</strong>.</p>

<p>For macOS users, beware of phishing and malvertising delivering <strong>Odyssey Stealer</strong>, a full RAT exfiltrating data from over 200 browser and crypto wallets. 🍎 Attackers are also forging TCC authorisations via AppleScript and using fake Apple Support articles to steal credentials. A critical shift sees threat actors abusing Pastebin comments to promote fake crypto arbitrage exploits, injecting malicious JavaScript directly into browsers to hijack swap interfaces and steal cryptocurrency. Flare's analysis confirms macOS stealers overwhelmingly prioritises crypto theft, underscoring the urgent need for robust macOS-specific detection capabilities.</p>

<p>We also explore the <strong>ClearFake</strong> campaign's use of EtherHiding on compromised WordPress sites, deploying <strong>Lumma Stealer</strong> by executing contracts on the BNB Smart Chain. This innovative technique blends malicious traffic with legitimate Web3 activity, offering increased resilience. ⛓️ Recognise the outdated and dangerous assumption that 'Macs don't get viruses' and understand the critical need for organisations to implement strong detection for macOS TTPs, including unsigned applications, unusual Terminal activity, and data exfiltration patterns.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 20:50:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1reT2WAdo837Nz_9UCT52hYQfQygXM0v4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1771188606295</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, February 15, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Alert:</b> Dive into the latest cyber threats with stdout! We're tracking a single, sophisticated actor responsible for over 83% of recent attacks exploiting <b>Ivanti EPMM zero-day vulnerabilities</b> (CVE-2026-21962 & CVE-2026-24061). This threat actor, operating from bulletproof infrastructure, is also targeting Oracle WebLogic, GNU Inetutils Telnetd, and GLPI. Get the details on Ivanti's hotfixes and essential mitigation strategies for organisations.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ Next, uncover the North Korean Lazarus Group's new 'Graphalgo' campaign. They're luring JavaScript and Python developers with fake job offers and malicious coding challenges that install a modular Remote Access Trojan (RAT) via legitimate package registries like npm and PyPi. This RAT is designed for extensive data exfiltration and specifically checks for MetaMask, indicating a strong focus on crypto-theft. Learn what to do if you've been affected.</p>

<p>✉️ Finally, beware of a cunning <b>physical phishing campaign</b> targeting Trezor and Ledger hardware wallet users. Threat actors are sending official-looking letters with QR codes leading to malicious sites designed to steal your recovery phrases. We explain how this leverages past data breaches and reiterate the golden rule: hardware wallet manufacturers will <i>never</i> ask for your recovery phrase online. Stay vigilant!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 20:49:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1pLKYSp0pH_BeatnJKi-FcAntfCNosJtz" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1771102195281</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, February 14, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 This stdout episode unpacks a busy 24 hours in cyber security, diving into significant breaches and active campaigns. We cover Dutch telco Odido's breach affecting millions and luxury brands Louis Vuitton, Dior, and Tiffany fined for inadequate cloud security. Discover how suspected Russian intelligence is deploying CANFAIL malware against Ukrainian sectors using LLMs for reconnaissance, and how "ClickFix" campaigns leverage Claude LLM artefacts and Google Ads to deliver the MacSync infostealer to macOS users.</p>
<p>Explore new threat research, highlighting nation-state actors aggressively targeting the Defence Industrial Base with zero-day exploits and social engineering. Unpack the security risks of autonomous AI agents in "swarm" orchestrations, from credential sprawl to over-privileged access, and get the lowdown on npm's authentication overhaul and its lingering MFA phishing risks. Plus, Microsoft faces pressure over Bring-Your-Own-Vulnerable-Driver attacks and declines to classify new Windows LNK shortcut spoofing as vulnerabilities.</p>
<p>Stay ahead with critical vulnerability alerts: a pre-authentication RCE in BeyondTrust Remote Support (CVE-2026-1731) is actively exploited, alongside two critical RCE zero-days in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) compromising European government agencies. Apple's first 2026 zero-day (CVE-2026-20700) affecting iPhones/iPads, and a critical SQL injection flaw in Microsoft Configuration Manager (CVE-2024-43468) are also under active exploitation. Patch immediately!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 20:51:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=16IlInxsxDHlEpYYpW5-3YFN6MJHq_9hL" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1771015919043</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, February 13, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>&#x1F525; Your daily deep dive into the latest in infosec! This <b>stdout</b> episode <b>analyses</b> critical developments from the last 24 hours, focusing on active breaches, emerging attack techniques, and exploited zero-days.</p>

<p>&#x1F4A5; <b>Active Breaches & Ransomware:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Dutch mobile provider Odido suffers a cyberattack, exposing <b>6.2 million customer records</b> including names, bank details, and addresses.</li>
    <li>Senegal grapples with "The Green Blood Group" ransomware, which exfiltrated <b>biometric data</b> and highlights regional cybersecurity maturity gaps.</li>
    <li>A new group, 0APT, emerges with cryptographically strong ransomware binaries, despite initial victim claims being questioned.</li>
</ul>

<p>&#x1F50D; <b>New Techniques & Threat Research:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>State-backed actors are actively leveraging <b>Google Gemini AI</b> for reconnaissance, vulnerability analysis, and malware development.</li>
    <li>Ransomware groups are adopting stealthy tactics, using legitimate employee monitoring tools like Net Monitor for Employees Professional, chained with SimpleHelp RMM for network compromise.</li>
    <li>Group-IB reports the industrialisation of supply chain attacks, with AI-assisted tools accelerating vulnerability scanning and <b>identity attacks replacing traditional malware</b>.</li>
</ul>

<p>&#x1F512; <b>Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Apple rushes out updates for a <b>critical zero-day (CVE-2026-20700)</b> in dyld, actively exploited in sophisticated, targeted attacks.</li>
    <li>Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile zero-days (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) are seeing 83% of exploitation attempts from a single bulletproof hosting IP, consistent with initial access brokers.</li>
</ul>

<p>&#x1F4C8; <b>Broader Threat Landscape:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>California fines Disney $2.75M for CCPA violations regarding data opt-out difficulties.</li>
    <li>Hundreds of Chrome extensions found exfiltrating browsing history to data brokers.</li>
    <li>CISA prepares for sector-specific town halls on the stalled CIRCIA regulation, seeking industry feedback.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 20:51:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1eTXR8FTXg3lic2OAoKUqNs5whHizMUV1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770929476599</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, February 12, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with stdout! We unpack critical incidents including the <b>ApolloMD data breach</b> by Qilin ransomware, impacting over 620,000 individuals. Law enforcement action saw the arrest of a <b>JokerOTP phishing-as-a-service</b> operator linked to $10M in losses, while new <b>payroll fraud</b> schemes leverage social engineering against help desks to redirect paychecks, often bypassing detections via VDI. 💸</p>
<p>Threat actors are evolving their tactics: discover how <b>LummaStealer infections</b> are surging via CastleLoader and the ClickFix technique. The <b>Crazy ransomware gang</b> is abusing legitimate tools like Net Monitor and SimpleHelp for persistence and evasion, and North Korea's <b>UNC1069</b> deploys new macOS malware, deepfakes, and AI-generated video in crypto-theft campaigns. Plus, a new <b>SSHStalker Linux botnet</b> is using IRC for C2, brute-forcing, and 15-year-old kernel exploits. 🛠️</p>
<p>Stay ahead of vulnerabilities: Microsoft's February Patch Tuesday addressed <b>six actively exploited zero-days</b>, including RCE flaws in Windows Shell, IE, and Word, all now in CISA's KEV. We also cover a critical <b>Telnet vulnerability (CVE-2026-24061)</b> with a CVSS 9.8, and a new <b>Notepad Markdown RCE (CVE-2026-20841)</b> requiring social engineering. ⚠️</p>
<p>Finally, we analyse broader threat landscape insights, from the risks of posting AI-generated caricatures to the ongoing concerns around Telnet usage in the APAC region, and the data privacy implications of AI health apps. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15l3USj89vw9uJIk-QKaTsDJVOqK7_sLC" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770843224124</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, February 11, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<code>
<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Debrief</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with stdout! We're tracking active exploitation of <b>SolarWinds Web Help Desk</b> instances and the <b>Warlock ransomware group's</b> breach of SmarterTools via critical RCE (CVE-2026-24423) and authentication bypass (CVE-2026-23760) flaws. Discover how <b>UNC3886</b> persistently breached Singaporean telcos with a zero-day for espionage, and the widespread impact of <b>Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile zero-days</b> (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) on European government agencies, exposing employee data. Plus, a destructive Russian-backed attack on Poland's energy grid and the <b>SafePay ransomware</b> link to the Volvo Group NA data exposure via Conduent.</p>

<p>Unpack new threat actor tactics, including <b>UNC1069's</b> sophisticated social engineering, deepfake CEO, and multi-stage malware (WAVESHAPER, HYPERCALL, DEEPBREATH, CHROMEPUSH) targeting a crypto executive. Learn about <b>TeamPCP's</b> worm-like attacks exploiting misconfigured cloud services (Docker, Kubernetes, Redis, React2Shell) across 60,000+ servers for cryptomining and data theft. We also cover the emergence of <b>ZeroDayRAT</b>, a new commercial mobile spyware, and how malicious prompts can trick AI agents in messaging apps into data-leaking URLs. Beware of trojanised 7-Zip installers turning systems into residential proxy nodes and state-linked phishing campaigns targeting high-profile European figures.</p>

<p>Stay ahead with critical vulnerability updates: <b>Microsoft's February Patch Tuesday</b> addressed 58 flaws, including six actively exploited zero-days and three public disclosures. Fortinet has also patched a critical SQL Injection vulnerability (CVE-2026-21643, CVSS 9.1) in <b>FortiClientEMS</b>, allowing unauthenticated RCE. The latest Picus Labs Red Report highlights a strategic shift from loud ransomware to stealthy, long-term access, with a focus on data extortion and evasion. We also delve into the evolving threat of "process comprehension" in <b>OT cyberattacks</b> and the ongoing debate around <b>FISA Section 702</b> renewal. Finally, Microsoft rolls out new mobile-style security controls for Windows 11 and updates Secure Boot certificates.</p>
</code>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=137pIJ7k03NWRseQIBdXUoLGcftMCb2pf" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770756785172</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, February 10, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Unpacking the latest in cyber security: European government entities are reeling from Ivanti zero-day exploits (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340), while ransomware hits Senegal's national ID office, US payment providers, and SmarterTools. SolarWinds Web Help Desk RCEs (CVE-2025-40551, CVE-2025-26399) are under active exploitation, with attackers utilising legitimate tools for persistence. 💥</p>

<p>New threat intelligence reveals China's "Expedition Cloud" platform for critical infrastructure cyberattack rehearsals and TeamPCP's (DeadCatx3) "massive campaign" targeting cloud-native environments with worm-driven exploits. Discover the emergence of Amaranth-Dragon, a new Chinese cyber espionage group linked to APT-41, and UNC3886's covert access into Singaporean telcos. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>A deep-dive into vulnerabilities covers a critical BeyondTrust RCE (CVE-2026-1731), multiple SmarterMail flaws added to CISA's KEV catalogue, and over 50,000 internet-exposed OpenClaw instances vulnerable to RCE. We also unpack the systemic challenges of AI security beyond cloud infrastructure and how modern compilers can inadvertently reintroduce side-channel vulnerabilities. 🛠️</p>

<p>In broader news, Bunnings successfully challenged a privacy violation over facial recognition, India proposes "Digital Identities" for AI agents, and China tightens its cryptocurrency ban. Plus, Russia grants asylum to an alleged Spanish "cyberterrorist" wanted for espionage. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:53:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1G0cCqdDnO6bnwfTGEwoyN2yrmUVh9Nwq" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770670435434</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, February 9, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Alert: OpenClaw & Shadow AI Risks Unpacked!</b> 🚨</p>
<p>This episode of stdout dives deep into the alarming security landscape surrounding <b>OpenClaw</b>, the open-source AI agent, and its marketplace, <b>ClawHub</b>. We unpack hundreds of malicious skills designed for data exfiltration, backdoor injection, and stealer malware, alongside critical vulnerabilities including one-click Remote Code Execution (RCE) and zero-click attacks via indirect prompt injection. Discover how cleartext credentials, API keys, and over 30,000 exposed OpenClaw instances are creating new attack surfaces, highlighting the significant "Shadow AI" risk. We also cover the adjacent Moltbook social network's misconfigured database, exposing 1.5 million API tokens and 35,000 email addresses.</p>
<p>We discuss OpenClaw's response, including the integration of VirusTotal scanning for all uploaded skills, and then shift gears to a powerful new open-source tool: <b>Tirith</b>. 🛡️</p>
<p>Learn how Tirith is revolutionising command-line security by hooking into user shells (zsh, bash, fish, PowerShell) to inspect and block malicious URLs. We detail its effectiveness against homograph attacks, terminal injection, pipe-to-shell patterns, dotfile hijacking, insecure transport, typosquatted git repositories, and credential exposure in URLs. Best of all, Tirith performs all analysis locally, ensuring privacy and minimal overhead. Get the lowdown on this essential cross-platform defence tool!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:49:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1PbxmR0v37gjPdlCbPPA169aMpD_4xKM9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770583790972</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, February 8, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Stay ahead with the latest 24-hour cyber developments! We dissect a sophisticated state-sponsored phishing campaign using Signal's social engineering to target high-ranking officials across Europe, linked to Russia-aligned groups. Learn how Chinese-backed actors are exploiting vulnerable network devices in Norwegian <b>organisations</b>, and get the lowdown on Russia's Static Tundra group hitting critical infrastructure in Poland via FortiGate VPNs lacking multi-factor authentication. 💥</p>
<p>Shifting focus to privacy, we examine New York City's controversial exploration of AI-powered cameras for subway fare evasion, sparking significant civil liberties concerns. Additionally, a new audit probes the Department of Homeland Security's collection and management of Personally Identifiable Information and biometric data, following allegations of broad surveillance and facial recognition expansion. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 20:50:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1JvO_K1MOo13D7nIA28O0730uDylR71-y" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770497405450</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, February 7, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout Daily Briefing: Active Threats & Breaches** 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the latest cyber developments! We're tracking a breach at Spain's Ministry of Science via an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) vulnerability and a Qilin ransomware attack on Romania's national oil pipeline operator, Conpet. An Illinois man pleaded guilty to hacking 600 Snapchat accounts, while the Asian state-backed TGR-STA-1030 group has breached over 70 government and critical infrastructure organisations globally using phishing and N-day exploits. Plus, Norway confirms Chinese state-sponsored Salt Typhoon activity, and Germany warns of Signal account hijacking targeting high-ranking individuals.</p>

<p>🛠️ **New Techniques & Threat Actor Tactics** 🛠️</p>
<p>Discover how ransomware operators like LockBit and Qilin are abusing ISPsystem VMmanager's default Windows templates for payload delivery. Threat actors are weaponising the legitimate, albeit expired, EnCase kernel driver to disable EDR products, exploiting a Driver Signature Enforcement gap. Unpack DKnife, a China-nexus framework performing deep packet inspection and traffic manipulation via routers, and get the latest on DDoS trends, including a record 31.4 Tbps attack and the rise of "smash-and-dash" tactics.</p>

<p>⚠️ **Exploited Vulnerabilities & AI Risks** ⚠️</p>
<p>CISA has issued a critical warning for CVE-2026-24423, an actively exploited Remote Code Execution (RCE) flaw in SmarterMail. We also explore significant risks in AI agent platforms: Moltbook exposed user secrets and Personally Identifiable Information (PII) via an unauthenticated API key, while OpenClaw's marketplace revealed sensitive credentials in over 7% of its skills. Learn about indirect prompt injection attacks and the broader implications of these agentic network vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>🛡️ **Defensive Insights & Regulatory Updates** 🛡️</p>
<p>On the defensive front, Anthropic's Claude Opus 4.6 has autonomously discovered over 500 previously unknown high-severity vulnerabilities in open-source libraries. We also look at KEV Collider, a new tool to help organisations better triage CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities Catalogue, and CISA's Binding Operational Directive 26-02, mandating federal agencies to remove end-of-life network edge devices to mitigate substantial exploitation risks.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 20:52:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1n7YcBj8Or2oKFpuHT6uALDovzD2zAWKa" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770411141037</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, February 6, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber skirmishes! 💥 This episode uncovers significant breaches at Substack and Betterment, exposing millions of user details via social engineering and dating back to October 2025. We track Qilin ransomware's hit on Romania's Conpet, a suspected pro-Russian attack on Italy's La Sapienza University, and broader 'Russian origin' cyberattacks targeting Italian interests. Plus, discover how threat actors are hijacking NGINX servers with malicious config injections and exploiting unsecured Zendesk systems for spam campaigns.</p>

<p>Unpack cutting-edge threats and tactics. 🕵️‍♀️ APT28 (Fancy Bear) is exploiting a new Microsoft Office vulnerability (CVE-2026-21509) with MiniDoor malware, while the Asia-based TGR-STA-1030 group leverages a new Linux kernel rootkit, ShadowGuard, in a vast cyberespionage operation. We also explore an AWS cloud intrusion achieving admin access in minutes, potentially with AI assistance, and DragonForce ransomware's shift to a 'cartel' model. Discover Iranian IRGC spear-phishing, Microsoft's LLM 'sleeper agent' detection, the pervasive SystemBC botnet, and BYOVD attacks abusing revoked kernel drivers. Plus, a critical coding error in Nitrogen ransomware causing irreversible data loss.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, 🚨 critical flaws (CVE-2026-25049) in the n8n open-source workflow automation platform allow remote code execution and full host control, with PoCs publicly available. GitHub Codespaces has disclosed attack vectors enabling RCE by simply opening malicious repositories, a behaviour Microsoft currently deems 'by design.' We also cover a critical sandbox escape (CVE-2025-64721) in Sandboxie, now patched.</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the broader threat landscape and regulatory shifts. 📈 GreyNoise research reveals CISA silently updated 59 KEV entries for ransomware use, challenging patch prioritisation. Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) system security is gaining board-level focus, with ransomware operations increasingly targeting these 'crown jewel' assets. CISA has also issued a binding directive for federal agencies to replace unsupported 'edge devices' within twelve months, and Microsoft is mandating TLS 1.2 for Azure Blob Storage by February 2026.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:53:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1cx2hgm4Qt3GLqnz7NTeJ23x7WdHcpvaH" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770324795255</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, February 5, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Brief:</b> Your essential 24-hour intel drop for Cyber Security Analysts, covering 20 critical stories across 8 topics. Today, we dive into active cyber events, emerging threats, and urgent vulnerability patches.</p>

<p>💥 <b>Breaches & Attacks:</b> The US military digitally disrupted Iranian air missile <b>defence</b> systems in Operation Midnight Hammer. Step Finance lost $40M from compromised executive devices, while Coinbase confirmed a new insider breach affecting ~30 customers. The Mexican government faces 2.3TB data leak allegations from Chronus Group, though claims are downplayed. Ivanti EPMM is under active attack via critical zero-days (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340), and ransomware gangs are now exploiting VMware ESXi sandbox escape (CVE-2025-22225).</p>

<p>🕵️‍♀️ <b>New Techniques & Research:</b> Russia's APT28 (Fancy Bear) rapidly exploited CVE-2026-21509 (MS Office bypass) within three days, deploying MiniDoor and Covenant Grunt. Python-based infostealers are expanding to macOS via fake ads, and Predator spyware can now block iOS camera/mic indicators. Discover an EDR killer abusing a revoked EnCase kernel driver, and learn why Nitrogen ransomware's ESXi variant has a critical decryption flaw. AI agents are significantly assisting criminals in vuln scanning and malware writing, but Gartner warns against "insecure by default" OpenClaw-as-a-service. ⚠️</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Critical Vulnerabilities:</b> CISA mandates patching for actively exploited SolarWinds Web Help Desk RCE (CVE-2025-40551) and a 5-year-old GitLab SSRF (CVE-2021-39935). Ivanti EPMM zero-days (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) allow unauthenticated RCE, with CVE-2026-1281 added to the KEV catalog. Google Looker patched SQLi and RCE flaws, while VMware ESXi sandbox escape (CVE-2025-22225) and Sangoma FreePBX vulnerabilities (CVE-2019-19006, CVE-2025-64328) are also under CISA's urgent patch orders. ⏰</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Industry & Regulatory:</b> The Eclipse Foundation will enforce pre-publication security checks for Open VSX Registry extensions. DHS is revamping critical infrastructure partnerships, and CISA is considering an AI Information Sharing and Analysis Centre. Microsoft is rolling out native Sysmon functionality to Windows 11 Insiders, and Ukraine has implemented a Starlink "whitelist" to counter Russian drone use. 🔒</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:52:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1WxgztTQ94cyo9m0bckriYnyyz99qU4mv" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770238354607</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, February 4, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🎧 <strong>stdout</strong> delivers your daily deep dive into the latest in information security for Cyber Security Analysts. We've got the essential updates from the last 24 hours, covering active cyber events, novel techniques, and critical exploited vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>🚨 **Active Threats & Breaches:** We unpack a sophisticated Dropbox phishing campaign harvesting credentials via fake PDF lures hosted on legitimate cloud services. Get the details on the Iron Mountain breach, where the Everest extortion gang claimed 1.4TB, though the company reports a limited incident involving marketing materials accessed via compromised credentials. Plus, a 20-year-old has been arrested in Poland for operating a global DDoS botnet, and a Polish defence ministry employee detained on suspicion of spying for Russian and Belarusian intelligence. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>⛓️ **New Techniques & Supply Chain Attacks:** Stay ahead of emerging attack vectors with insights into the new <strong>GlassWorm macOS malware</strong>, targeting systems via compromised OpenVSX extensions to steal passwords, crypto-wallet data, and developer credentials. We also detail the China-linked Lotus Blossom group's <strong>Notepad++ supply chain attack</strong>, which delivered the stealthy Chrysalis backdoor through trojanised updates, exploiting insufficient verification controls in older versions. </p>

<p>💥 **Actively Exploited Vulnerabilities:** Our deep dive reveals Russian APT28 (Fancy Bear) leveraging a recently patched <strong>Microsoft Office zero-day (CVE-2026-21509)</strong> against Ukrainian government and EU organisations. Learn about the critical <strong>React Native Metro RCE (CVE-2025-11953)</strong>, allowing unauthenticated command execution and EDR-disabling payloads, despite its low Exploit Prediction Scoring System (EPSS) score. CISA has also flagged a critical <strong>SolarWinds Web Help Desk RCE (CVE-2025-40551)</strong>, demanding urgent federal agency patching. We also expose the "dumpster fire" that is the OpenClaw DIY AI bot farm, riddled with high-impact RCE and command injection flaws, alongside exposed API keys from the Moltbook project. </p>

<p>🌐 **Threat Landscape & Regulatory Scrutiny:** We discuss the critical impact of recent major <strong>cloud service outages</strong> on identity systems and Zero Trust models, disrupting authentication and authorisation. Uncover CISA's silent updates to its Known Exploited Vulnerability (KEV) catalog regarding ransomware use, and a coordinated reconnaissance campaign targeting <strong>Citrix NetScaler infrastructure</strong>. In regulatory news, X and Grok AI face intense scrutiny and raids in France and the UK over alleged generation of illicit content, while the UK investigates its first suspected cyber sanctions breaches. </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:53:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Zn1ECy8bYwjo2aX35iVzzydi7evLP9T1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770151982478</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, February 3, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This <b>stdout</b> episode unpacks a busy 24 hours in infosec, tracking critical supply chain compromises and active cyber events. State-sponsored actors hijacked <b>Notepad++</b> and <b>eScan antivirus</b> update mechanisms, while a malicious update push via the <b>Open VSX Registry</b> delivered GlassWorm malware. We also cover the <b>NationStates</b> data breach via a one-click RCE, and a Belgian high school's data theft followed by attempted parent extortion. 💥</p>

<p>Dive into new threat intelligence: North Korea's <b>Labyrinth Chollima</b> has splintered into specialised entities for crypto theft and espionage. We reveal over 230 malicious "skills" found in the <b>OpenClaw AI assistant</b> registry, deploying info-stealing malware. On the vulnerability front, Russia-linked <b>APT28</b> is actively exploiting a new <b>Microsoft Office zero-day (CVE-2026-21509)</b>, and a critical one-click RCE was patched in the <b>OpenClaw AI ecosystem</b>. 🛡️</p>

<p>Our analysis extends to the broader threat landscape, highlighting over 175,000 exposed <b>Ollama open-source AI deployments</b> ripe for exploitation, and the increasing trend of infrastructure cyberattacks. We discuss the perils of the "move fast and break things" software culture and Microsoft's plan to phase out the vulnerable <b>NTLM authentication protocol</b>. Plus, a critical shutdown bug affecting some <b>Windows 10/11</b> devices post-January updates. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, we cover significant data privacy and regulatory news: the US Treasury's termination of contracts with <b>Booz Allen Hamilton</b> due to data safeguards failure, McDonald's push for better password hygiene, and a simulated breach of South Korean government systems. We also touch on the $600,000 settlement for security professionals wrongfully arrested during a legitimate pen test. Stay informed! 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 20:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1zOFf9QAu-5J_Vb8i3ALSRA6461K_bHWS" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1770065550562</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, February 2, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Urgent warning: Dive into <b>ongoing data extortion attacks</b> targeting misconfigured MongoDB instances. Cybersecurity firm Flare reveals thousands of publicly exposed databases have been wiped, with threat actors demanding Bitcoin ransoms. Learn critical defences against these widespread compromises. 🛡️</p>

<p>Next, we unpack the evolving threat landscape with a chilling account of a <b>sophisticated deepfake applicant</b> attempting to infiltrate a security firm. This incident underscores the growing challenge of AI-driven social engineering, particularly in the context of North Korean-affiliated IT worker scams. Discover the red flags and countermeasures to protect your organisation from advanced identity deception. 🤖</p>

<p>Finally, we analyse Apple's new "Limit Precise Location" feature for iPhones and iPads. This privacy update restricts cellular networks to approximate location tracking, a significant move following substantial FCC fines against carriers for illegally sharing user data. Understand how this impacts your privacy and device security. 📍</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:50:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1dgcS-107Mk1NTfyn9a7W1sq4Yi2_hxmZ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769979007829</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, January 31, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</b> A former Google engineer has been convicted for economic espionage and theft of over 2,000 AI trade secrets. Dating giants Bumble and Match Group are investigating claims of data breaches by the ShinyHunters group. Google, Cloudflare, and partners successfully disrupted IPIDEA, a massive China-based residential proxy network, reducing its operational capacity by 40%. We also cover a police probe into potential obstruction of a data breach investigation affecting 33.7 million Coupang customer accounts in South Korea, major anti-piracy operations by Europol and the US DoJ, and further notifications stemming from the TriZetto Provider Solutions health data exposure. Plus, illicit cryptocurrency flows hit a record $158 billion in 2025, driven by sanctions-linked activity and nation-state use.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ <b>New Threats & Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b> Bitdefender researchers uncovered an Android malware campaign leveraging Hugging Face as a repository for thousands of APK payloads, exploiting Accessibility Services for credential theft with server-side polymorphism. Trend Micro details China-linked Advanced Persistent Threat groups utilising the sophisticated PeckBirdy command-and-control framework in watering-hole attacks and espionage. Cisco Talos identifies a new campaign by China-linked actor UAT-8099 targeting vulnerable Internet Information Services (IIS) servers in Asia with web shells and custom BadIIS SEO malware. ⚠️ Ivanti disclosed and patched two critical, actively exploited zero-day code-injection flaws (CVE-2026-1281, CVE-2026-1340) in Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile (EPMM), allowing unauthenticated remote code execution. SmarterTools also addressed critical remote code execution flaws (CVE-2026-24423, CVE-2026-23760) in SmarterMail, with one under active exploitation, alongside a path coercion vulnerability.</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Threat Landscape & Regulatory Shifts:</b> A senior Secret Service official highlights the Internet Assigned Numbers Authority (IANA) domain registration system as a significant, often overlooked weakness. We look at Java developers' preferences for delegating container security, and an opinion piece suggesting cyber security will be America's key differentiator in the AI race against China. Microsoft plans to disable the 30-year-old NTLM authentication protocol by default in future Windows releases due to security vulnerabilities. Tenable introduces Tenable One AI Exposure to address AI governance and shadow AI risks. Finally, the White House's Office of Management and Budget (OMB) rescinded Biden-era Software Bill of Materials (SBOM) and secure software development attestations for federal agencies, deeming them "unproven and burdensome," and CISA issued insider threat guidance following an incident involving its acting Director and public ChatGPT.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:52:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1hm9yMz9Ef85SSJgCiarI2eEY1hh8c6OT" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769806369389</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, January 30, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your daily intel drop for Cyber Security Analysts!** 🚨</p>

<p>Today, we're unpacking critical cyber events from the last 24 hours. Discover how a <strong>MicroWorld Technologies update server breach</strong> deployed backdoors, and delve into the <strong>Russian Electrum group's coordinated attack on Polish energy infrastructure</strong>. We also cover the <strong>Marquis Software Solutions ransomware incident</strong> linked to a SonicWall cloud backup breach, and <strong>ShinyHunters' 10M+ record theft from Match Group</strong> via a compromised Okta SSO account. Plus, don't miss the details on the <strong>Aisuru/Kimwolf botnet's record-breaking 31.4 Tbps DDoS attack</strong>. 💥</p>

<p>Stay ahead of the curve with insights into actively exploited vulnerabilities: a critical <strong>Fortinet zero-day (CVE-2026-24858)</strong> allowing authentication bypass, the persistent exploitation of a patched <strong>WinRAR path traversal flaw (CVE-2025-8088)</strong>, and multiple <strong>critical RCE vulnerabilities in SolarWinds Web Help Desk</strong>. Cisco Talos reports vulnerability exploits are now the leading initial access vector, often within hours of disclosure. 📉</p>

<p>We also track law enforcement wins, including the <strong>FBI's takedown of the RAMP dark web marketplace</strong> and <strong>Google's disruption of the IPIDEA residential proxy network</strong>. Get the lowdown on new threat actor tactics: TA584's use of <strong>Tsundere Bot with Ethereum blockchain C2</strong>, and the <strong>specialisation of North Korea's Labyrinth Chollima group</strong> into distinct espionage and crypto-theft operations. Plus, a warning about <strong>175,000 publicly exposed Ollama AI servers</strong> creating "LLMjacking" risks. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on significant developments in data privacy and regulation, including a <strong>class action lawsuit against xAI's Grok</strong> for deepfake generation, <strong>Apple's new precise location blocking feature</strong>, and <strong>Google's enhanced Android theft protection</strong>. We also look at France Travail's hefty €5M CNIL fine for data security failings and the US's push for global AI cybersecurity standards. 🌍</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 20:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1kzKfN2zbZncT8aLYfYy-B4Li8VcXuY9f" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769720029722</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, January 29, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Your daily deep dive into the latest in cyber security. We're analysing 24 articles across seven key topics from the last 24 hours, tailored for cyber security analysts.</p>

<p>🚨 <b>Active Threats & Exploits:</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Unpack Sandworm's coordinated attack on Poland's power grid, compromising operational technology, and the "Bizarre Bazaar" campaign actively exploiting exposed Large Language Model endpoints for crypto mining and data exfiltration. We also cover significant law enforcement wins, including the takedown of Kingdom Market, Empire Market, and the RAMP cybercrime forum.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♀️ <b>New Techniques & Vulnerabilities:</b> 🕵️‍♀️</p>
<p>Discover Mustang Panda's updated CoolClient backdoor, now stealing browser data and deploying a new rootkit, alongside malicious PyPI packages (`spellcheckerpy`, `spellcheckpy`) delivering Python RATs – a stark warning about "slopsquatting." Get the lowdown on critical, actively exploited flaws: a Fortinet FortiCloud SSO zero-day (CVE-2026-24858) granting admin access, and widespread exploitation of a six-month-old WinRAR path-traversal vulnerability (CVE-2025-8088) by nation-states and cybercriminals. Plus, immediate patching advice for critical authentication bypass and RCE flaws in SolarWinds Web Help Desk, a vm2 Node.js sandbox escape (CVE-2026-22709), and n8n workflow automation RCEs (CVE-2026-1470, CVE-2026-0863).</p>

<p>🌍 <b>Broader Landscape & Privacy:</b> 🌍</p>
<p>Gartner predicts a shift to zero-trust data governance by 2028, driven by concerns over "model collapse" from unverified AI data. We examine Latin America's surge as the riskiest region for cyberattacks and the data leak risks associated with insecure Moltbot AI assistant deployments. Privacy discussions include Microsoft's alleged provision of BitLocker keys to law enforcement, the ongoing debate around online age verification, and WhatsApp's new "Strict Account Settings" for high-risk users, alongside Meta's migration to Rust for enhanced security.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:52:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=10eJuS5MlcIdADDQdA0eSW1aRRDcthFo_" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769633554099</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, January 28, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀</p>

<p>We're tracking major incidents, including a large-scale cyberattack on Russian firm Delta, Nike's investigation into a 1.4TB data leak claim by WorldLeaks, and ShinyHunters' alleged breaches impacting 29.8 million SoundCloud users, plus Panera Bread, CarMax, and Edmunds. Discover how China-linked Salt Typhoon allegedly accessed UK Downing Street officials' phones for years, and the DoJ's charges against 31 individuals for a $5.4 million ATM skimming scheme using Ploutus malware. 🕵️‍♀️</p>

<p>Deep dive into new threat research: a malicious campaign leveraging the ClickFix method with fake CAPTCHAs and signed Microsoft App-V scripts to deliver Amatera infostealer. Learn about ShinyHunters' evolved voice-phishing targeting ~100 organisations in an Okta SSO credential-stealing operation, and the new 'Stanley' malware-as-a-service offering Chrome extensions that bypass Google's review process. We also cover the active exploitation of the high-severity WinRAR path traversal flaw (CVE-2025-8088) by state-sponsored and financially motivated groups, and Chainalysis' findings on Chinese money laundering networks processing $16.1 billion in illicit crypto. 💻</p>

<p>Stay informed on critical vulnerabilities: Microsoft's out-of-band patch for an actively exploited Office zero-day (CVE-2026-21509), the critical authentication bypass in SmarterMail (CVE-2026-23760) exposing over 6,000 servers, and a critical sandbox escape in the vm2 Node.js library (CVE-2026-22709). Both Microsoft Office and SmarterMail flaws are now in CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue. 🚨</p>

<p>Plus, we touch on Google's $68 million privacy settlement, Microsoft's illegal tracking cookies in Austrian schools, WhatsApp's new "Strict Account Settings," and the legal challenge against the Met Police's live facial recognition. France plans to replace US videoconferencing tools with its own "Visio" app, while CISA's post-quantum cryptography guide faces criticism. Finally, an opinion piece argues for transferring the CVE programme from MITRE to the private sector. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:52:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1miAMXdgAxmuIiijDCnrHvn5hvVPecf1S" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769547122501</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, January 27, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[**stdout**: Your daily deep dive into the cyber security landscape for technical analysts.

🚨 **Active Threats & Breaches:** ESET attributes the December 2025 DynoWiper attack on Poland's power grid to Russia's Sandworm group. WorldLeaks (Hunters International rebrand) claims a 1.4TB data theft from Nike, currently under investigation. Koi Security uncovered two malicious AI-powered Visual Studio Code extensions, with over 1.5 million installs, siphoning source code to China-based servers. LayerX identified 16 malicious ChatGPT Chrome extensions stealing credentials and session tokens. A London court awarded over $4.1 million for Pegasus spyware attacks on Ghanem Al-Masarir, with conduct linked to Saudi Arabia.

🕵️ **New Techniques:** North Korea's Konni APT group is deploying AI-generated PowerShell malware via spear-phishing, targeting blockchain developers in Australia, Japan, and India.

🩹 **Critical Vulnerabilities:** CISA added a critical VMware vCenter Server Remote Code Execution flaw (CVE-2024-37079) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue, with Broadcom confirming active exploitation. Shadowserver tracks nearly 800,000 internet-exposed Telnet servers, many vulnerable to CVE-2026-24061, an actively exploited authentication bypass allowing unauthenticated root login. Microsoft issued emergency out-of-band updates for an actively exploited Office zero-day (CVE-2026-21509). Koi Security also identified "PackageGate" flaws in JavaScript package managers, bypassing supply-chain defences, though npm declined a fix. Pwn2Own Automotive 2026 uncovered 76 zero-days in automotive systems, including Tesla infotainment.

📈 **Industry Trends & Regulatory Shifts:** The increasing sophistication of AI-based attacks highlights the need for a combined Network Detection and Response (NDR) and Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) defence strategy. The Supreme Court will hear Salazar v. Paramount Global, questioning Facebook tracking pixel legality under the Video Privacy Protection Act. The European Commission launched a formal investigation into X and its Grok chatbot under the Digital Services Act, concerning the generation and spread of sexually explicit images, including child sexual abuse material. The international Pall Mall Process is developing voluntary industry guidelines for commercial cyber intrusion tools. The UK government plans an in-house digital identity scheme, dropping the compulsory element. Cloudflare reported a 25-minute BGP route leak on January 22nd, affecting IPv6 traffic due to an accidental policy misconfiguration.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:52:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Es0xiQr1EUFUEaiIZphuwE9peiq0Wa9d" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769460729177</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, January 26, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This episode of <b>stdout</b> dives into a recent report linking Russian state-sponsored group Sandworm (APT44) to a failed data-wiping attack on Poland's energy infrastructure in late December 2025. ⚡️ Discover details on their attempted deployment of the new destructive DynoWiper (Win32/KillFiles.NMO) and the historical context of these persistent threats.</p>

<p>Then, we analyse 1Password's new pop-up warnings designed to combat sophisticated phishing attempts. 🛡️ Learn how these warnings protect users from manually entering credentials on malicious sites, particularly those employing typosquatting, and why this additional layer is crucial amidst rising AI-powered phishing threats. We also cover the alarming statistics on user susceptibility to phishing.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:49:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1OStLqTCjX84blXW6rb_VpcAACGhCvRgG" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769374174117</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, January 25, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>Active Threats & Exploits:</strong> Dive into the latest cyber skirmishes! ShinyHunters is leveraging voice phishing against Okta, Microsoft, and Google SSO for data theft and extortion. We also unpack Sandworm's unsuccessful DynoWiper attack on Poland's power grid and a multi-stage phishing campaign targeting Russia with Amnesia RAT, ransomware, and the 'defendnot' tool to disable Microsoft Defender. Plus, North Korea's Konni group is deploying AI-generated PowerShell malware against blockchain engineers in the APAC region.</p>

<p>💥 <strong>Critical Vulnerabilities Under Attack:</strong> Get the lowdown on actively exploited flaws. Cisco's Unified Communications zero-day (CVE-2026-20045) is granting root privileges, while a critical VMware vCenter Server bug (CVE-2024-37079) continues to be exploited over a year after its patch. Both are now on CISA's Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue, demanding immediate attention.</p>

<p>🧠 <strong>Emerging Risks & Techniques:</strong> Explore the evolving threat landscape, including the significant security risks posed by AI agents in enterprise environments, challenging traditional identity and access management models. Understand how organisational agents, with their broad access and often unclear ownership, create new authorisation bypass paths.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:50:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1mFPJlvJPtmNqaXBTxHw0UT6jeVfIjU0f" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769287828436</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, January 24, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! Your daily deep dive into the critical cybersecurity developments of the last 24 hours. We're breaking down active cyber events, new attack techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities impacting organisations globally.</p>

<p>🚨 This episode, we unpack recent breaches affecting UK councils and German art collections, alongside a multi-million dollar ATM jackpotting scheme. Developers beware: two malicious AI-themed VS Code extensions have exfiltrated 1.5 million installs' worth of source code and credentials to China-based servers. 💻</p>

<p>Threat actors are evolving, with Okta warning of sophisticated vishing-as-a-service kits bypassing MFA, and Microsoft flagging multi-stage Adversary-in-the-Middle (AitM) phishing campaigns targeting the energy sector. 🕵️‍♂️ Learn how criminals are leveraging "Scattered Spider-style" helpdesk scams to intercept credentials.</p>

<p>🔒 Critical vulnerabilities are under active exploitation: Fortinet's FortiCloud SSO bypass (CVE-2025-59718) remains exploitable despite patches, allowing unauthorised admin account creation and config exfiltration. CISA has updated its KEV catalog with four new flaws, including a PHP remote file inclusion and a supply chain attack. Plus, an 11-year-old GNU InetUtils telnetd flaw (CVE-2026-24061) is being actively exploited for unauthenticated root access. 💥</p>

<p>We also discuss Australia's review of national security risks from Chinese-made electric buses, Google's warning about the imminent "Metasploit moment" for AI-powered cyberattack kits, and Microsoft's provision of BitLocker keys to the FBI. 🌐 Get the essential facts and key takeaways you need as a Cyber Security Analyst.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 20:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TXajHZ0-T-zeZWFCVQUpNeHQLDC_tWmF" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769201544233</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, January 23, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<b>🚨 Active Threats & Breaches:</b> Automated attacks are targeting Fortinet FortiGate devices via FortiCloud SSO, exploiting CVE-2025-59718/59719 for configuration changes and admin account creation, with a patch bypass reported for FortiOS 7.4.10. The energy sector saw Microsoft accounts compromised through SharePoint phishing, leading to credential theft and widespread internal/external phishing. Plus, a Russian national pleads guilty to a four-year Zeppelin/GlobeImposter ransomware conspiracy, causing over $1.5 million in losses.

<b>🕵️‍♂️ New Techniques & Research:</b>
<ul>
    <li>Discover a malicious PyPI package, `sympy-dev`, deploying an XMRig miner on Linux using `memfd_create` and `/proc/self/fd` for stealthy in-memory execution.</li>
    <li>North Korean actors are abusing Microsoft VS Code's built-in tunnelling feature for spear-phishing, gaining full remote control and bypassing traditional C2 infrastructure.</li>
</ul>

<b>⚠️ Critical Vulnerabilities Exploited:</b>
<ul>
    <li>Cisco's actively exploited zero-day, CVE-2026-20045, an RCE affecting Unified Communications products and Webex Calling, now on CISA's KEV catalogue.</li>
    <li>A critical authentication bypass in SmarterTools SmarterMail (WT-2026-0001) under active exploitation, allowing admin password resets and remote code execution.</li>
    <li>An 11-year-old flaw, CVE-2026-24061, in GNU InetUtils telnetd, actively exploited for root access via argument injection – decommission telnetd now!</li>
</ul>

<b>📈 Industry Insights & Regulatory Shifts:</b>
<ul>
    <li>Discussions at Davos focused on securing AI agents with zero trust, least-privilege access, and guard agents to prevent insider threats.</li>
    <li>The Bank of England's CBEST report highlights persistent basic cyber security safeguard failures in the UK financial sector, despite years of regulation.</li>
    <li>GDPR fines hit €1.2 billion in 2025 amidst a 22% rise in daily breach notifications, indicating increased enforcement and incident disclosures.</li>
    <li>CISA and NIST face lawmaker scrutiny and budget constraints impacting critical programmes like post-quantum encryption validation, leading to resource reshuffling.</li>
    <li>CIRCL launched GCVE, a decentralised system for tracking software vulnerabilities, offering an alternative to the traditional CVE programme.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=12BbdUHllxCEfs5KEseG-GGvVR-EHi0-Z" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769115123184</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, January 22, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest 24-hour cyber landscape with critical updates on active threats. We're tracking the <b>Everest ransomware group's Under Armour breach</b>, leaking 72.7 million accounts, and a sophisticated <b>mobile phishing campaign in Greece</b> using a fake cell tower. Discover the alleged leader of <b>Black Basta ransomware</b> and a critical <b>LastPass phishing campaign</b> targeting master passwords. 🎣</p>

<p>Unpack new attack techniques with the "CrashFix" variant of ClickFix, deploying malicious browser extensions and the Python-based ModeloRAT. Get insights into <b>VoidLink, a stealthy Linux malware framework</b> developed with AI assistance for long-term cloud access. ☁️</p>

<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: active exploitation of a <b>FortiGate patch bypass (CVE-2025-59718)</b>, a severe <b>WordPress ACF: Extended flaw (CVE-2025-14533)</b> granting admin privileges, and a fixed <b>Cloudflare WAF bypass</b>. We also cover arbitrary JS execution in the <b>`binary-parser` npm library</b>, "ChainLeak" vulnerabilities in the <b>Chainlit AI framework</b>, and the stunning <b>37 zero-days demonstrated at Pwn2Own Automotive 2026</b>, including a Tesla hack. 🚗</p>

<p>Finally, we explore the ethical complexities of ransomware negotiations, <b>HackerOne's new AI Research Safe Harbour</b>, the UK's push for secure software, Ireland's proposed surveillance legislation, and the EU's potential phase-out of "high-risk" IT suppliers. Don't miss why the <b>cURL project ended its bug bounty</b>! ⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:51:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1sOD5pkSymIBU9mX2WqbYWueLxUPO37eu" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1769028704557</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, January 21, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Key cyber security developments from the last 24 hours include the <b>Nomad Leopard</b> campaign, targeting Afghan government employees with spear-phishing and FalseCub malware for data exfiltration. Discover how AI is revolutionising cybercrime, with "Dark LLMs" enabling rapid malware development and deepfake fraud. We highlight the AI-generated <b>VoidLink Linux malware</b>, which targets major cloud environments and was likely developed by a single individual in under a week. 🤖</p>

<p>Analyse critical vulnerabilities:</p>
<ul>
    <li>A prompt injection flaw in <b>Google Gemini AI</b>, exploitable via Google Calendar invites to access private meeting data and create deceptive events.</li>
    <li>Three critical bugs in <b>Anthropic's Git Model Context Protocol (MCP) server</b>, chainable for remote code execution or file overwrites through prompt injection.</li>
    <li>Easy-to-exploit arbitrary file read and SSRF flaws in the popular open-source AI framework <b>Chainlit</b>, leading to data leaks and account takeovers (patched in v2.9.4).</li>
    <li>A patched ACME validation bug in <b>Cloudflare</b> that allowed Web Application Firewall (WAF) bypass to origin servers. 🛡️</li>
</ul>

<p>Explore the evolving threat landscape with the reported winding down of the illicit Telegram-based <b>Tudou Guarantee</b> marketplace and the alarming rise of "predator bots" exploiting APIs, now accounting for over half of global web traffic and causing significant economic harm. We also examine sustained cyber threats from pro-Russian hacktivist groups, primarily through disruptive DDoS attacks, and discuss essential layered defence strategies. 📊</p>

<p>Finally, get the lowdown on US congressional moves to temporarily extend key cybersecurity laws and allocate significant funding to CISA, including for election security. Plus, reports of mass spam attacks leveraging <b>Zendesk</b> instances from major companies like Live Nation and Capcom, often bypassing spam filters. 🚨</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:51:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1lJ1hBXeQBqu2usmPeF0yekbgKAdmlztX" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768942304936</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, January 20, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with stdout's daily deep dive into the latest in cyber security. Today, we unpack 13 critical developments from the last 24 hours, covering active threats, novel tradecraft, and crucial policy shifts.</p>

<p>🚨 <strong>Active Threats & Breaches:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>Higham Lane School crippled by a serious cyberattack impacting IT and physical safety systems.</li>
    <li>Ingram Micro disclosed a SafePay ransomware breach affecting 42,521 individuals' personal data.</li>
    <li>Iranian state television was briefly hijacked to broadcast protest footage.</li>
    <li>The NCSC warns of ongoing DDoS attacks on UK critical infrastructure by pro-Russia hacktivists.</li>
</ul>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ <strong>New Tradecraft & Exploits:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>Discover PDFSider, a stealthy Windows backdoor used in Qilin ransomware attacks, delivered via DLL side-loading.</li>
    <li>The KongTuke campaign deploys ModeloRAT through a malicious Chrome extension masquerading as an ad blocker.</li>
    <li>Researchers exploited an XSS vulnerability in the StealC info stealer's control panel, gaining insights into threat actor operations and uncovering a prolific lone-wolf actor.</li>
    <li>Mandiant releases rainbow tables to accelerate Net-NTLMv1 deprecation, cracking credentials in under 12 hours.</li>
</ul>

<p>⚖️ <strong>Legal & Law Enforcement:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>A US Navy sailor sentenced to 16 years for selling technical manuals and operational information to Chinese intelligence.</li>
    <li>Nicholas Moore pleaded guilty to hacking US government systems, including the Supreme Court.</li>
    <li>A Jordanian Initial Access Broker linked to a $50 million ransomware attack after selling network access to an undercover FBI agent.</li>
    <li>Interpol apprehended 34 individuals in Spain tied to the Nigeria-based Black Axe syndicate.</li>
</ul>

<p>🛡️ <strong>Policy, Privacy & Critical Updates:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>Examine security and safety concerns surrounding OpenAI's new ChatGPT Health product.</li>
    <li>US lawmakers push to restrict ICE's Mobile Fortify app, addressing civil liberties and biometric surveillance.</li>
    <li>Microsoft issues an urgent Windows 11 out-of-band update (KB5077797) to fix critical shutdown and Remote Desktop authentication bugs.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:30:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1SUliEKLuLHQjP98fp2XR3HA_eCsFkeKt" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768858208359</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, January 17, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚀 <strong>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Intel Briefing</strong></p>
<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cyber security with 16 critical articles across five key topics. We summarise the latest active threats, exploited vulnerabilities, and evolving attack techniques impacting organisations globally.</p>

<p>🚨 <strong>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li><strong>Grubhub</strong> confirms a data breach and extortion demands from ShinyHunters, potentially linked to previous data thefts.</li>
    <li>Canada's <strong>CIRO</strong> discloses a sophisticated phishing attack impacting 750,000 investors, with PII at risk.</li>
    <li>The <strong>Anchorage Police Department</strong> proactively took systems offline after a third-party data migration service provider was compromised.</li>
</ul>

<p>💥 <strong>Critical Vulnerabilities Under Attack:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li><strong>Cisco</strong> patches a maximum-severity zero-day RCE (CVE-2025-20393) in AsyncOS, actively exploited by China-linked APT UAT-9686.</li>
    <li><strong>HPE OneView</strong>'s critical RCE (CVE-2025-37164) is under large-scale exploitation by the RondoDox botnet, targeting government and financial sectors.</li>
    <li>Hackers are actively exploiting an authentication bypass (CVE-2026-23550) in the <strong>Modular DS WordPress plugin</strong>, granting remote admin access.</li>
    <li>Discover <strong>StackWarp</strong> (CVE-2025-29943), an AMD CPU vulnerability allowing malicious insiders to access sensitive data in SEV-SNP environments.</li>
    <li>Plus, a critical IoT flaw in <strong>Äike e-scooters</strong> due to default private keys, and a simple XSS in <strong>CISA's own web tool</strong>.</li>
</ul>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ <strong>Threat Actor Insights & Malware Evolution:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>China-linked APT <strong>UAT-8837</strong> targets North American critical infrastructure, utilising a Sitecore zero-day (CVE-2025-53690) and Earthworm for reverse tunnelling.</li>
    <li><strong>Mustang Panda</strong> deploys a new Lotuslite backdoor in phishing campaigns against US government entities.</li>
    <li>The alleged ringleader of <strong>Black Basta ransomware</strong>, Oleg Evgenievich Nefedov, has been identified and added to international most-wanted lists.</li>
    <li>An Initial Access Broker, "r1z," pleads guilty to selling network access and EDR killer malware, linked to a $50M ransomware attack.</li>
    <li><strong>Gootloader</strong> evolves its evasion tactics with highly malformed ZIP archives designed to crash analysis tools.</li>
</ul>

<p>🔒 <strong>Data Privacy & Future Defences:</strong></p>
<ul>
    <li>The <strong>Carlsberg Experience</strong> exposed visitor data due to weak authentication on wristband IDs.</li>
    <li>Explore <strong>PNNL's ALOHA</strong>, an AI-based system utilising LLMs to drastically reduce attack reconstruction and purple teaming times.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1c9cXCRH10zgcIjn99BCAwofiDvUIr_0F" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768596723514</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, January 16, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout Daily Briefing: Cyber Threats & Vulnerabilities Unpacked** 🚨</p>

<p>The last 24 hours in cyber security saw a major ransomware attack on South Korean conglomerate Kyowon Group, impacting over 5.5 million individuals with exfiltrated customer data. Meanwhile, a staff member has been bailed following a data breach investigation at a UK GP surgery. 💥</p>

<p>In new threat research, Microsoft, Europol, and German authorities successfully disrupted RedVDS, a prolific cybercrime-as-a-service platform linked to an estimated $40 million in fraud. We also unpack a critical prompt injection risk in Anthropic's Cowork AI, allowing sensitive file exfiltration to attacker accounts. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Our analysis highlights several high-stakes vulnerabilities: a high-severity DoS flaw in Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS (CVE-2026-0227) allowing unauthenticated attackers to disable firewalls, and critical bugs in Delta Electronics PLCs that could lead to unsafe physical conditions. AWS CodeBuild's "CodeBreach" misconfiguration risked GitHub repository takeovers, while Google's Fast Pair protocol is exposed to "WhisperPair" (CVE-2025-36911), a critical flaw affecting hundreds of millions of Bluetooth devices, enabling forced pairing and eavesdropping. 🔒</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, we examine Cyble's report on hackers increasingly targeting non-critical sectors in Australia and New Zealand with initial access sales and ransomware. 🇦🇺🇳🇿 Plus, we cover the record surge in CVE assignments, major data privacy shifts including the FTC's ban on GM/OnStar sharing driver data, AWS's new European Sovereign Cloud, and the concerning potential for AI tools to inadvertently normalise foreign influence. 💡</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:52:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1L5Vy_oYphT4j-m-fKBDwR6lOMrawObr4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768510358770</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, January 15, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>⚡️ **stdout: Daily Cyber Debrief** ⚡️</p>
<p>Tracking critical incidents from the last 24 hours: a ransomware attack crippling Belgian hospitals and a thwarted Russian cyberattack on Poland's power grid. Major data breaches impacted Monroe University, Endesa, Eurail, and the Victorian Department of Education, while Pax8 accidentally exposed partner data. 🏥🔌</p>

<p>Unpack the latest in threat actor activity and novel techniques: Russia's 'Void Blizzard' targeting Ukraine's Defence Forces with PluggyApe, and the significant takedown of the RedVDS cybercrime service. Get across new research on VoidLink, an advanced cloud-native Linux malware framework, DeadLock ransomware's Polygon smart contract C2, Predator spyware's anti-detection capabilities, and the Kimwolf botnet infecting Android TV devices. 🕵️‍♂️👾</p>

<p>Stay ahead of the curve with insights into critical vulnerabilities: Microsoft's January Patch Tuesday zero-day (CVE-2026-20805), RCE flaws in popular AI/ML Python libraries, a Node.js DoS vulnerability, and a publicly exploited command injection in Fortinet FortiSIEM (CVE-2025-25256). We also cover "Reprompt," a new attack method that hijacked Microsoft Copilot Personal sessions. 🚨🛠️</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the broader threat landscape: North Korea's extensive crypto thefts funding WMDs, China's intensifying "siege rehearsal" cyberattacks on Taiwan's critical infrastructure, and new Western guidance for securing industrial OT. Plus, France's CNIL issues a hefty GDPR fine to Free/Free Mobile, California investigates xAI's Grok AI for deepfake allegations, and CISA awaits a permanent director. 🌏⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:57:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1VGVMFaR48hL7Am_unmGcyPLhr-7tTUAn" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768424279219</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, January 14, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Breaches & Law Enforcement Blitz:</b> This episode of stdout dives into a massive 24 hours, starting with the breach of <b>BreachForums</b> exposing 324,000 users. We analyse the confirmed leak of <b>Target's</b> internal source code and documentation, plus suspected ransomware attacks hitting South Korea's <b>Kyowon Group</b> and Belgium's <b>AZ Monica hospital</b>. Central Maine Healthcare also reports a data breach affecting over 145,000 individuals. On the law enforcement front, we cover a 7-year sentence for hacking Rotterdam ports, the arrest of a "violence-as-a-service" coordinator for the Foxtrot network, and the disruption of the Black Axe criminal organisation in Spain. 🚔</p>

<p>🔬 <b>Evolving Threats & Techniques:</b> Get the lowdown on the sophisticated <b>SHADOW#REACTOR</b> campaign delivering Remcos RAT via an evasive multi-stage Windows attack, leveraging obfuscated VBS, PowerShell, and MSBuild. Discover an emerging phishing campaign abusing Cloudflare services to deploy <b>AsyncRAT</b>, and how Kremlin-linked <b>Void Blizzard</b> is targeting Ukrainian military personnel with PluggyApe malware through tailored messaging app lures. We also expose the malicious "MEXC API Automator" Chrome extension stealing crypto API keys and a new LinkedIn phishing tactic. 🎣</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Patches:</b> CISA has added <b>CVE-2025-8110</b>, a high-severity path traversal RCE in Gogs, to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue due to active exploitation. Microsoft's January 2026 Patch Tuesday addressed 114 vulnerabilities, including three zero-days: an actively exploited information disclosure in Desktop Window Manager (<b>CVE-2026-20805</b>), a Secure Boot certificate bypass, and an EoP in the Windows Agere Soft Modem Driver. Plus, ServiceNow patched a critical AI Platform vulnerability (<b>CVE-2025-12420</b>), and RCE flaws were found in popular AI/ML Python libraries like NeMo and Uni2TS. 🛠️</p>

<p>🌍 <b>Strategic Insights & Industry Shifts:</b> We discuss Mandiant's open-sourcing of <b>AuraInspector</b> for Salesforce security, the US debate on cyber deterrence, and calls for stronger action against North Korea's IT worker schemes and crypto heists. India introduces strict new crypto regulations, and CrowdStrike acquires Seraphic Security to bolster browser runtime protection against "shadow AI." Stay informed on the broader cyber landscape. 📊</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 22:05:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1QdXUCAEpnIWfTmd5o9kGQzMmECZ9TLhN" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768341948809</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, January 13, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Intel Briefing.</b> 🇦🇺 Dive into the last 24 hours of information security, delivering critical insights for Cyber Security Analysts.</p>

<p>🚨 Today's critical updates feature major data breaches impacting <b>Target</b> (860GB source code), the <b>University of Hawaii Cancer Center</b> (ransomware, SSNs stolen), and Spanish energy giant <b>Endesa</b> (10M+ customer records for sale). Even <b>BreachForums</b> wasn't immune, exposing 324,000 user accounts. We also cover the alleged breach of US House committees by <b>Salt Typhoon</b> and a UK school closure due to cyberattack.</p>

<p>🔍 Unpack the latest threat intelligence: From the industrial scale of <b>Pig Butchering-as-a-Service (PBaaS)</b> to new <b>GoBruteforcer</b> attacks on cryptocurrency databases and threat actors scanning for misconfigured <b>LLM proxy servers</b>. Learn about Block's successful <b>AI prompt injection</b> red-team, the <b>Kimwolf Android botnet</b>, and evolving phishing campaigns like "Prompt Poaching" Chrome extensions and DCRat targeting hospitality organisations.</p>

<p>💥 Don't miss urgent vulnerability patches: CISA's directive on the actively exploited <b>Gogs RCE (CVE-2025-8110)</b> zero-day, the maximum-severity <b>n8n RCE (CVE-2026-21858 "Ni8mare")</b>, and critical flaws in <b>Veeam</b>. Plus, suspected Chinese exploitation of <b>VMware ESXi zero-days</b> and a concerning <b>Telegram IP leak</b> via proxy links.</p>

<p>🌍 We also cover the US's "gray zone" cyber operations, the doubling of AI security risk assessments by business leaders, and X's formal investigation by Ofcom over content concerns. Stay ahead with stdout.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:54:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1DGkkR0iQWb95oBssvoToLsrroO6GHbnJ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768251263668</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, January 12, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Brief:</b> Dive into the latest cyber developments! Instagram denies a new 17.5 million account data breach, attributing circulating phone numbers, usernames, and emails to older API scraping incidents. Meta confirms fixing a bug allowing mass password reset requests. <b>Key takeaway:</b> No passwords leaked, but vigilance against targeted phishing and 2FA are crucial. 🛡️</p>

<p>⚖️ We also analyse significant data privacy actions. CalPrivacy has fined Datamasters $45,000 and banned them from selling Californian PII for reselling sensitive health data without registration. S&P Global Inc. also copped a $62,600 fine for an administrative error in failing to register as a data broker. Stay informed on regulatory compliance and the upcoming California Delete Act. 📊</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 20:49:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1EzEcVMuMFwDlqS_z5KppQ4fY62JBynai" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768164589831</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, January 11, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Brief:</b> Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security!</p>

<p>We're diving into significant developments, including the arrest of 34 individuals linked to the <b>Black Axe cybercrime syndicate</b>, responsible for over $6 million in Business Email Compromise and Man-in-the-Middle scams. Plus, the latest iteration of <b>BreachForums suffered a data breach</b>, exposing 323,988 user records and over 70,000 public IP addresses, posing a critical operational security risk. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>On the threat intelligence front, the Iranian actor <b>MuddyWater (TA450) has deployed RustyWater</b>, a new Rust-based implant (Archer RAT/RUSTRIC). This custom malware is distributed via spear-phishing, targeting diplomatic, maritime, financial, and telecom entities across the Middle East with advanced C2 and anti-analysis capabilities. We also unpack a World Economic Forum study on <b>deepfake fraud tools</b>, revealing their current limitations against live Know Your Customer (KYC) checks but highlighting the emergence of advanced identity fraud capabilities. 🎣</p>

<p>In data privacy, discover how digital advocates are developing <b>counter-surveillance methods against US Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) technologies</b>, including adversarial noise stickers for license plates and mapping tools for Flock Automated License Plate Readers (ALPRs). Finally, we examine the controversial exclusion of central and local government from the <b>UK's new Cyber Security and Resilience Bill</b>, drawing criticism amidst high public sector cyber incidents. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 20:50:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1QpGz9P7c4GZ3YQelzqn70GCHCuRTA6CT" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768078242246</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, January 10, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Active Threats & Breaches:</b> Unpack the latest cyber incidents, including malicious Chrome extensions exfiltrating sensitive LLM conversations and browsing data from 900,000 users. We also cover a significant Snapchat phishing scheme and the Illinois DHS's accidental exposure of nearly 700,000 residents' personal and health data due to misconfigured privacy settings. Plus, get the lowdown on North Korean state-sponsored group Kimsuky (APT43) utilising "quishing" with malicious QR codes in MFA-resilient spearphishing campaigns. 🎣</p>

<p>💥 <b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Exploitation:</b> Dive deep into actively exploited flaws. Huntress reports Chinese-speaking threat actors likely exploited three VMware ESXi zero-days (CVE-2025-22226, -22224, -22225) over a year before public disclosure, leveraging a sophisticated VM escape toolkit. CISA has added a maximum-severity RCE in HPE OneView (CVE-2025-37164) to its KEV catalogue, confirming active exploitation. We also detail the industry-wide response to "React2Shell" (CVE-2025-55182), a maximum-severity RCE affecting React frameworks, and Trend Micro's critical RCE patch for Apex Central (CVE-2025-69258). 💻</p>

<p>⚖️ <b>Policy, Privacy & Industry Insights:</b> Stay informed on regulatory actions, including the California Privacy Protection Agency fining Datamasters $45,000 for selling sensitive health data without registration. We examine X's Grok AI image generation tool limiting features after severe criticism over non-consensual deepfakes. Additionally, CISA has retired ten emergency directives, and the NSA welcomes Tim Kosiba as its new Deputy Chief. Finally, explore CrowdStrike's $740 million acquisition of SGNL, aiming to bolster identity security against evolving threats. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 11:09:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Mq9Qnt0PgS6OaFh0SBMS2C-0Q13g-scO" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1768043364765</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, January 9, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🇦🇺 Your daily deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. Today, we're unpacking critical vulnerabilities, active exploits, and evolving threat tactics.</p>

<p>🚨 **Urgent Vulnerabilities & Exploits:** We're tracking "ni8mare" (CVE-2026-21858, CVSS 10.0) in n8n automation, allowing unauthenticated RCE on 100,000 servers. CISA has added two critical flaws to its KEV catalogue: a max-severity RCE in HPE OneView (CVE-2025-37164, CVSS 10.0) and a 15-year-old Microsoft Office PowerPoint bug (CVE-2009-0556, CVSS 8.8), both actively exploited. Plus, a zero-day command injection (CVE-2026-0625, CVSS 9.3) is hitting end-of-life D-Link DSL gateways – replacement is key! We also cover data theft via jsPDF (CVE-2025-68428, CVSS 9.2) and RCEs in Zed IDE.</p>

<p>😈 **New Attack Techniques & Campaigns:** Discover the "Boto Cor-de-Rosa" Python WhatsApp worm spreading Astaroth banking trojan in Brazil, and the GoBruteforcer botnet targeting crypto databases with weak AI-generated passwords. IBM's AI coding agent "Bob" is vulnerable to prompt injection for malware execution and data exfiltration. MuddyWater is evolving with custom backdoors, and Phishing-as-a-Service toolkits have doubled, featuring advanced anti-analysis and MFA bypass capabilities. We also look at `pkr_mtsi` malvertising campaigns and GeoServer exploitation for XMRig miners.</p>

<p>🌐 **Threat Landscape & Breaches:** Iberia airline confirms a 77GB data leak from a Zestix/Sentap infostealer. Emsisoft reports a 50%+ increase in ransomware attacks globally, with CISA adding 245 KEVs in 2025, 24 exploited by ransomware groups. Taiwan's energy sector saw a tenfold increase in Chinese cyberattacks. Also, Microsoft Exchange Online faces an IMAP4 outage, and ownCloud advises MFA due to Zestix/Sentap data auctions.</p>

<p>⚖️ **Regulatory & Privacy Watch:** UK regulators are investigating X and Grok AI over nonconsensual imagery generation, a major test for the Online Safety Act. OpenAI faces privacy concerns with its ChatGPT Health program and is ordered to provide 20 million logs in a copyright lawsuit. Microsoft is enforcing MFA for the 365 admin centre from Feb 2026. Plus, rare criminal prosecutions for stalkerware and transnational scam networks.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:54:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1SUEY0zaPOdDokinVqWDDe-UjY5zk23ql" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767905691046</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, January 8, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>🚨 stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing 🚨</h3>

Stay ahead with the latest in cyber security! This episode dives into critical developments from the last 24 hours, covering active breaches, exploited vulnerabilities, and emerging threat techniques.

<p>We unpack significant cyberattacks impacting global entities: 💥 <b>Brightspeed ISP</b> investigating claims of 1M+ customer records stolen, 🚗 <b>Jaguar Land Rover's</b> production halted by Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters, and the 🛰️ <b>European Space Agency</b> confirming another major breach with 500GB of sensitive data exfiltrated, allegedly via an unpatched vulnerability. The 🇬🇧 <b>UK Ministry of Justice</b> faces scrutiny after a £50M cyber investment failed to detect a breach for months, compromising sensitive legal aid data. Plus, 🇹🇼 <b>Taiwan's energy sector</b> sees a tenfold increase in Chinese cyberattacks, correlating with geopolitical events, and ☁️ <b>ownCloud</b> users are urged to enable MFA following infostealer-led breaches.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, we highlight actively exploited flaws: ⚠️ A critical RCE (CVE-2026-0625) in legacy <b>D-Link DSL gateway routers</b> is under active exploitation, allowing unauthenticated command injection. 🛡️ <b>Veeam Backup & Replication</b> has patched a critical RCE (CVE-2025-59470) allowing code execution as a postgres user, a frequent target for ransomware. Furthermore, the maximum severity "Ni8mare" vulnerability (CVE-2026-21858) in <b>n8n workflow automation</b> could allow unauthenticated remote file reading and potential RCE on over 100,000 servers – update to v1.121.0+ immediately!</p>

<p>Discover new threat research and industry insights: 🇷🇺 Pro-Russian hacktivist group <b>NoName057(16)</b> is leveraging its multiplatform DDoSia tool for sustained application-layer attacks. We also discuss the crucial role of AI in proactive risk management, the second successful prosecution of a <b>stalkerware vendor</b>, and the 🇬🇧 <b>UK's new £210M Government Cyber Action Plan</b> to bolster public sector defences. Stay informed on regulatory changes, including new <b>FCC fines for robocall mitigation</b> database non-compliance, and a significant <b>Microsoft Outlook bug</b> preventing access to "Encrypt Only" emails. Don't miss the details on a multi-billion dollar scam empire dismantled in Cambodia and concerns over communication in bug bounty programmes.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:52:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1pyCLDHifGYuajm4G6ScIjQnsoUFCo_4E" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767819121680</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, January 7, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with <i>stdout</i>. We're tracking active threats, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities impacting organisations globally.</p>

<p>This episode, we unpack the widespread data theft by <b>Zestix/Sentap</b>, leveraging info-stealers and a lack of MFA to compromise critical infrastructure and more. Discover how a UK school was crippled by a cyberattack, the <b>Ledger</b> breach via a payment partner, and the <b>TridentLocker</b> ransomware hitting a federal contractor. Plus, the £196 million impact of the <b>Jaguar Land Rover</b> cyberattack.</p>

<p>🔍 On the research front, we expose the <b>PHALT#BLYX</b> campaign targeting European hospitality with DCRat via fake Booking.com emails and BSOD tricks. Learn about the expanding <b>Kimwolf Android botnet</b>, now nearly 2 million strong, exploiting exposed ADB services for DDoS and proxy resale. We also reveal how researchers identified members of the notorious <b>Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters</b> group.</p>

<p>⚠️ Critical vulnerabilities demand attention: a <b>CVSS 9.9 RCE</b> in the n8n workflow automation platform (CVE-2025-68668) allowing arbitrary command execution via a sandbox bypass. Also, actively exploited command injection (CVE-2026-0625) in end-of-life <b>D-Link DSL routers</b>, urging immediate replacement.</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, we discuss the reclassification of industrialised fraud as a global security threat and Microsoft's controversial stance on AI prompt injection as a non-vulnerability. We also highlight "Prompt Poaching" – malicious and legitimate Chrome extensions exfiltrating your AI chat data. Finally, the UK government launches its <b>£210 million Cyber Action Plan</b>, acknowledging past shortcomings and aiming to uplift public sector defences.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:51:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fj-ZVHFm7NVtO8cuLkO6HOCUCfgI_vM2" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767732688332</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, January 6, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber developments. We unpack significant breaches including New Zealand's ManageMyHealth exposing 100,000+ patient records and Ledger customers' data compromised via a third-party. Discover how Trust Wallet's Chrome extension suffered an $8.5M theft due to exposed GitHub secrets, and track UAC-0184's Viber-based attacks on Ukrainian entities. Plus, we cover Brightspeed's investigation into a 1M+ PII data theft claim and a successful Resecurity honeypot operation against the Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters. 🚨</p>

<p>Explore emerging threats and techniques: From the Python-based VVS Stealer targeting Discord and browser data, to China's DarkSpectre compromising 8.8 million users with browser extension malware. Learn about Mustang Panda's new kernel-mode rootkit, the latest callback phishing and vishing campaigns abusing Microsoft Teams, and malvertising tactics delivering FireClient malware via fake SAP Concur extensions. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Crucial vulnerability alerts: The RondoDox botnet is actively exploiting the critical React2Shell flaw (CVE-2025-55182, CVSS 10.0) for unauthenticated RCE on over 84,000 devices. Uncover Bluetooth headphone vulnerabilities allowing data exfiltration and impersonation, and the risks of "recommended extension" attacks in VSCode IDE forks. Stay ahead with the facts. 💥</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 20:51:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1qSb-6JbPj_plj4QHHZDIkhu78fhU7Rgr" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767646287232</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, January 5, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>This episode dives into critical cyber developments from the last 24 hours:</p>

<ul>
    <li><b>Breaches & Active Threats:</b> Clop group claims responsibility for a breach at Korean Air's former unit, KC&D, compromising 30,000 employees' PII via a suspected Oracle EBS zero-day. Emurasoft's official EmEditor installer was hijacked, delivering a malicious PowerShell payload. Plus, Westminster City Council confirms sensitive data theft from a November incident affecting shared IT systems.</li>
    <li><b>Critical Vulnerabilities:</b> Discover a CVSS 10.0 unauthenticated root RCE (CVE-2025-54322) in Xspeeder SXZOS firmware, identified by an AI agent. With Xspeeder unresponsive, an estimated 70,000 hosts remain vulnerable.</li>
    <li><b>Emerging Threats (AI):</b> Palo Alto Networks predicts AI agents will be the biggest insider threat by 2026, highlighting "superuser" and "AI doppelganger" risks. Learn how attackers are already using AI as a force multiplier, exemplified by the "Anthropic attack."</li>
    <li><b>Regulatory Watch:</b> The Trump administration has lifted sanctions on three individuals previously associated with the Intellexa spyware consortium.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:49:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=14ciJJVwybOiOfJW-wu59RYMh7u1JXBkI" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767559793716</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, January 4, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A major cyber event unfolds as the <b>ShinyHunters</b> hacking group claims a significant breach of cyber security firm <b>Resecurity</b>. 🕵️‍♂️ They allege the theft of employee data, internal communications, threat intelligence reports, and client information, backing their claims with published screenshots.</p>

<p>However, Resecurity fiercely disputes these claims, asserting the accessed systems were not part of their production infrastructure but a deliberately deployed <b>honeypot</b>. 🍯 They detail detecting initial probing in November, prompting the setup of an isolated environment populated with synthetic datasets, including over 28,000 consumer records and 190,000 payment transactions.</p>

<p>The firm actively monitored ShinyHunters' activity, observing over 188,000 automated data exfiltration attempts. 📊 This operation allowed Resecurity to collect crucial telemetry on the attacker's <i>tactics, techniques, and infrastructure</i>, even exposing confirmed IP addresses due to proxy connection failures. This intelligence has reportedly been shared with law enforcement. 🚨</p>

<p>The saga continues as ShinyHunters responded with a defiant Telegram post: "Nice damage control Resecurity. More information coming soon!" This incident highlights the escalating <b>cat-and-mouse game</b>, where deception techniques are now employed by both threat actors and defenders. ⚔️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 20:49:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1e6UHkg9J4wMeQGcP5XtuiHiF0F2qYwEl" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767473353302</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, January 3, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout Daily Briefing: Active Threats & Exploits** 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber developments impacting analysts today. We unpack the <b>$8.5M Trust Wallet crypto theft</b> linked to the Shai-Hulud NPM supply chain attack, where compromised GitHub secrets led to a malicious browser extension. Plus, trace over <b>$35M in ongoing cryptocurrency losses</b> from the 2022 LastPass breach, with attackers decrypting vaults and laundering funds via Russian exchanges, "demixed" by TRM Labs. Get the details on the <b>TridentLocker ransomware attack</b> on federal contractor Sedgwick, and alleged data sales from engineering firm Pickett and Associates. Covenant Health revises its Qilin ransomware breach impact to nearly 478,188 patients, exposing sensitive PII and medical records.</p>

<p>🔎 **New Techniques & Threat Actor Activity** 🔎</p>

<p>Discover a sophisticated <b>multi-stage phishing campaign</b> abusing Google Cloud's "Send Email" feature to bypass DMARC/SPF, redirecting through trusted Google services to steal credentials (now blocked). We also analyse new remote access trojans (RATs) deployed by <b>Transparent Tribe (APT36)</b> targeting Indian government and strategic entities, using weaponised LNK files and adaptive persistence mechanisms. Learn how APT36 is linked to the Patchwork group's Python-based backdoors.</p>

<p>⚠️ **Critical Vulnerabilities Under Active Exploitation** ⚠️</p>

<p>Understand the ongoing risk from over <b>10,000 Fortinet firewalls</b> still exposed to active exploitation of a five-year-old critical 2FA bypass flaw (CVE-2020-12812) in FortiGate SSL VPNs, rated 9.8 severity. Fortinet warns customers of persistent attacks manipulating username case with LDAP enabled.</p>

<p>🌐 **Industry News & Recognition** 🌐</p>

<p>European regulators are considering action against X after its AI tool, Grok, generated sexually explicit deepfakes of a minor, with the UK planning to ban "nudification tools." We also celebrate the recognition of cybersecurity professionals, including Gavin Webb of the NCA, for their pivotal roles in disrupting the LockBit ransomware group, and British researcher Jacob Riggs, granted Australia's National Innovation visa for responsible vulnerability disclosure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 20:51:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1CUGa0fLCc4jI9BYO79XRk-piX5H3dgQh" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767387062882</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, January 2, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Security Briefing</b> 🇦🇺</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of critical cyber developments! 🚀 We're tracking a <b>$3.9M crypto heist</b> from Unleash Protocol via smart contract compromise and the arrest of a Lithuanian national for a <b>$1.2M clipboard-stealing malware</b> operation. Get the lowdown on a coordinated campaign exploiting <b>10+ Adobe ColdFusion CVEs</b>, plus Amazon thwarting over 1,800 suspected North Korean operatives infiltrating its workforce. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Unpack new threats including the <b>RondoDox botnet</b> actively exploiting the critical React2Shell vulnerability (CVE-2025-55182, CVSS 10.0) on 90,000+ susceptible devices. Discover the resurfaced <b>GlassWorm supply chain attack</b> targeting macOS users with malicious Open VSX extensions, and Kaspersky's discovery of <b>Keenadu pre-installed Android malware</b>. We also cover OceanLotus (APT32) targeting China's Xinchuang initiative with a unique ELF Trojan. 💻</p>

<p>Explore the emerging <b>IPCola proxy botnet</b> with 1.6M+ IPs and the <b>ErrTraffic cybercrime toolkit</b> automating "ClickFix" attacks. Understand how a global <b>Magecart campaign</b> is evolving into full identity compromise, and the intricacies of <b>GhostAd</b> (Android) and <b>SkyWalk</b> (iOS) mobile ad fraud schemes. We also reveal a 4-second window in <b>AWS IAM eventual consistency</b> allowing persistence after key deletion. 🔒</p>

<p>Finally, we examine "hacktivist proxy operations" providing plausible deniability for states, Meta's alleged "playbook" to mislead regulators on scam ads, Disney's $10M COPPA settlement, and Reddit banning the r/ChatGPTjailbreak community for deepfake content. Stay informed, stay secure. 💡</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:50:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1eDyLjJmuM5CRfxWm9_t-vu0ARo5sAkEr" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767300642472</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, January 1, 2026</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest 24-hour cyber landscape! This episode unpacks significant active events, emerging threats, and critical vulnerabilities. We cover the <b>Unleash Protocol's $3.9M crypto loss</b> due to an <b>unauthorised contract upgrade</b> via a multisig governance exploit, and the <b>European Space Agency's 200GB data breach</b> from external servers.</p>

<p>Explore new attack vectors with the Chinese APT <b>DarkSpectre's browser extension campaigns</b> impacting over 8.8 million users, and the novel <b>ErrTraffic cybercrime service</b> automating ClickFix attacks. On the exploitation front, the <b>RondoDox botnet is actively leveraging the critical React2Shell flaw (CVE-2025-55182)</b> in Next.js servers to deploy cryptominers and Mirai variants. Plus, a severe <b>authentication bypass (CVE-2025-13915) in IBM API Connect</b> demands immediate patching.</p>

<p>Also, hear about <b>ALPHV BlackCat affiliates pleading guilty</b> to extortion, Disney's $10M COPPA penalty, Hong Kong's new "Money Safe" anti-fraud measures, and the mysterious delisting of Intellexa/Predator spyware individuals by OFAC. Finnish authorities have also seized a ship suspected of damaging a Baltic Sea subsea cable. Stay informed, stay secure!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1YxmTkJlBaug-uvF-EvCYoN9BlI4MQ6Oo" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767214211561</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, December 31, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **Active Threats & Breaches:** Two ex-incident responders pleaded guilty to launching BlackCat ransomware attacks against US organisations. An ex-Coinbase agent was arrested for selling 70,000 customer records, leading to phishing and attempted extortion. South Korea's KT Telecom faced scrutiny over insecure femtocells enabling fraud and communication snooping. Plus, the European Space Agency confirmed a breach of external servers, with 200GB of data exfiltrated.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ **New Techniques & Threat Actors:** Chinese state-backed Mustang Panda is deploying a novel kernel-mode rootkit for the ToneShell backdoor, targeting governments in Southeast and East Asia. Cybercrime group Silver Fox is hitting Indian users with tax-themed phishing delivering ValleyRAT via DLL hijacking, and utilising SEO poisoning for backdoor distribution. A new "Zoom Stealer" campaign, linked to DarkSpectre, is harvesting corporate meeting intelligence from 2.2 million users via malicious browser extensions.</p>

<p>⚠️ **Critical Vulnerabilities & AI Security:** A high-severity information disclosure flaw in MongoDB Server, dubbed "MongoBleed" (CVE-2025-14847), is under active exploitation, allowing unauthenticated attackers to leak sensitive server memory. OpenAI warns that prompt injection for AI browser agents may never be fully "solved," highlighting evolving security risks. We also touch on the call for a unified federal framework for AI regulation in the US amidst fragmented state laws.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 20:51:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TRRpwQ4l08VwD1hkfIBpN_4QH915FiF3" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767127873122</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, December 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your daily dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. Tracking significant breaches: insider threats at <b>Coupang</b> (33M customer data) & <b>Coinbase</b> (69.5k customers), plus external leaks impacting <b>Wired</b> subscribers (2.3M emails) & <b>Korean Air</b> employees.</p>

<p>💰 Ransomware rampages on: <b>Gentlemen ransomware</b> hits Oltenia Energy Complex, and a supply chain attack on <b>Marquis Software</b> affects up to 1.35 million bank customers via a SonicWall exploit. A critical compromise of <b>Trust Wallet's browser extension</b> also led to a $7 million crypto heist from 2,596 wallets.</p>

<p>⚠️ Stay ahead of active threats: <b>CVE-2025-14847 (MongoBleed)</b>, a critical MongoDB vulnerability allowing unauthenticated data leaks, and the ongoing exploitation of a five-year-old <b>Fortinet FortiOS 2FA bypass (CVE-2020-12812)</b> in SSL VPNs.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ New tradecraft: a sophisticated spear-phishing campaign using 27 malicious <b>npm packages</b> for resilient hosting, targeting critical infrastructure-adjacent organisations. Plus, a major arrest in a <b>clipper malware</b> operation that stole $1.2 million in crypto by swapping clipboard addresses on 2.8 million systems.</p>

<p>💡 We also analyse the inadequacy of traditional security frameworks against <b>AI-specific attack vectors</b>, with 23.77 million secrets leaked via AI systems in 2024 alone. Finally, explore Europe's push for digital sovereignty with <b>GAIA-X</b> and France's CNIL fining <b>Nexpublica France</b> €1.7 million for poor cyber security practices and GDPR violations.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fLueH5BWe8hSShxwBvQE4BdBFgiC23Cb" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1767041540556</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, December 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Dive into the latest cyber security developments with stdout. Today, we unpack a <b>high-severity vulnerability</b> impacting MongoDB: <i>CVE-2025-14847</i>. Rated <b>CVSS 8.7</b>, this flaw allows unauthenticated clients to read uninitialised heap memory, potentially exposing sensitive in-memory data. 🚨

We analyse the technical specifics: the issue stems from <i>improper handling of length parameter inconsistency</i> within Zlib compressed protocol headers. Mismatched length fields can lead to the disclosure of internal state information or pointers, which could significantly aid further exploitation. 🕵️‍♂️

Are your MongoDB deployments at risk? We detail the <b>affected versions</b>, including 8.2.0-8.2.3, 8.0.0-8.0.16, 7.0.0-7.0.26, 6.0.0-6.0.26, 5.0.0-5.0.31, 4.4.0-4.4.29, and all 4.2, 4.0, and 3.6 series. ⚠️ Crucially, <b>patches are available</b> in versions 8.2.3, 8.0.17, 7.0.28, 6.0.27, 5.0.32, and 4.4.30. If immediate patching isn't feasible, we discuss the recommended mitigation: disabling zlib compression on your MongoDB Server. 🛠️]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 20:49:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fSqv5W5WxDgiu9V4tky1HZoamtSvJmfr" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1766868551647</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, December 27, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[🚨 **Breach Alert!** The Trust Wallet Chrome extension (v2.68.0) was compromised, leading to an estimated $7 million in crypto losses through seed phrase exfiltration. Plus, pro-Russian group NoName057(16) claims a DDoS attack on France's La Poste, and GrubHub users received fraudulent crypto scam emails from a legitimate subdomain.

🕵️‍♂️ **APT Insights:** Kaspersky uncovers the China-linked Evasive Panda (Bronze Highland) APT, which deployed its MgBot backdoor via DNS poisoning and adversary-in-the-middle attacks. Discover their sophisticated techniques, including custom encryption and payloads disguised as PNGs, targeting entities in Türkiye, China, and India.

🤖 **AI in Cyber Warfare:** The accelerating pace of AI-driven attacks demands a strategic shift. We explore how threat actors exploit vulnerabilities within minutes and the critical need for defenders to leverage AI in defence. Plus, re-evaluate your tabletop exercises to simulate AI-powered attacks, including prompt injection and data exfiltration, and discover the importance of 'analog friction' for critical actions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 20:49:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1RqKFzOhv87D0xauJFvfQrQRZtv7hlWxS" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1766782177105</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, December 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Breaches & Attacks:</b> ShinyHunters targets PornHub (via Mixpanel SMS phishing) and SoundCloud, exposing millions of user records. RansomHouse hits Askul, stealing 740,000 customer details via compromised credentials lacking multi-factor authentication. Venezuela's PDVSA also reports a cyberattack impacting administrative systems.</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ <b>New Threats & Techniques:</b> Discover SantaStealer, a new malware-as-a-service aiming for in-memory operation, despite poor OpSec. Amazon Threat Intelligence reveals Russia's GRU (Sandworm) shifting to exploit misconfigured AWS edge devices for critical infrastructure access. Huntress Labs warns of a surge in hypervisor ransomware, with Akira leading the charge. Plus, a malicious NuGet package, "Tracer.Fody.NLog," found stealing crypto wallet data for nearly six years.</p>

<p>💥 <b>Active Exploitation:</b> Threat actors are actively weaponising the critical React2Shell vulnerability (CVE-2025-55182, CVSS 10.0) to deploy Linux backdoors and steal cloud/AI credentials, with over 111,000 IPs vulnerable. Also, unauthenticated bypass flaws in Fortinet FortiGate devices (CVE-2025-59718, CVE-2025-59719) are under active exploitation, allowing attackers to export device configurations if FortiCloud SSO is enabled. Patch immediately or disable FortiCloud SSO!</p>

<p>⚖️ <b>Privacy & Policy:</b> The Texas AG sues major smart TV manufacturers (Sony, Samsung, LG, Hisense, TCL) over alleged secret recording and selling of viewing habits via ACR. We also cover challenges for CISA renewal, MI6's tech-augmented intelligence vision, Google discontinuing its "dark web report" tool, and European law enforcement dismantling a €10M call centre fraud network.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:51:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=147fwvbQ_iWFuZKi11Qgb1DXZpN3z88iL" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1765918310570</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, December 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing 🎙️</h3>

Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security! 🚨 We analyse active cyber events, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities you need to know.

<p><b>Breaches & Active Attacks:</b> The French Interior Ministry confirms an email server attack, while Jaguar Land Rover reveals payroll data theft by Scattered Lapsus Hunters. Financial sector breaches hit Prosper Marketplace (13.1M) and 700Credit (5.8M), exposing sensitive PII. An insider breach at Opexus compromised federal agency data, and Spanish police nab a suspect for selling 64M records. Plus, track espionage from WIRTE/Ashen Lepus and APT36, alongside Operation Hanoi Thief targeting Vietnamese entities.</p>

<p><b>Techniques & Tradecraft:</b> Dive into evolving threat actor tradecraft. 🛠️ Active Adversary-in-the-Middle (AitM) phishing campaigns are bypassing MFA for Microsoft 365 and Okta SSO users, while large-scale phishing leverages fake Calendly invites and Browser-in-the-Browser techniques. Discover how digital calendar subscriptions are exploited for malicious content, and learn about the advanced tactics of 'The Gentlemen' ransomware. Interestingly, CyberVolk's VolkLocker RaaS has a critical flaw allowing free decryption!</p>

<p><b>Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b> Urgent patches are out for actively exploited zero-days! 🐞 Apple and Google addressed critical WebKit bugs (CVE-2025-14174, CVE-2025-43529) used by commercial spyware. We also cover a SOAPwn vulnerability in .NET, an un-CVE'd flaw in Gladinet CentreStack/Triofox, and the actively exploited WinRAR path traversal (CVE-2025-6218). Widespread exploitation continues for React2Shell (CVE-2025-55182), linked to multiple state-backed groups. Plus, a new Windows RasMan DoS zero-day has unofficial patches available.</p>

<p><b>Key Developments:</b> 🌐 CISA & MITRE release the 2025 CWE Top 25, with XSS still at number one. The NCSC weighs in on cyber-deception, and Microsoft rolls out new PowerShell security warnings and a Baseline Security Mode for Office. We also touch on upcoming US travel data requirements, a Ukrainian national charged for critical infrastructure attacks, and Denmark's controversial VPN proposals. Stay informed on these crucial developments!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:53:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ZXpCjx1TQjs-8qDYykhJXR9Uo3fgxVbT" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1765832030058</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, December 8, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🇦🇺 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🇦🇺</p>
<p>Today, we unpack a critical development for cybersecurity analysts: Portugal's new legal safe harbour for good-faith security research. 🛡️ This pivotal policy update, Article 8.o-A, now exempts ethical vulnerability detection from previous cybercrime classifications, empowering researchers to uncover exploitable weaknesses without legal fear. 🔍</p>
<p>We detail the strict conditions governing this exemption, including immediate disclosure, no economic benefit beyond professional compensation, and prohibitions against service disruption or data harm. This move aims to foster proactive identification of vulnerabilities and improve overall cyber resilience. 🚀</p>
<p>Understand how Portugal's stance aligns with an international trend, mirroring protections in Germany and the US, and its implications for responsible vulnerability disclosure and the future of ethical hacking. Essential insights for every analyst tracking the evolving threat landscape. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 20:49:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1OsZDgBpKddBxs3uas9TsF662Y93r9EmC" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1765140558751</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, December 7, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>🚨 stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing 🚨</h3>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats! This episode unpacks <b>CVE-2025-55182, "React2Shell,"</b> a critical 10.0 CVSS insecure deserialisation flaw in React Server Components. 💥 Actively exploited by China state-nexus groups like Earth Lamia, Jackpot Panda, and UNC5174, this vulnerability enables unauthenticated RCE, leading to AWS credential theft attempts, cryptojacking, and downloader deployment across an estimated 2.15 million internet-facing instances. CISA has added it to their KEV catalogue, confirming widespread impact and urgent mitigation needs.</p>

<p>We also analyse groundbreaking threat research: discover "IDEsaster" and "PromptPwnd," over 30 new vulnerabilities in AI coding tools like GitHub Copilot and Google Gemini. 🤖 These flaws leverage prompt injection and auto-approved agent calls for data exfiltration and RCE. Plus, learn about a novel SVG/CSS clickjacking technique by Lyra Rebane, bypassing the same-origin policy to exfiltrate sensitive data, even when JavaScript is blocked. 🖼️</p>

<p>Stay informed on evolving attack vectors: the FBI warns of a rise in AI-enhanced virtual kidnapping scams, using doctored social media images for fake proof-of-life in extortion attempts. 📞 Finally, we examine the shift to phishing-resistant passkeys, exploring their cryptographic benefits, widespread adoption, and the remaining social engineering risks for multi-device implementations. 🔑</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1nYJun6RPRb8W0MOr9uNUnq_fEayfw57P" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1765054294591</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, December 6, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🇦🇺</p>
<p>Stay ahead with stdout, your daily deep dive into critical cyber security developments. We analyse active cyber events, emerging attack techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities impacting analysts today.</p>

<p>🚨 <b>Active Breaches & Ransomware:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Pharmaceutical firm Inotiv impacted by a Qilin ransomware attack, affecting 9,542 individuals with 176GB of data exfiltrated.</li>
    <li>Asus confirms a third-party supplier compromise by the Everest ransomware gang, resulting in 1TB of camera source code theft.</li>
    <li>Barts Health NHS Trust reports a data breach following a Clop ransomware Oracle zero-day exploit, exposing patient invoice details and former employee data.</li>
</ul>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ <b>New Threats & Techniques:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Multi-agency advisories warn of <b>BRICKSTORM</b>, a sophisticated Golang backdoor attributed to PRC state-sponsored actors (UNC5221/Warp Panda), targeting VMware vSphere and Windows for long-term persistence and credential extraction.</li>
    <li>Revelations about Intellexa's Predator spyware detail remote access to customer systems, the "Aladdin" malicious mobile ad vector, and multiple Android/iOS zero-days enabling one-click infections.</li>
    <li>Anthropic's SCONE-bench highlights AI agents' increasing proficiency in exploiting smart contract vulnerabilities, making profitable autonomous exploitation technically feasible.</li>
    <li>Discover new zero-click agentic browser attacks capable of deleting entire Google Drives via LLM-powered assistants, alongside "HashJack" manipulating AI browsers with hidden prompts.</li>
    <li>The FBI warns of evolving virtual kidnapping scams, now using AI-altered social media photos for fake proof-of-life.</li>
</ul>

<p>⚠️ <b>Critical Vulnerabilities Under Active Exploitation:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li><b>React2Shell (CVE-2025-55182):</b> A critical insecure deserialisation flaw in React Server Components 'Flight' protocol, actively exploited by China-linked actors (Earth Lamia, Jackpot Panda) for unauthenticated RCE, causing a widespread Cloudflare outage.</li>
    <li>A command injection vulnerability in <b>Array AG Series VPN</b> devices (ArrayOS AG 9.4.5.8 and earlier) is being actively exploited to plant PHP webshells and create rogue users. A fix is available in ArrayOS 9.4.5.9.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1o1olSfTGD-GLR3IKbvz2HFPlzcaJIHMb" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764967917722</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, December 5, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Brief:</b> Your essential update on the past 24 hours in cyber security. We're dissecting active threats, emerging techniques, and critical vulnerabilities impacting organisations worldwide.</p>

<p>💥 <b>Active Attacks & Breaches:</b> Marquis Software Solutions suffered a ransomware attack, compromising 400,000 customers across 74 US banks, likely exploiting a SonicWall flaw. Cloudflare fended off a record 29.7 Tbps UDP DDoS from the AISURU botnet. Yearn Finance's yETH pool was exploited for $9 million due to a protocol flaw. The Shai-Hulud 2.0 supply chain attack exposed 400,000 secrets across npm and GitHub. Insider threats remain a concern, with arrests for data breaches at a government contractor and an Australian man sentenced for "Evil Twin" Wi-Fi attacks. Plus, COLDRIVER's spear-phishing campaigns are targeting non-profits with Proton Mail lures and adversary-in-the-middle pages.</p>

<p>🔬 <b>New Threats & Techniques:</b> Discover the latest in cyber tradecraft. The Chinese-speaking GoldFactory group is deploying Android malware droppers via modified banking apps in Southeast Asia. New variants of BPFDoor and Symbiote Linux malware are exploiting extended Berkeley Packet Filters for stealth, incorporating IPv6 and dynamic port hopping. We're also seeing TangleCrypt, a new Windows malware packer used in Qilin ransomware attacks, leveraging BYOVD for EDR evasion. A fake "prettier-vscode-plus" extension in the VS Code Marketplace delivered the Anivia loader and OctoRAT. Concerningly, Anthropic's Claude Skills have been weaponised to execute MedusaLocker ransomware, exploiting persistent permissions. Chinese hackers are also using Brickstorm malware on VMware vSphere to create hidden rogue VMs and steal snapshots.</p>

<p>⚠️ <b>Critical Vulnerabilities:</b> Stay ahead of the exploit curve. Attackers are actively exploiting CVE-2025–8489, a critical privilege escalation flaw in King Addons for Elementor (WordPress). A maximum-severity RCE vulnerability (CVSS 10.0) has been disclosed in React Server Components and frameworks (CVE-2025-55182/CVE-2025-66478), with exploitation considered imminent – patches are available and crucial. Microsoft also quietly patched CVE-2025-9491, a critical Windows shortcut (.lnk) file bug exploited since 2017 by state-sponsored groups.</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Threat Landscape & Strategic Shifts:</b> A new report highlights AI-powered attacks, large-scale JavaScript injection, and surging Magecart as key threats reshaping web security. Russia has blocked FaceTime and Snapchat, citing security concerns, while Let's Encrypt plans to reduce SSL/TLS certificate validity to 45 days by 2028 for improved internet security. International agencies, including Australia, have released joint guidelines for securely integrating AI into Operational Technology environments. NATO also conducted its largest-ever Cyber Coalition exercise, focusing on defending critical infrastructure against complex hybrid threats.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:53:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Qm7BVYDgl97ymHuEyQk8LPgTWaMSJgI1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764881606836</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, December 3, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber security developments! 🇦🇺 This <b>stdout</b> episode unpacks critical incidents, including the University of Pennsylvania's data breach, linked to Clop ransomware's exploitation of <b>CVE-2025-61882</b> in Oracle E-Business Suite. We also cover the FTC's action against Illuminate Education for a 2021 breach exposing 10 million student records, and the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea Council confirming a data exfiltration event from shared IT systems. Plus, a significant Microsoft Defender XDR portal outage disrupted threat hunting for over 10 hours.</p>

<p>Explore emerging threats: 🕵️‍♂️ The <b>Glassworm</b> malware campaign resurfaces, targeting VS Code extension marketplaces with invisible Unicode and Rust-based implants to steal GitHub, npm, and crypto wallet data. Iran-linked <b>MuddyWater</b> deploys the new <b>MuddyViper</b> backdoor via spearphishing critical infrastructure, disguised as a classic Snake game. North Korea's <b>Famous Chollima</b> (Lazarus) is luring engineers into a fake IT worker scheme using AI and deepfakes to bypass KYC. We also detail the <b>Shai-Hulud 2.0 NPM malware</b> attack, compromising over 800 packages and exposing 400,000 raw secrets across GitHub repositories.</p>

<p>Stay ahead of vulnerabilities: 🚨 Google's December Android security update patches 107 flaws, including two actively exploited zero-days (<b>CVE-2025-48633</b> & <b>CVE-2025-48572</b>) affecting the Android framework. In the wider threat landscape, Europol's <b>Operation Olympia</b> successfully shut down <b>Cryptomixer</b>, a crypto laundering platform that processed over €1.3 billion. We also examine new U.S. legislation proposing sanctions for 'critical cyber threat actors' and India's controversial mandate for the unremovable 'Sanchar Saathi' app on all new smartphones, raising privacy concerns. Finally, insights from the U.S. Senate Commerce Committee hearing on the <b>Salt Typhoon</b> operation highlight debates on regulatory oversight versus voluntary information sharing.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:51:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1VYIf5CDs7UiUjtMo2rI69Dr8KIkXZ05U" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764708685965</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, December 2, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🇦🇺 This episode dives into the last 24 hours of cyber developments, featuring a massive data breach impacting <b>33.7 million Coupang customers</b> and a critical <b>supply chain attack</b> on the SmartTube Android TV app. We also cover the French Football Federation's member data compromise.</p>

<p>We track active threats, including the <b>Lazarus Group's alleged $30 million crypto heist</b> from Upbit and the arrest of individuals exploiting <b>120,000 IP cameras</b>. Plus, an Australian man faces jail time for Wi-Fi Pineapple attacks, and authorities dismantle the <b>€1.3 billion Cryptomixer service</b>. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>New threat research reveals the <b>Tomiris actor's use of Telegram/Discord for C2</b>, and the seven-year "ShadyPanda" operation infecting <b>4.3 million Chrome/Edge users</b> with malicious browser extensions. 🕵️‍♀️ We also expose <b>17,000 live secrets</b> found in public GitLab repositories.</p>

<p>In regulatory news, Switzerland advises against hyperscale clouds for sensitive data, Singapore issues directives to Google/Apple on fake government messages, and Russia imposes 'restrictive measures' on WhatsApp. ⚖️ The FTC also settles with Illuminate Education over a 2021 student data breach, highlighting poor security practices and delayed notifications.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=17hHCA6ZOovAhqxEUwW7nBTzUDVY8VNTK" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764622340516</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, December 1, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Active Exploitation Alert!</b> CISA has added <strong>CVE-2021-26829</strong> to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue. This critical cross-site scripting flaw in OpenPLC ScadaBR is being actively exploited by the pro-Russian hacktivist group <strong>TwoNet</strong>. Learn how they gained initial access via default credentials, established persistence, and defaced HMI login pages in industrial control systems. We also detail TwoNet's evolving tactics, from DDoS to targeting industrial systems and offering ransomware-as-a-service. 🛠️</p>

<p>🌍 Plus, a deep dive into a long-running exploit operation uncovered by VulnCheck. Discover the Google Cloud-hosted Out-of-Band Application Security Testing (OAST) endpoint driving over 1,400 exploit attempts across 200+ CVEs, primarily targeting Brazil. We reveal the custom Java class file, <code>TouchFile.class</code>, expanding on a public Fastjson RCE exploit (v1.2.47) to execute commands and make outbound HTTP requests. Stay informed on the latest threats and techniques impacting the cyber landscape. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 20:49:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1zVX26Mi7au6qjDP4LJVgRHZEPMLR9qx9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764535770374</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 On <b>stdout</b> today: We dissect the significant data breach impacting Japanese beer giant Asahi Group Holdings. 🍺</p>
<p>Explore the fallout from the September ransomware attack, claimed by the <b>Qilin group</b>, which compromised personal data for up to <b>1.9 million individuals</b> – including customers, external contacts, and current/retired employees.</p>
<p><b>Key details include:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li><b>Exposed Data:</b> Full names, genders, physical & email addresses, phone numbers. Dates of birth for employees.</li>
    <li><b>No Payment Card Info:</b> Asahi confirms payment card details were <i>not</i> compromised.</li>
    <li><b>Ongoing Response:</b> Two months post-incident, Asahi continues system restoration and implements enhanced cyber defence strategies, including redesigned communication routes and tightened network controls. 🛡️</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 20:49:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15z1g_tgxnZpmH7mvN2r6DKT6XcTAsyR-" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764449345177</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 29, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential update on the last 24 hours in cybersecurity. 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks major breaches including a <b>$30M Solana heist</b> from Upbit, a data compromise affecting 230,000+ Brsk customers, the French Football Federation's data leak, and Asahi's encounter with <b>Qilin ransomware</b> impacting 1.5 million. 📉</p>

<p>We dive deep into new threats: the <b>Shai-Hulud 2.0 npm worm</b> that exfiltrated credentials from 25,000+ developers via CI/CD misconfiguration, and a critical <b>Microsoft Teams guest access blind spot</b> bypassing MDO365 protections. Plus, discover <b>17,000+ exposed live secrets</b> across GitLab Cloud repos, including GCP and OpenAI keys. 🔑</p>

<p>Also on the agenda: California's new universal opt-out law for data sharing, GrapheneOS's departure from OVHcloud over French privacy concerns, the UK's Budget forecast leak via a guessable URL, and an Australian man sentenced for operating "evil twin" Wi-Fi networks to steal credentials. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:50:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1D2mrhV1Ga-7DBRbu_y4E7jB8ZYKiOs5U" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764363041247</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, November 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Breaches & Active Campaigns:</b> This episode of stdout dives into the latest cyber incidents, including the permanent shutdown of <b>Crisis24's OnSolve CodeRED</b> following an INC ransomware attack and PII leak. We unpack <b>Asahi's Qilin ransomware</b> fallout impacting nearly two million individuals, and the <b>ShinyHunters breach</b> affecting Gainsight's Salesforce-connected apps. Plus, an <b>OpenAI API data breach</b> via smishing, the FCC's alarm over <b>US radio equipment hijacking</b>, and the <b>Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters'</b> new campaign targeting Zendesk users with typosquatting and weaponised helpdesk tickets.</p>

<p>🛠️ <b>New Threats & Techniques:</b> Get across the emerging tactics from threat actors. We analyse the <b>ShadowV2 botnet</b>, a Mirai variant exploiting 8 known vulnerabilities in IoT devices, and ESET's detailed report on <b>QuietEnvelope</b>, a sophisticated, state-sponsored toolset targeting OpenFind MailGates with stealthy backdoors. Discover how Russia-aligned <b>Water Gamayun APT</b> is exploiting MSC EvilTwin (CVE-2025-26633) for code injection, and the expansion of <b>Bloody Wolf APT's NetSupport RAT</b> attacks incorporating geofencing. We also cover the novel <b>EtherHiding technique</b> using blockchain smart contracts to deliver infostealers, and why <b>Tycoon 2FA (Storm-1747)</b> is now the most prolific Phishing-as-a-Service platform, leveraging real-time Adversary-in-the-Middle tactics.</p>

<p>🔍 <b>Vulnerabilities & Landscape Insights:</b> We examine an unpatched flaw in the <b>Retell AI API</b> enabling large-scale social engineering, and Kaspersky's report on a significant surge in phishing attacks, with nearly half targeting online shoppers. Hear Australia's Director-General of Security warn of <b>Chinese state-backed hackers probing critical infrastructure</b>, and a deep dive into the dark web job market's mirroring of real-world economies, with high demand for reverse engineers and penetration testers.</p>

<p>🛡️ <b>Security Posture & Regulatory Updates:</b> Stay informed on key defensive and policy shifts. Singapore mandates new <b>anti-spoofing protections</b> for Apple and Google by December 2025, and Microsoft announces plans to block unauthorised script injection attacks in <b>Entra ID authentication</b> from October 2026. Plus, updates on Microsoft Defender for Office 365's new capability to automatically remove malicious calendar entries.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 20:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1-g0KLiU6lDtZfBGwuE-WO1jZdLcY0K-6" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764276777959</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, November 27, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</b> This episode unpacks a flurry of recent attacks, including the INC Ransomware group's strike on Crisis24's OnSolve CodeRED, disrupting emergency alerts and exposing sensitive PII like clear-text passwords. We also cover a suspected ransomware incident affecting shared IT services for London councils, Comcast's $1.5M FCC fine following a vendor breach impacting 274,000 customers, and Dartmouth College's data theft linked to a Russian campaign targeting Oracle E-Business Suite. Plus, Gainsight's breach potentially compromised over 200 Salesforce instances, and a malicious Chrome extension, "Crypto Copilot," was found siphoning Solana funds with hidden fees.</p>

<p>🛠️ <b>New Threat Research & Techniques:</b> Dive into the latest tradecraft with Akira ransomware affiliates exploiting compromised SonicWall SSL VPNs of acquired companies for rapid lateral movement. We explore the rise of "AI-for-evil" Large Language Models like WormGPT 4, lowering the barrier for generating ransomware scripts and spear phishing emails. Discover how the Russia-aligned RomCom actor is using SocGholish fake updates to deliver Mythic Agent malware, and the Shai-Hulud v2 supply chain attack's expansion to the Maven ecosystem, compromising over 830 packages by stealing API keys and GitHub tokens. Also, get the lowdown on ShadowV2, a Mirai-based botnet that emerged during an AWS outage, infecting IoT devices globally.</p>

<p>🔓 <b>Exploited Vulnerabilities & Key Takeaways:</b> ASUS has released critical firmware updates for AiCloud routers, patching nine flaws including an authentication bypass (CVE-2025-59366) exploitable remotely. A high-severity signature verification bypass (CVE-2025-12816) in the 'node-forge' JavaScript library also demands attention, allowing unauthenticated attackers to craft malformed ASN.1 data. We also discuss the FBI's warning on over $262 million in Account Takeover fraud, the persistent challenges in Operational Technology security, and the House Homeland Security Committee's probe into AI tools like Claude being used in likely-Chinese espionage campaigns, reshaping cyber defence and offence. Plus, Thailand bans Worldcoin's iris scans, and Microsoft outlines plans to bolster Entra ID sign-in security against external script injection by late 2026.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:52:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1tayuFPcU7IuuRnoa5M3AX0JxBPwGYJFz" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764190371633</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, November 26, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber skirmishes! 💥 This episode of <strong>stdout</strong> unpacks critical active events, including Dartmouth College's data breach by the Clop gang via an Oracle zero-day (CVE-2025-61882), impacting over 1,400 individuals. We also cover the FBI's urgent warning on a surge in Account Takeover (ATO) fraud, siphoning over $262 million, and the Devman ransomware attack crippling Georgia's court systems. Plus, CISA alerts on sophisticated commercial spyware campaigns targeting high-value mobile users, exploiting zero-days in iOS, WhatsApp, and Samsung devices. 📱</p>

<p>Get the lowdown on new attack vectors and exploited flaws. 🛡️ Discover how the 'Recent Links' feature on online code-formatting tools exposed 80,000+ sensitive pastes, including Active Directory credentials and private keys. We also dissect the ClickFix social engineering campaign, which uses steganography in Windows Update lures to deliver the Rhadamanthys infostealer. CISA has added an actively exploited Oracle Identity Manager zero-day (CVE-2025-61757) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue, mandating urgent patching. 🚨</p>

<p>Explore cutting-edge threat research and future predictions. 🔬 The self-replicating Shai-Hulud worm has resurfaced, infecting nearly 500 npm packages and exposing 26,000+ GitHub repositories by stealing developer secrets. Learn about the Russian-linked campaign distributing the StealC V2 infostealer via malicious Blender .blend files, evading AV. We also delve into Anthropic's findings on LLM 'alignment faking' and Trend Micro's forecast for 2026 as the year of AI-aided ransomware, predicting agentic AI will democratise offensive capabilities. 🤖</p>

<p>Finally, stay informed on critical regulatory shifts and notable industry news. ⚖️ A coalition of civil liberties groups is demanding an inquiry into the UK's ICO over alleged 'collapse in enforcement activity' and reduced investigations. We also cover the arrest of a Russian cybersecurity entrepreneur on treason charges for criticising state apps and opposing anti-cyberfraud legislation. Plus, the Tor network is upgrading its security with the new Counter Galois Onion (CGO) encryption algorithm for enhanced resilience against traffic interception. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:51:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_62xqG9OFwMPJo9_QVdbnCz9kAs8jOUw" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764103900474</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, November 25, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</strong> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the latest 24-hour cyber security landscape. We analyse significant breaches, active threats, and critical vulnerabilities impacting organisations globally.</p>

<p>This episode unpacks major incidents including a voice phishing breach at <strong>Harvard University</strong>, data theft from <strong>Cox Enterprises</strong> via Clop ransomware, and the widespread <strong>Shai-Hulud npm supply chain attack</strong> compromising developer secrets. We also cover hacktivism targeting Donbas Post and data theft at SitusAMC.</p>

<p>🔬 Our threat intelligence segment reveals <strong>PlushDaemon APT's "EdgeStepper" implant</strong> hijacking DNS traffic, <strong>APT 31's attacks on Russia's IT sector</strong>, and how politically sensitive prompts can make <strong>AI models generate more vulnerable code</strong>. Plus, new <strong>ClickFix variants</strong> are using steganography to deliver info stealers.</p>

<p>🩹 Get the lowdown on actively exploited flaws: a critical deserialisation RCE in <strong>Microsoft WSUS (CVE-2025-59287)</strong>, five "trivial-to-exploit" vulnerabilities in <strong>Fluent Bit</strong> (urging updates to 4.1.1/4.0.12), and a years-old RCE in the <strong><code>glob</code> CLI tool (CVE-2025-64756)</strong>. Patch now!</p>

<p>⚖️ We also touch on CISA's warnings regarding <strong>commercial spyware and drone threats</strong> to critical infrastructure, the UK's push for <strong>software developer liability</strong>, and the controversial reversal of FCC cybersecurity rules. Stay informed, stay secure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 20:52:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TQ6bIGnYx6myUYM32TYcijcqQxD6ecWd" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764017531551</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, November 24, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>🚨 Data Breach Alert: Iberia & Supply Chain Risk</h3>
<p>Stay sharp with stdout! This episode unpicks a recent data breach at Spanish airline Iberia, where a third-party supplier compromise led to the exposure of customer names, emails, and loyalty card IDs. We analyse the incident's scope, noting the airline's assurance that no login credentials or payment information were affected, and the broader implications of supply chain vulnerabilities.</p>

<h3>🔒 Cross-Platform Security & Rust in Action</h3>
<p>Then, we shift gears to a major step in cross-platform security: Google's enablement of file sharing between Android Quick Share and Apple AirDrop. We explore how this new capability, initially for Pixel 10-series devices, was built with security at its core, featuring extensive threat modelling, independent audits, and the strategic use of Rust to mitigate memory-safety vulnerabilities. Discover the current 'Everyone for 10 minutes' mode and Google's push for a 'Contacts Only' future. 📱</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 20:49:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=14jLTP14K2ukGxyw53pwFNzsLD0RwR7K2" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763930964159</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 23, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats! Today, we unpack a critical, actively exploited pre-authentication Remote Code Execution (RCE) vulnerability in <b>Oracle Identity Manager (CVE-2025-61757)</b>, now in CISA's KEV <a href="https://www.cisa.gov/known-exploited-vulnerabilities-catalog">catalogue</a>. Discover how a simple URL parameter bypasses authentication, enabling unauthenticated Groovy script execution and suspected zero-day exploitation since August.</p>
<p>We also expose a massive <b>WhatsApp data scraping incident</b> that harvested 3.5 billion user records by abusing an unthrottled API. Plus, get the lowdown on China-linked <b>APT31 (Violet Typhoon)</b>, which stealthily targeted the Russian IT sector, leveraging legitimate cloud services and social media for C2 and exfiltration, remaining undetected for extended periods. 🕵️‍♂️</p>
<p>Finally, explore <b>Matrix Push C2</b>, a new malware-as-a-service platform weaponising browser notifications for fileless, cross-platform phishing attacks. Learn how this innovative framework bypasses traditional security controls, offering persistent communication and advanced victim tracking, including enumerating cryptocurrency wallets. Stay ahead with actionable intelligence for cyber security analysts. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 20:49:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1j4AONj8t8jWrajP40UJdjqsrEAvh6DFq" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763844592173</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catch the latest in cyber! 🇦🇺 This daily dive into the last 24 hours covers critical breaches, emerging threats, and legal shifts impacting InfoSec professionals.</p>

<p>🚨 **Active Threats & Breaches:** Salesforce customers are again reeling from a third-party vendor breach, with ShinyHunters (UNC6240) claiming responsibility for compromising data from nearly 1,000 organisations. We also unpack an insider threat at CrowdStrike and ransomware attacks hitting local government entities. Plus, the UK NCA's "Operation Destabilise" has exposed a Russian-linked money laundering network funnelling cybercrime profits into Russia's military-industrial complex. 💰</p>

<p>🕵️‍♂️ **New Techniques & APTs:** Google TAG reveals "BadAudio," a previously undocumented malware used by China-linked APT24 in a three-year espionage campaign, employing sophisticated DLL hijacking and control flow flattening. Another report details how China-linked APT31 infiltrated Russia’s technology sector for years, exfiltrating data and masking activity via social media and timed intrusions. </p>

<p>⚠️ **Vulnerabilities & Legal Landscape:** Grafana Labs issues a max severity warning for CVE-2025-41115 in Grafana Enterprise, allowing privilege escalation via SCIM provisioning. We also highlight the critical risks posed by legacy web forms across government agencies. In legal news, two British teenagers plead not guilty to Computer Misuse Act offences related to the Transport for London attack, while the SEC voluntarily dismisses its lawsuit against SolarWinds. Regulatory updates include the FCC rolling back telecom cybersecurity mandates and charges laid over attempts to smuggle restricted Nvidia AI chips to China. ⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:51:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1G88QiY8jQeUJAwDrx4TCBKjWjZHmLm-7" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763758296212</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, November 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! 🇦🇺</p>

<p>We're diving deep into active threats, starting with Iran-linked <b>Imperial Kitten</b> and <b>MuddyWater</b> blurring lines between cyber and kinetic warfare, mapping ship AIS and accessing CCTV before missile strikes. 🚢 Major data breaches also hit <b>PowerSchool</b> (millions of student records due to school board negligence), <b>Salesforce</b> (customer data theft linked to Gainsight, OAuth token revocation), and <b>FS Italiane Group</b> (2.3 TB exposed via IT provider). Legal actions see an Ohio IT contractor jailed for sabotage, crypto scammers sentenced, and arrests of <b>Void Blizzard</b> and <b>Jabber Zeus</b> affiliates. ⚖️</p>

<p>Discover new attack techniques: MI5 warns of Chinese operatives using LinkedIn for intelligence. 🕵️‍♀️ Malicious VPN/ad-blocking browser extensions are intercepting web traffic, while the <b>Sneaky2FA</b> phishing kit now uses Browser-in-the-Browser (BitB) to bypass MFA. 🎣 macOS users beware <b>NovaStealer</b>, replacing Ledger/Trezor apps, and Android users, <b>Sturnus</b> can capture E2EE messages from Signal, WhatsApp, and Telegram. Researchers also released <b>SharpParty</b> for EDR evasion via Windows Thread Pools. 🛡️</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities demand immediate attention! 🚨 <b>Fortinet FortiWeb</b> has two actively exploited zero-days (CVE-2025-58034, CVE-2025-64446), including an authenticated OS command injection and unauthenticated admin command execution. CISA has added one to its KEV <b>catalogue</b>. A critical pre-auth RCE (CVE-2025-61757) in <b>Oracle Fusion Middleware Identity Manager</b> and an unpatched two-year-old flaw (CVE-2023-48022) in the <b>Ray AI framework</b> are being exploited by <b>ShadowRay 2.0</b> for cryptomining. Patch alerts also for <b>glob CLI</b>, EOL <b>D-Link DIR-878</b> routers, <b>SonicWall SonicOS SSLVPN</b> DoS, and <b>Shelly Pro 4PM</b> smart relays. GreyNoise reports a 40-fold surge in scanning for <b>Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect VPN</b>, often a precursor to new vulnerabilities. 📈</p>

<p>Plus, the EU proposes GDPR changes for AI training, the FCC rescinds Biden-era telecom cyber regs, and sanctions hit Russian bulletproof hosting providers. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:53:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1U3iB_Z_OipHS7nV-suv5KnRhwS9ruX12" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763671985889</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, November 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Threat Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>"Operation WrtHug," a China-linked campaign, has compromised 50,000 end-of-life ASUS WRT routers for suspected espionage. Globally, "ShadowRay 2.0" is cryptojacking over 230,000 Ray AI clusters by exploiting a critical RCE (CVE-2023-48022, CVSS 9.8). Major data breaches impacting 62 million students via PowerSchool and a Russian insurer, alongside a $25 million crypto laundering conviction, also feature in the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>Uncover new attack vectors and threat intelligence: China-linked APT "PlushDaemon" is deploying the Go-based EdgeStepper implant for adversary-in-the-middle attacks, facilitating extensive data theft. Learn about a critical vulnerability in ServiceNow's Now Assist AI allowing second-order prompt injection, and a Python-based WhatsApp worm spreading the Eternidade Stealer across Brazilian devices. Amazon Threat Intelligence warns of "cyber-enabled kinetic targeting" by nation-states, while MI5 alerts on Chinese intelligence recruitment in UK democratic institutions.</p>

<p>Stay ahead of actively exploited vulnerabilities: Fortinet warns of an OS command injection (CVE-2025-58034) in FortiWeb, now on CISA's KEV catalogue. A symbolic link-based RCE (CVE-2025-11001) in 7-Zip is under active exploitation, and a critical PHP command injection (CVE-2025-9501) in the W3 Total Cache WordPress plugin allows unauthenticated RCE.</p>

<p>Finally, we examine critical data privacy and regulatory shifts: WhatsApp's enumeration flaw exposed 3.5 billion user records, while the Airlines Reporting Corporation ceases selling travel data to government agencies. The temporary expiration of CISA 2015 raises concerns, and the US, UK, and Australia sanction Russian bulletproof hosting provider Media Land. The EU's proposed "Digital Omnibus" package could significantly reshape GDPR and AI Act regulations, potentially rolling back privacy protections.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 20:53:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1hFH456G3kmCOoQ4eabDSUT27G4veEGL4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763585600552</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 Dive into the latest cyber developments, from active breaches to emerging attack techniques.</p>

<p>We unpack Logitech's data breach by the Clop gang, exploiting a third-party zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) to exfiltrate data. Discover the "ClickFix" malware campaign, which ingeniously abuses the decades-old Finger protocol (TCP port 79) as a LOLBIN to deliver Python infostealers and NetSupport Manager RATs. 🛡️</p>

<p>Analyse the RondoDox botnet's active exploitation of unpatched XWiki servers via critical eval injection vulnerability CVE-2025-24893 (CVSS 9.8), enabling arbitrary remote code execution for guest users. This flaw, now in CISA's KEV catalogue, is being leveraged for DDoS attacks, crypto mining, and reverse shells. 🚨</p>

<p>Finally, uncover the illicit scheme where five U.S. citizens aided North Korean IT workers in infiltrating 136 U.S. companies, generating over $2.2 million for the DPRK regime. Plus, the Department of Justice's pursuit of $15 million in cryptocurrency seized from APT38 (BlueNoroff). 💰</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:49:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=13pXULGzKdJJGdKMgtKHRXhHNGIL3l_uT" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763239794424</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 15, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential 24-hour intel drop for Cyber Security Analysts. Today, we unpack a flurry of active threats and critical vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Catch up on significant breaches including <b>DoorDash's</b> third incident via social engineering, <b>Clop's</b> unverified claim against NHS.uk, and <b>ShinyHunters'</b> hit on Checkout.com's legacy systems. Dive into the controversial use of Anthropic's Claude Code AI by Chinese state-sponsored actors (GTG-1002) for digital intrusions, and a 15,000+ IP botnet disrupting a Russian port operator. Plus, the FBI warns of an aggressive health insurance scam targeting Chinese speakers in the US. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>On the threat intelligence front, CISA and the FBI update on <b>Akira ransomware's</b> expansion to Nutanix AHV, now a top-five variant exploiting SonicWall and Veeam. Cisco Talos details <b>Kraken ransomware</b>, a HelloKitty successor benchmarking systems for optimal encryption, often via SMB. We also cover the 'IndonesianFoods' self-spreading worm flooding the npm registry with 150,000+ packages for crypto token farming. 🐛</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities demand immediate attention: Fortinet confirms a silently patched <b>FortiWeb zero-day (CVE-2025-64446)</b>, actively exploited since October to create admin users. ASUS warns of a critical <b>authentication bypass (CVE-2025-59367)</b> in DSL routers. Plus, discover "ShadowMQ" – remote code execution flaws impacting major AI inference frameworks from Meta, Nvidia, Microsoft, and PyTorch projects due to unsafe ZeroMQ and Python pickle deserialisation. 💥</p>

<p>Finally, we look at government actions: The US establishes a "Scam Center Strike Force" against Chinese crypto scam networks, seizing over $401 million. A suspected Russian GRU officer faces extradition, and Google disrupts the "Smishing Triad's" Lighthouse text scam kit. The Justice Department secures guilty pleas in a North Korean IT worker scam, seizing $15 million from APT38. An op-ed highlights the urgent need for a cybersecurity talent incubator in the retail sector. ⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 09:48:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Dq9JjukkxzUPaMRBcdD72vYgRZ6d8epF" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1763200137977</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, November 13, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Major disruptions include the takedown of the <strong>Rhadamanthys infostealer</strong> operation and a UK court sentencing a fraudster for a <strong>£5 billion Bitcoin scam</strong>. 💰 We analyse the <strong>Qilin ransomware attack</strong> on UK pathology provider Synnovis, compromising sensitive patient data and severely disrupting NHS services. Plus, an APT group exploited <strong>zero-day vulnerabilities</strong> in Citrix NetScaler ADC/Gateway (CVE-2025-5777) and Cisco ISE (CVE-2025-20337), deploying custom web shells for likely espionage. 🕵️</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Microsoft's latest Patch Tuesday addressed 63 defects, including an <strong>actively exploited Windows Kernel zero-day</strong> (CVE-2025-62215) and a critical RCE (CVE-2025-60724). 💥 Synology users, update immediately for a critical <strong>BeeStation OS RCE</strong> (CVE-2025-12686) publicly demonstrated at Pwn2Own. We also cover the resurgence of <strong>DanaBot malware</strong> with a new variant using Tor C2 infrastructure, and Google's lawsuit against the "Lighthouse" phishing-as-a-service scheme. 🎣</p>

<p>Hear Australia's spy chief warn of "high-impact sabotage" on critical infrastructure by authoritarian regimes, and the UK CAA's concerns about inevitable organised <strong>drone attacks on airports</strong>. ✈️ We also explore the new UK Cyber Security and Resilience Bill, expanding regulations to datacentres and MSPs, and Google's "Private AI Compute" for secure cloud processing. 🔒</p>

<p>Key updates include the Kochava data broker settlement, Public Citizen's deepfake warnings for OpenAI's Sora 2, and Windows 11's native support for third-party passkey managers.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1B7yXkadfexWUsU7LcabUMhw9tEau221T" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762980764551</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, November 12, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your daily intel on the cyber frontline!</b> 🚨</p>

<p>This episode dives deep into the last 24 hours of infosec, covering critical breaches, cunning new attack techniques, and urgent vulnerability disclosures. We unpack the confirmed nation-state theft of F5 BIG-IP source code and 44 undisclosed vulnerabilities, raising long-term supply chain concerns. Hear about the Yanluowang IAB pleading guilty, linked to $1.5M in ransoms, and North Korean APT37 (KONNI) actively abusing Google's "Find Hub" to track and wipe Android devices. Plus, Clop's latest victim, GlobalLogic, saw over 10,000 employee records exfiltrated via exploited Oracle E-Business Suite flaws (<b>CVE-2025-61882, CVE-2025-61884</b>). We also cover the "Bitcoin Queen's" sentencing for laundering $7.3B in crypto.</p>

<p>🔬 <b>New Threats & Techniques:</b> Discover "Quantum Route Redirect" (QRR), a sophisticated Phishing-as-a-Service platform targeting Microsoft 365 users globally with 1,000+ domains and bot filtering. Microsoft researchers unveil "Whisper Leak," a side-channel attack inferring LLM prompt topics from encrypted network traffic. We also track GootLoader's resurgence with advanced evasion tactics, including custom WOFF2 fonts and Z85 encoding, leading to Supper backdoor and INC ransomware deployments.</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Vulnerability Watch:</b> Microsoft's November Patch Tuesday addresses 63 flaws, including an actively exploited Windows Kernel EoP zero-day (<b>CVE-2025-62215</b>) and four critical vulnerabilities. SAP issues urgent patches for a max severity 10.0 CVSS hardcoded credentials flaw (<b>CVE-2025-42890</b>) and a critical code injection (<b>CVE-2025-42887</b>). Learn how attackers exploited Gladinet Triofox's authentication bypass (<b>CVE-2025-12480</b>) to achieve SYSTEM privileges and remote code execution. Finally, UK cyber insurers report a staggering 230% increase in ransomware payouts, totalling £197 million, highlighting the escalating threat landscape.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 20:51:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1usPUbdgT3pu1pDBTL5qaiqDKZ_htuLJ_" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762894287080</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, November 11, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! 🎧</p>

<p>This episode unpacks critical active events, including the <b>Clop ransomware's Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882)</b> impacting Allianz UK, and a massive data breach at Chinese firm Knownsec exposing state-owned cyber weapons and global target lists. We also cover a widespread <b>PureRAT phishing campaign</b> targeting the hospitality sector and the conviction of a Yanluowang ransomware Initial Access Broker. 💥</p>

<p>Dive into new threat research: discover how <b>Curly COMrades abuses Hyper-V</b> for stealthy malware deployment, the rise of <b>Cephalus Go-based ransomware</b> exploiting RDP, and malicious NuGet packages with time-delayed logic bombs. Plus, we examine information stealer campaigns leveraging EvilAI-created installers and Aurologic GmbH's role as a high-risk hosting hub. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: CISA orders patching for a <b>Samsung zero-day (CVE-2025-21042)</b> actively exploited by LandFall spyware, and a severe RCE in the <b><code>expr-eval</code> JavaScript library (CVE-2025-12735)</b>. We also detail patched flaws in Microsoft Teams, SimpleHelp RMM exploits leading to ransomware, and supply chain risks in Advanced Installer. 🚨</p>

<p>Finally, we explore the evolving landscape of AI in security, from Cisco's new 17-billion parameter model to Microsoft's "Agent 365" and the "Whisper Leak" side-channel attack. Get the lowdown on the temporary extension of the U.S. CISA Act, Australia's sanctions against North Korean cybercrime, and new privacy features from WhatsApp and Microsoft Authenticator. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1jQoSfyYFnSv10qQ92FOFblTrvAwP0wsz" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762807950625</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, November 10, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Unpacking critical cyber developments from the last 24 hours. </p>

<p>First up, we're diving into three new <b>runC vulnerabilities</b> (CVE-2025-31133, CVE-2025-52565, CVE-2025-52881) impacting <b>Docker and Kubernetes container runtimes</b>. These flaws could allow attackers to <b>bypass container isolation</b> and gain <b>root access to the host system</b> by manipulating <code>/dev/null</code> and <code>/dev/console</code> bind-mounts. Patches are available in runC versions 1.2.8, 1.3.3, and 1.4.0-rc.3+, with user namespaces and rootless containers offering key mitigations. </p>

<p>📱 Next, the Swiss National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) warns of a sophisticated new <b>iPhone phishing scam</b>. Threat actors are sending targeted smishing texts, often with convincing details from the device's lock screen, to trick lost iPhone owners into clicking fake "Find My" links. The goal? To <b>steal Apple ID credentials</b> and potentially <b>bypass Activation Lock</b> for device resale. Remember: enable Lost Mode immediately, use a dedicated email for contact details, and protect your SIM with a PIN. Apple will never contact you via SMS or email about a found device. 🎣</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:49:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=11dZUbr1kDMUsi8w8ijxeZryVNspozvkP" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762721372682</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 9, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Key cyber developments from the last 24 hours:</p>

<p>A Russian national has pleaded guilty as an Initial Access Broker for the Yanluowang ransomware group, facilitating attacks on seven US businesses and demanding $24 million. ⚖️</p>

<p>New threat research reveals:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Malicious NuGet packages with "time bombs" set for 2027/2028, targeting .NET database providers and impersonating the Sharp7 library for Siemens S7 industrial control devices. These could cause immediate operational stops or data corruption. Organisations are advised to audit assets. 💣</li>
    <li>Microsoft's "Whisper Leak" — a novel side-channel attack inferring AI chatbot conversation topics from encrypted TLS traffic with over 98% accuracy, posing significant privacy risks to LLMs. 🤫</li>
</ul>

<p>On exploited vulnerabilities:</p>
<ul>
    <li>LANDFALL, a commercial-grade Android spyware, exploited a zero-day (CVE-2025-21042) in Samsung Galaxy devices for nearly a year. The surveillance campaign, likely starting in July 2024, targeted specific Samsung Galaxy devices in the Middle East via zero-click attacks, often through crafted images. This spyware records calls, tracks locations, and harvests data, potentially linked to state-sponsored actors. 📱🕵️‍♂️</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Wx-rbG0XtWs7jTBTfCWD2jU9dD972inZ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762635011930</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 8, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout Daily Intel: Cyber Events & Exploits** 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. We unpack a suspected foreign actor breach at the US Congressional Budget Office and the UK's first-ever economic impact classification for a cyberattack, with Jaguar Land Rover's incident costing up to £2.1 billion. 💸</p>

<p>Threat intel reveals a new wave of sophisticated attacks:</p>
<ul>
    <li>📱 **"Landfall" Android Spyware:** Exploiting a zero-day (CVE-2025-21042) via WhatsApp DNG images for zero-click surveillance on Samsung Galaxy phones.</li>
    <li>🦠 **Gootloader Resurgence:** Delivering Rhysida ransomware with rapid domain controller compromise, using SEO poisoning and custom fonts for obfuscation.</li>
    <li>🛠️ **Malicious Dev Tools:** Watch out for rogue VS Code extensions, npm packages distributing Vidar Stealer, and NuGet time-bomb packages targeting Siemens S7 PLCs.</li>
    <li>🇨🇳 **China-linked APTs:** Exploiting legacy vulnerabilities for long-term persistence, deploying custom loaders and RATs, with ties to Salt Typhoon and Space Pirates.</li>
</ul>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Cisco ASA/FTD zero-days (CVE-2025-20362, CVE-2025-20333) are now actively exploited for denial-of-service attacks, forcing reboots. 🛡️ QNAP has patched seven zero-days, successfully exploited at Pwn2Own Ireland 2025. Update your systems immediately! 🩹</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, Google introduces new features to combat review extortion and highlights prevalent scams. 🌐 We analyse Illuminate Education's $5.1M fine for a data breach, Microsoft's EU data sovereignty efforts, and EPIC's concerns over government data mining. 🔒 New global regulations like DORA and SEC rules are driving a shift towards greater cyber accountability. ⚖️ Finally, the Department of Defense's revised master plan for cyber forces outlines a long road ahead for talent attraction and retention. 🏛️🚀</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:52:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fH756o5cftDZsuFeJ7r7kGQgADXQEiIW" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762548754051</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, November 7, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the latest 24-hour cyber developments, tailored for Cyber Security Analysts. Today, we're unpacking critical breaches, novel attack techniques, and urgent vulnerability alerts.</p>

<p><b>Breaches & Intrusions:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Hyundai AutoEver America confirms a data breach exposing names, Social Security Numbers, and driver's licences.</li>
    <li>Japanese media giant Nikkei reports a breach impacting over 17,000 employees and partners after malware compromised an internal Slack workspace.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>New Threats & Techniques:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Gootloader resurfaces with advanced SEO poisoning, utilising custom web fonts and malformed Zip archives to evade analysis, dropping the Supper SOCKS5 backdoor.</li>
    <li>Discover InedibleOchotense, a new Russia-aligned threat cluster impersonating ESET in spear-phishing campaigns against Ukrainian entities, deploying the Tor-enabled Kalambur backdoor.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Exploits:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Cisco issues urgent patches for critical flaws (CVE-2025-20354, CVE-2025-20358) in Unified Contact Center Express (UCCX), allowing unauthenticated RCE and authentication bypass.</li>
    <li>Cisco also warns of ongoing, sophisticated attacks by the government-backed ArcaneDoor group targeting Secure ASA and FTD firewalls, causing denial-of-service and employing zero-days for persistence.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Active Threat Landscape:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Russian state-backed Sandworm hackers are deploying destructive data-wiping malware against Ukraine's education, government, and critical grain sector.</li>
    <li>The State of Nevada releases a transparent after-action report detailing a ransomware attack, from initial compromise via a trojanised Google ad to a $1.5M recovery effort.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Privacy & Security Insights:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>An Italian executive reveals he was targeted with Paragon spyware, adding to a growing list of victims.</li>
    <li>Comparitech's latest study highlights persistent human laziness in password choices, with "123456" and "admin" remaining top offenders.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stay informed, stay secure. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1nQGLeFpgir9WYs92X3TXmarXXSr8vZpv" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762462323316</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, November 6, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</strong> The University of Pennsylvania confirms a data breach exposing 1.2 million donor records and internal documents via compromised credentials. SonicWall attributes a September incident to state-sponsored hackers accessing firewall configuration data. Plus, Operation Chargeback dismantles credit card fraud networks, recovering over €300 million from 4.3 million victims globally.</p>

<p>🤖 <strong>Emerging Threats & Tradecraft:</strong> Google's Threat Intelligence Group reveals a significant shift towards AI-powered malware, with new families leveraging LLMs for dynamic self-modification and obfuscation. State-backed actors are also abusing Google's Gemini LLM for vulnerability research and phishing. Tenable researchers uncover indirect prompt injection flaws in OpenAI's ChatGPT, while Russia-linked Curly COMrades employ malicious Alpine Linux VMs within Hyper-V for covert persistence. An Iranian threat cluster, UNK_SmudgedSerpent, targets US academics with social engineering and legitimate RMM tools.</p>

<p>⚠️ <strong>Critical Vulnerabilities Exploited:</strong> CISA adds two actively exploited flaws to its KEV catalog: a file disclosure in Gladinet CentreStack/Triofox (CVE-2025-11371) and an unauthenticated RCE in Control Web Panel (CVE-2025-48703). Urgent updates are also needed for actively exploited WordPress plugins (WP Freeio, Noo JobMonster, Post SMTP) enabling privilege escalation. AMD addresses a high-severity flaw (CVE-2025-62626) in Zen 5 CPUs that could weaken cryptographic keys.</p>

<p>⚖️ <strong>Regulatory & Privacy Shifts:</strong> The US DHS proposes a controversial expansion of biometric data collection for immigration. The US Treasury sanctions North Korean entities laundering cryptocurrency to fund weapons programs. The UK launches a Telecoms Charter to combat fraud, and US House GOP leaders push for restrictions on Chinese tech in critical industries. Also, Google's $32 billion acquisition of Wiz receives US DOJ clearance, and a new memory-safe C/C++ compiler, Fil-C, earns a favourable review.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1MXXPhCh-8pl0WBZvOc6Q2T2LzGGOw8TK" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762375917630</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, November 5, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Stay across the latest in cyber security. We're tracking a massive <b>$100M+ crypto heist</b> from Balancer's DeFi pools, potentially linked to North Korean groups, alongside a concerning <b>insider threat</b> where cyber professionals deployed ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware. Sweden's Miljödata suffered a breach impacting 1.5 million, while Poland faced a wave of attacks, possibly tied to Russian hybrid warfare. 💰</p>

<p>Analyse new threats: discover <b>"SleepyDuck,"</b> a malicious Solidity VSCode extension using Ethereum smart contracts for resilient command-and-control. Explore sophisticated campaigns targeting the <b>defence sector</b>, including Operation SkyCloak's Tor-enabled backdoors and Russia's Curly COMrades exploiting Microsoft Hyper-V to bypass EDR. We also cover <b>"SesameOp,"</b> a novel backdoor abusing OpenAI's Assistants API for stealthy C2, and the alarming <b>67% surge in mobile malware</b> on Google Play. 📱</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Google's AI agent, Big Sleep, uncovered <b>five critical WebKit flaws</b> in Apple Safari, now patched. We also delve into the "dramatic" rise in cybercrime involving physical violence in Europe, the retraction of a controversial AI-driven ransomware report, and significant privacy concerns around health data and EU Commission location tracking. Get the essential updates. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:52:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1KE-pzCXcVq1_lZs3ASxkEFrMq_WRu2eu" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762289543981</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, November 4, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay sharp with your daily dose of cyber intelligence! 🇦🇺 This episode of <b>stdout</b> unpacks the last 24 hours, highlighting critical active events. We're tracking the University of Pennsylvania's 1.2 million donor record breach via compromised SSO, and Askul's 1.1TB data leak following a <i>RansomHouse</i> attack. Discover how cybercriminals are now collaborating with organised crime to hijack physical cargo using compromised RMM tools like <i>ScreenConnect</i>. Plus, hear about the indictment of three former IR pros for <i>BlackCat</i> ransomware attacks and SK Telecom's massive financial hit from a data breach.</p>

<p>Dive into cutting-edge threat research, including Australia's ASD warning on the <i>"BADCANDY"</i> implant actively targeting unpatched Cisco IOS XE (CVE-2023-20198). 🚨 We reveal <i>"Airstalk,"</i> a suspected nation-state Windows malware exfiltrating data from Omnissa Workspace ONE, and new Android threats like <i>"BankBot-YNRK"</i> and <i>"DeliveryRAT."</i> Uncover how <i>Qilin</i> ransomware now leverages WSL for Linux encryptors, and the novel <i>"SesameOp"</i> backdoor using OpenAI's API for covert C2. We also detail malicious VS Code extensions, Discord-based RATs, and <i>BlueNoroff's</i> multi-platform <i>"GhostCall"</i> campaigns targeting Web3 professionals.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, we break down Microsoft's hotpatching woes with KB5070881 for a critical WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287), and significant flaws in LUKS2 disk encryption impacting confidential computing systems. 🔒 Plus, learn about exposed API keys and a backdoor in Tata Motors' sites, risking over 70 terabytes of sensitive data.</p>

<p>Beyond the immediate threats, we examine the heightened cyberattack risks to European power grids and hacktivist targeting of internet-exposed industrial control systems. 🌐 Proton's new Data Breach Observatory reveals 306.1 million leaked records, with small and medium-sized businesses as prime targets. We also touch on WhatsApp's biometric passkeys, the push for cyber reinsurance, and MITRE ATT&CK v18's enhanced mobile and ICS coverage. Stay informed, stay secure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:53:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TRErvt94SX95Rp_i9v-FIhcIkPXlJCke" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762203220254</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 2, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Alert: Cisco IOS XE Under Siege!</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Active exploitation of <b>CVE-2023-20198</b>, a critical 10.0 CVSS vulnerability, is impacting unpatched Cisco IOS XE devices. China-linked threat actors, including Salt Typhoon, are weaponising the low-equity BADCANDY Lua-based web shell to create privileged accounts and seize control. An urgent ASD bulletin highlights hundreds of Australian devices compromised since late 2023. Essential hardening guidelines are crucial to protect infrastructure from re-infection.</p>

<p>📧 A politically motivated cyber incident at the University of Pennsylvania saw an offensive email targeting thousands of students, highlighting potential email system compromises and data breach threats. This bears hallmarks of similar attacks following the Supreme Court's affirmative action ruling.</p>

<p>⚖️ Federal law enforcement has arrested Baron Cain Martin, an alleged leader of the violent extremist group 764. Martin faces 29 charges, including providing material support to terrorists and the production/distribution of child sexual abuse material. The group leverages cyber means for grooming and extortion, with ongoing law enforcement efforts to dismantle such networks.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:50:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1CtM31DRm-wtSbS-sy5f1m1Fd66XstaQR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762030206899</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 1, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>stdout: Key Cyber Developments (Last 24 Hrs)</strong> 🚨</p>
<p>This episode covers the extradition of an alleged <strong>Conti ransomware</strong> member and arrests linked to <strong>Meduza Stealer</strong> in Russia. We also analyse a university breach sending offensive emails.</p>
<p>🔍 <strong>Threat Intel & Exploits:</strong> Discover <strong>Airstalk</strong>, a new malware by CL-STA-1009 misusing AirWatch MDM APIs for covert C2. We detail active exploitation of an unpatched <strong>Windows LNK vulnerability (CVE-2025-9491)</strong> by UNC6384/Mustang Panda targeting EU diplomacy. CISA adds a <strong>VMware Tools/Aria zero-day (CVE-2025-41244)</strong> and a <strong>Linux kernel flaw (CVE-2024-1086)</strong>, now used in ransomware, to its KEV catalogue.</p>
<p>🔥 <strong>Critical Warnings:</strong> The Australian government warns of ongoing exploitation of <strong>Cisco IOS XE (CVE-2023-20198)</strong> by state actors like Salt Typhoon, planting BadCandy webshells. Storm-1849/UAT4356 is actively scanning and exploiting <strong>Cisco ASA (CVE-2025-30333, CVE-2025-20362)</strong> against US financials and government. CISA/NSA release guidance to harden Exchange and WSUS following exploitation of <strong>WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287)</strong>.</p>
<p>🛡️ <strong>Policy & Privacy:</strong> We touch on the critical need for government-industry collaboration, privacy concerns around the <strong>Digital Euro</strong>, and the FCC's plan to rescind telecom cybersecurity regulations. Also, NHS hospitals face risks due to <strong>Windows 11 upgrade delays</strong>, and Microsoft Edge rolls out a new <strong>scareware sensor</strong>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1s77qvqEWnySRA8brlmtDyzHzqb3PION5" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761943977458</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 31, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily:</b> Unpacking the last 24 hours in cyber security. 🚨</p>

<p>This episode dives into critical active events, including hacktivists tampering with Canadian industrial control systems and an ex-L3Harris Trenchant GM pleading guilty to selling US cyber-exploits to a Russian broker. We also analyse the financial fallout of a cyberattack on Marks & Spencer and a brief data exposure at the People's Postcode Lottery. 🇨🇦🇬🇧</p>

<p>Dive deep into new threat research: two significant npm supply chain campaigns, "PhantomRaven" utilising novel Remote Dynamic Dependencies to bypass static analysis and steal credentials, plus another infostealer campaign using typosquatting and multi-layered obfuscation. Also, Russia-linked cybercriminals are abusing the AdaptixC2 framework for ransomware. 💻🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Urgent vulnerability alerts: Docker users are advised to update due to high-severity path traversal (CVE-2025-62725) in Docker Compose and a patched DLL hijacking flaw (EUVD-2025-36191) in Docker Desktop. CISA and NSA have also released new guidance for hardening Microsoft Exchange servers, with over 29,000 still vulnerable to a critical hybrid flaw (CVE-2025-53786). ⚠️</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on data privacy concerns as advocacy groups urge the FTC to block Meta's AI chatbot data plans, and France's move to the decentralised Matrix network for secure government communications. 🇫🇷🔒</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1grwJ1QN9knJ2VQDcTtc6bpanE2_LUS89" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761857546078</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This episode unpacks the latest in cyber security from the last 24 hours. We dive into significant breaches, including advertising giant Dentsu's U.S. subsidiary, Merkle, exposing staff and client data, and EY's 4TB unencrypted SQL Server backup exposed due to a cloud misconfiguration. Hear about Russian threat actors using living-off-the-land tactics in Ukraine and Cloud Atlas exploiting the old CVE-2017-11882 against Russia's agricultural sector. Plus, hacktivist breaches against Canadian critical infrastructure caused disruptions and unsafe conditions. 🚨</p>

<p>🔍 Discover new threat research, including "AI-targeted cloaking" – a context poisoning attack against agentic web browsers like ChatGPT Atlas. Qualys reports a surge in automated botnet attacks (Mirai, Gafgyt, Mozi) exploiting RCE vulnerabilities in PHPUnit, Laravel, and Spring Cloud Gateway. We also expose the "PhantomRaven" campaign, deploying 126 malicious npm packages to steal authentication tokens and CI/CD secrets, cleverly evading static analysis.</p>

<p>⚠️ On the vulnerability front, a critical, unpatched denial-of-service flaw dubbed "Brash" has been found in Chromium's Blink engine, capable of crashing billions of browsers. We also highlight Germany's alarming 92% of public-facing Exchange servers running out-of-support versions. Stay informed on the UK ICO's £200k fine for spam texts and the AFP's new AI tool to interpret "crimefluencer" slang. Get the essential facts you need to stay ahead!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1mSZH0olaOnnwiTM_Jns9c-DxnHrLAEpp" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761771099944</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 29, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Stay sharp with the latest in cyber security! This episode of stdout dives into critical developments from the last 24 hours. We unpack F5's nation-state attack update and Google's refutation of a massive Gmail breach. 🕵️‍♂️ Discover new threat actor tactics, including SideWinder's ClickOnce attacks on South Asian diplomats, the emergence of the Atroposia malware-as-a-service platform, and BlueNoroff's sophisticated GhostCall and GhostHire campaigns targeting Web3. Plus, we analyse the Qilin ransomware gang's active RaaS operations, now leveraging Windows Subsystem for Linux to bypass traditional defences.</p>

<p>🔒 Get the lowdown on actively exploited vulnerabilities: a critical Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) RCE (CVE-2025-59287) with widespread exploitation, and two Dassault Systèmes DELMIA Apriso flaws (CVE-2025-6205, CVE-2025-6204). We also explore TEE.Fail, a new side-channel attack extracting secrets from Intel, AMD, and NVIDIA TEEs, and the inherent prompt injection vulnerabilities in AI browsers like OpenAI's Atlas, posing significant data exfiltration risks. 🧠</p>

<p>⚖️ Beyond the technical, we discuss "LLM grooming" where popular chatbots cite Russian state-attributed sources, raising disinformation concerns. Hear about the severe human toll of the UK MoD's Afghan relocation scheme data breach and a civil rights lawsuit against the NYPD's Domain Awareness System. Finally, we cover the US declining the UN Cybercrime Convention and Noyb's criminal complaint against Clearview AI in Austria, leveraging GDPR for potential executive imprisonment.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:52:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_n-o5uI46HCSI1HreGTnKk4DBNTNU1dL" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761684745097</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Security Brief** 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks a busy 24 hours in cyber security, analysing 18 articles across seven key topics for technical analysts. We cover a flurry of active cyber events, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Highlights include the highly coordinated cyber theft of Shaquille O'Neal's Range Rover 🚗, the Jingle Thief group's cloud-targeting gift card fraud, and the F5 BIG-IP source code breach now suspected to have begun in late 2023 by Chinese state-sponsored actors. We cover data exposures at Iran's Ravin Academy and Sweden's power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät (claimed by Everest ransomware), plus a mass-exploitation campaign leveraging GutenKit and Hunk Companion plugins for WordPress RCE. Also, a former defence contractor exec faces charges for selling trade secrets to Russia.</p>

<p>Explore the latest in threat research and techniques: the Qilin ransomware group is escalating attacks with Linux variants on Windows, BYOVD exploits, and Veeam targeting. Kaspersky links Memento Labs (Hacking Team successor) to Operation ForumTroll, exploiting a Chrome zero-day (CVE-2025-2783) for "Dante" spyware. We detail Lazarus Group's "Operation Dream Job" targeting European defence, MuddyWater's Phoenix backdoor distribution, and the RedTiger tool's exploitation for data theft. Learn about new XWorm 6.0 features, Microsoft 365 Exchange Online Direct Send abuse, "CoPhish" OAuth token theft via Copilot Studio, and LockBit 5.0's multi-platform resurgence. Advanced phishing evasion techniques, including JavaScript-driven SEG bypasses and QR codes in PDFs, are also on our radar.</p>

<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: a Windows Server Update Service (WSUS) RCE (CVE-2025-59287) is under active exploitation, prompting an emergency patch. We detail "TARmageddon" (CVE-2025-62518) in the async-tar Rust library, allowing RCE and supply chain attacks, and a critical ASP.NET Core security bypass (CVE-2025-55315) in QNAP NetBak PC Agent. OpenAI's Atlas web browser is vulnerable to prompt injection via its omnibox, and multiple unpatched flaws in EfficientLab's WorkExaminer Professional allow unauthenticated administrative access.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1cZXrsnY8wp2tKi7N1dAYRzrdCCMCYfM0" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761598478303</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 26, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>stdout</strong> delivers your daily deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments. Today, we unpack critical vulnerabilities and novel attack techniques impacting AI platforms, alongside significant regulatory discussions on mobile device security.</p>

<p>First, we analyse two potent threats targeting Microsoft Copilot. Discover the "<strong>Sneaky Mermaid</strong>" indirect prompt injection, a clever technique that exploited Mermaid diagram integration and CSS to exfiltrate sensitive tenant data by tricking users into clicking a fake login button. 🧜‍♀️ We also dissect '<strong>CoPhish</strong>', a new OAuth phishing method weaponising legitimate Copilot Studio agents to host malicious chatbots on trusted Microsoft domains, designed to trick users and administrators into granting extensive permissions. Datadog advises strong application consent policies and monitoring Copilot Studio agent creation events to mitigate this threat. 🎣</p>

<p>Then, we shift focus to the UK, where Members of Parliament are urging tech giants like Apple, Google, and Samsung to implement more robust technical measures against a surge in phone thefts. 📱 We examine proposals for cloud-based or IMEI-linked device locks to render stolen handsets useless for resale, and the industry's expressed concerns regarding privacy and security implications. 🔒</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15a4FJDaSGRqSgC5UpUV06eoqVuwbwMMv" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761425411993</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 25, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Get your daily dose of cyber intelligence with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 We unpack the last 24 hours of noteworthy developments for cyber security analysts.

This episode, we're tracking significant active threats: 🚨 A confirmed data breach at Toys R Us Canada exposed customer details. An L3Harris insider threat saw offensive cyber capabilities sold to Russia for $1.3M. Plus, Russia's agricultural agency was hit by a large-scale DDoS attack, disrupting food shipments.

Dive into sophisticated campaigns: 🎣 LastPass users face CryptoChameleon's advanced phishing, attempting to steal passkeys with fake death claims. ESET uncovers Lazarus Group's 'Operation DreamJob' targeting European <b>defence</b> firms with fake offers to deploy the ScoringMathTea RAT. Group-IB details Iranian MuddyWater's breach of 100+ gov/diplomatic entities using weaponised Word attachments and their 'Phoenix' backdoor. Plus, we explore Check Point's 'YouTube Ghost Network' distributing stealer malware, and Palo Alto's Unit 42 linking China-backed 'Smishing Triad' to over 194,000 malicious domains in a global credential theft operation.

On the vulnerability front: 💥 Microsoft has patched a critical WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287) actively exploited in the wild, with PoC code available. We also cover a patched Microsoft 365 Copilot prompt injection flaw, exploitable via Mermaid diagrams to exfiltrate tenant data. Pwn2Own Ireland 2025 saw over $1M awarded for 73 zero-days across various devices, highlighting ongoing risks. Plus, an HP OneAgent update issue disrupted Microsoft Entra ID authentication for Windows 11 AI PCs.

Finally, we examine the increasing focus of nation-state actors on exploiting forgotten perimeter devices, new Mozilla requirements for Firefox extension data disclosure, and the International Counter Ransomware Initiative's guidance on software supply chain resilience. Stay informed, stay secure!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1xFGCa3PIyGFeBBG47Xu8BF4Z9vefyVIi" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761339111792</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 24, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Intel: 24-Hour Cyber Snapshot</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats impacting organisations globally. SpaceX has disabled 2,500 Starlink terminals in Myanmar powering scam compounds, while US municipalities grapple with service disruptions. State-sponsored MuddyWater deployed Phoenix backdoor v4 against MENA governments, and North Korea's Lazarus Group executed "Operation DreamJob" targeting European defence firms with trojanised apps.</p>

<p>We unpack new techniques from "Jingle Thief" exploiting cloud environments for gift card fraud and "Smishing Triad's" massive Chinese-managed operation impersonating USPS and toll agencies. Google and Check Point also dismantled the "YouTube Ghost Network" distributing password-stealing malware via fake tutorials.</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities are under active exploitation: over 250 Magento stores were hit by <b>CVE-2025-54236 (SessionReaper)</b> allowing account takeover and RCE, and <b>CVE-2025-61932</b> in Motex Lanscope Endpoint Manager, enabling unauthenticated RCE, has been added to CISA's KEV catalogue. Plus, watch out for "AI Sidebar Spoofing" attacks on OpenAI Atlas and Perplexity Comet browsers. Microsoft has also disabled File Explorer's preview pane to block NTLM hash theft.</p>

<p>Stay informed on regulatory delays in the UK, updated third-party risk guidance from NYDFS (including AI provisions), and the growing adoption of managed identities to bolster security postures. Essential insights for every Cyber Security Analyst. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1z-kiKjVrh0EfHZIn0LdV2aqWhRJoL2kR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761252753546</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 23, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security! 🚨 We're tracking the £1.9 billion impact of the Jaguar Land Rover breach and active exploitation of the Microsoft SharePoint ToolShell zero-day (CVE-2025-53770) by Chinese-linked actors. Unpack the "PhantomCaptcha" spearphishing campaign targeting Ukrainian organisations with weaponised PDFs and WebSocket RATs. 🎣</p>
<p>New threats include the sophisticated PassiveNeuron APT using custom malware and the upgraded Vidar Stealer 2.0, now rewritten in C with advanced anti-analysis. 🕵️‍♂️</p>
<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: TP-Link Omada gateways patched for unauthenticated RCEs (CVE-2025-6542), and Adobe Commerce faces active exploitation of SessionReaper (CVE-2025-54236). We also cover the "TARmageddon" logic flaw (CVE-2025-62518) in Rust's `async-tar` library and the massive 56 zero-day haul at Pwn2Own Ireland. 💥</p>
<p>Plus, GCHQ warns of the UK's "contested and complex" threat environment, highlighting a quadrupling of significant cyberattacks. Get the essential intel you need, daily. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:52:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1kAnBqDOpJr6sbFouKxzMrQUHZonsp9U4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761166351166</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Stay sharp with stdout's daily deep dive into the latest cyber threats! 🚨 We're tracking **active exploitation** of critical vulnerabilities, including a high-severity Microsoft Windows SMB client flaw (CVE-2025-33073) and an Oracle E-Business Suite SSRF (CVE-2025-61884). Discover "TARmageddon" (CVE-2025-62518), a critical RCE in the unmaintained `async-tar` Rust library, posing systemic risk to numerous forks like `tokio-tar` and `uv`. Plus, get the highlights from Pwn2Own Ireland 2025, where researchers chained 34 zero-days to compromise QNAP and Synology devices, and learn about the concerning n-day vulnerabilities exposing 1.8 million developers using AI-powered Cursor and Windsurf IDEs.

In threat actor intelligence, Google reports Russian state-backed COLDRIVER (Star Blizzard) has rapidly evolved its malware arsenal, deploying NOROBOT, YESROBOT, and MAYBEROBOT via "ClickFix" social engineering attacks. 🕵️‍♂️ We also analyse how China-nexus group Salt Typhoon breached a European telecommunications organisation, exploiting Citrix NetScaler Gateway and deploying Snappybee malware via DLL side-loading through legitimate antivirus software.

Beyond the front lines, Veeam has acquired Securiti AI for $1.725 billion, marking a significant entry into the AI security market, while Dataminr plans to acquire ThreatConnect for $290 million to enhance real-time threat intelligence. 💼 On the regulatory front, Russia has ordered Apple to make local search engines default on iPhones, and the U.S. Senate advanced a bill to combat foreign robocalls. Finally, the non-profit DNS0.EU service has announced its immediate shutdown due to sustainability issues. 📉]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1jI5Q6lIs-Iz4iTSIJJcCgPrwQc-babOx" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761079894179</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. We're tracking critical active events, novel attack techniques, and newly exploited vulnerabilities.</p>

<p><b>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</b> China accuses the US NSA of a multi-stage cyberattack on its National Time Service Centre, exploiting SMS flaws and deploying 42 tools. F5 confirms a nation-state breach by China-nexus group UNC5221, stealing BIG-IP source code and maintaining 12 months of access. Operation Zero Disco exploits a Cisco IOS SNMP stack overflow (CVE-2025-20352) to deploy Linux rootkits, while Flax Typhoon (Ethereal Panda) compromised an ArcGIS system for over a year. Japanese retailer Askul halted operations due to ransomware, impacting major retailers, and Verisure's Swedish subsidiary, Alert Alarm, suffered a data breach exposing 35,000 customer records.</p>

<p><b>New Threat Research & Techniques:</b> North Korean actors UNC5342 are using EtherHiding to conceal JADESNOW and InvisibleFerret malware within Binance Smart Chain smart contracts, distributed via job scams. A new GNU/Linux rootkit, LinkPro, was found in an AWS compromise, leveraging eBPF for stealth. Android devices face Pixnapping (CVE-2025-48561), a side-channel attack to steal 2FA codes and Google Maps timelines. We also cover SEO poisoning leading to fake Ivanti Pulse Secure VPN sites, Qilin ransomware's ties to bulletproof hosting, widespread Microsoft-branded phishing, and multi-country smishing campaigns targeting taxpayers and drivers. macOS users are targeted by social engineering via fake Homebrew/TradingView sites deploying stealer malware, alongside phishing impersonating 1Password and LastPass breach notifications. Plus, a deep dive into SocGholish (FakeUpdates) and a coordinated campaign of 131 WhatsApp Web automation tool clones for large-scale spamming.</p>

<p><b>Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b> CISA has added five critical flaws to its KEV Catalogue, confirming active exploitation. This includes CVE-2025-33073, a Windows SMB privilege escalation allowing SYSTEM privileges, and CVE-2025-61884, a server-side request forgery in Oracle E-Business Suite. Also, authentication bypasses in Kentico Xperience CMS (CVE-2025-2746, CVE-2025-2747) and an Apple JavaScriptCore RCE (CVE-2022-48503). Urgent patching is advised for nearly 76,000 publicly exposed WatchGuard Firebox appliances vulnerable to CVE-2025-9242, a critical 9.3 CVSS remote code execution flaw exploitable without authentication. CERT/CC also disclosed CVE-2025-8036, a CORS header vulnerability combined with DNS rebinding that can lead to data exfiltration.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:54:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1uUxmDAcFQL9_9fORh7iw3gAPP501mw2Z" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760993655430</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security, featuring:</p>
<ul>
    <li>🚨 <strong>Operation SIMCARTEL Disrupted:</strong> Europol spearheaded a major takedown of a sophisticated cybercrime-as-a-service platform. Authorities seized 1,200 SIM box devices and dismantled infrastructure that facilitated over 49 million fake accounts for widespread fraud, phishing, and more.</li>
    <li>📱 <strong>TikTok ClickFix Attacks & Aura Stealer:</strong> New threat research exposes cybercriminals leveraging TikTok videos to spread the Aura Stealer. Disguised as software activation guides, these attacks trick users into executing PowerShell commands, compromising browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and other sensitive data.</li>
    <li>⚖️ <strong>Experian Netherlands Fined €2.7M for GDPR Breaches:</strong> A significant regulatory action sees Experian Netherlands penalised for illegally collecting and utilising personal data from various sources to generate credit scores without consent, leading to their exit from the country.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1hqUEaFjJ7D2farNmlK-hOtfh1GVKPrZY" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760907011444</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 18, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily: Your 24-Hour Cyber Briefing!</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber developments impacting analysts. Today, we unpack significant breaches including the <b>Prosper</b> incident affecting 17.6 million victims with sensitive PII, and the <b>Dairy Farmers of America</b> ransomware attack by the Play gang, exposing SSNs and bank details via sophisticated social engineering. Europol's "SIMCARTEL" operation dismantled a network responsible for $5.8 million in fraud, while <b>Envoy Air</b> confirmed a Clop extortion linked to a new Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882). Plus, suspected Iranian hackers reportedly accessed John Bolton's email.</p>

<p>Threat intelligence reveals North Korean operatives (Famous Chollima, UNC5342) deploying evasive techniques with new malware like BeaverTail and EtherHiding, the latter using public blockchains for C2. Microsoft has revoked over 200 fraudulent certificates used by Vanilla Tempest in Rhysida ransomware campaigns. On the vulnerability front, a critical out-of-bounds write in <b>WatchGuard Fireware OS</b> (CVE-2025-9242) allows unauthenticated RCE on IKEv2 VPNs. Over 266,000 <b>F5 BIG-IP</b> instances remain exposed post-breach, prompting CISA directives. Microsoft patched a high-severity HTTP request smuggling bug in <b>Kestrel ASP.NET Core</b> (CVE-2025-55315), and <b>ConnectWise Automate RMM</b> addressed critical flaws (CVE-2025-11492, CVE-2025-11493) enabling MITM and malicious updates.</p>

<p>We also look at the expanding attack surface from autonomous AI agents lacking identity security governance, as highlighted by SailPoint. Finally, legal battles unfold as US labor unions sue the Trump administration over a social media surveillance program, and the Computer & Communications Industry Association (CCIA) challenges Texas's new App Store Accountability Act, citing First Amendment and privacy concerns.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1bWXxv-sQScMVedO68tJ0an3Hn0uP8mlx" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760734333893</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout delivers the critical cybersecurity developments from the last 24 hours, tailored for cyber security analysts.

Catch up on major data breaches impacting Sotheby's and Prosper, exposing millions of sensitive records. 💸 We also detail Capita's £14 million fine for a Black Basta ransomware incident affecting 6.6 million, and Microsoft's disruption of Rhysida attacks using malvertising and fake Teams installers.

Explore cutting-edge threat techniques, including North Korea's UNC5342 group deploying 'EtherHiding' – crypto-stealing malware embedded in blockchain smart contracts for takedown resilience. ⛓️ We also examine China's 'Jewelbug' APT breaching a Russian IT provider in a rare East-on-East espionage operation, targeting potential software supply chain attacks.

Get the lowdown on actively exploited vulnerabilities: Cisco firewall flaws tied to the Chinese-backed ArcaneDoor campaign, a maximum-severity Adobe Experience Manager RCE (CVE-2025-54253) now in CISA's KEV, and a zero-day in Gladinet CentreStack (CVE-2025-11371) enabling RCE. 🚨 Also, learn about a high-severity request smuggling bug in ASP.NET Core Kestrel and the exploitation of Cisco IOS/IOS XE SNMP (CVE-2025-20352) to deploy a Linux rootkit in 'Operation Zero Disco'.

Beyond the technical exploits, we delve into broader threat landscape discussions: a proposed 'Secure Hosting Alliance Trust Seal' for web-hosting, Microsoft's report on a 32% surge in identity-based attacks, and a critical assessment of CVE/CVSS scoring systems. 📈 Plus, regulatory news covers a 19-year-old's sentencing for the PowerSchool hack, with $14.1 million in restitution ordered, and Cambodia's repatriation of South Korean nationals rescued from scam compounds. ⚖️]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:51:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1vp5wncC2ppGyMfMI670DN--ggYvPcj8B" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760647915086</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Unpacking a sophisticated <b>nation-state cyberattack on F5's BIG-IP</b> product development environment, which led to source code exfiltration and CISA's emergency directive ED 26-01. Patches have been released for 44 vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Stay alert to <b>active exploitation</b> of a critical unauthenticated RCE (CVE-2025-2611, CVSS 9.3) in <b>ICTBroadcast autodialer software</b>. We also cover the UK ICO's hefty £14M fine against <b>Capita</b> for its 2023 breach, exposing 6.6 million records, and a new <b>phishing campaign targeting LastPass and Bitwarden users</b> with fake breach alerts to deploy remote access tools.</p>

<p>⚙️ Our research segment highlights new threats: malicious <b>VSCode extensions</b> from "TigerJack" stealing source code and executing RCE, plus over 550 leaked secrets found in other extensions. Discover how Chinese state-linked actor "<b>Jewelbug</b>" conducted espionage against a Russian IT provider, and why <b>synced passkeys</b> pose a significant enterprise security risk due to cloud account recovery flaws.</p>

<p>🔒 Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities: two CVSS 10.0 RCE flaws in <b>Red Lion Sixnet RTUs</b> impacting industrial control systems, SAP's patches including a critical NetWeaver AS Java deserialization RCE (CVE-2025-42944, CVSS 10.0), and Senator Cassidy's call for more details on severe <b>Cisco ASA vulnerabilities</b> that reportedly breached a federal agency.</p>

<p>⚖️ Plus, New York state fined eight car insurance companies $14.2M for data breaches affecting over 825,000 individuals, and a 19-year-old was sentenced for the <b>PowerSchool hack</b> exposing 70 million student and teacher records. We also touch on concerns regarding <b>CISA's workforce reductions</b> and the termination of its MS-ISAC agreement.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=10K_79ORPkNEPaPRBBMWm-9JhzzroQW_E" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760561564863</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 15, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>⚡️ <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> ⚡️</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of critical infosec developments. We're tracking active cyber events, new attack techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities impacting organisations globally. This episode covers significant breaches at <b>Asahi</b> and <b>Qantas</b>, plus Michigan City's ransomware woes. Don't miss the US/UK's coordinated sanctions and Bitcoin seizure targeting Cambodia's Prince Group, indicted for "pig butchering" scams and human trafficking. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>🔬 Our threat research deep dive reveals Chinese state-backed <b>Flax Typhoon's</b> year-long persistence on ArcGIS servers via weaponised SOEs and covert C2. We also unpack malicious packages across npm, PyPI, and RubyGems using Discord webhooks for data exfiltration, alongside North Korean "Contagious Interview" campaigns targeting Web3 developers with over 300 malicious npm packages. 🕵️‍♀️</p>

<p>🚨 Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities, including Microsoft's October 2025 Patch Tuesday with <b>six zero-days</b> – two actively exploited in Windows Agere Modem Driver (CVE-2025-24990) and Remote Access Connection Manager (CVE-2025-59230), both added to CISA's KEV catalog. Oracle issued an emergency patch for an actively exploited pre-auth SSRF in E-Business Suite (CVE-2025-61884), publicly leaked by ShinyHunters. Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT (CVE-2025-10035) is also under active exploitation by Storm-1175 for ransomware campaigns. 💥</p>

<p>We also cover Microsoft Edge's IE mode restrictions due to unpatched Chakra JavaScript engine zero-days, AMD's "RMPocalypse" fix (CVE-2025-0033) for critical EPYC processor flaws, and the Android "Pixnapping" side-channel attack (CVE-2025-48561) stealing sensitive data. Plus, a concerning UEFI shell 'memory modify' command found in 200,000 Linux Framework systems, enabling Secure Boot bypass. 💻</p>

<p>🌍 In broader threat landscape news, the UK's NCSC reports a record surge in "nationally significant" cyberattacks, while Taiwan faces a 17% increase in daily Chinese cyber intrusions targeting critical infrastructure, combined with information warfare. Florida's AG is suing Roku over alleged collection and sale of children's sensitive data. ⚖️</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on the evolving threat landscape driven by AI-generated malware, the need for Continuous Threat Exposure Management, Mozilla's new built-in Firefox VPN beta, and a public dispute between FuzzingLabs and Gecko Security over CVE credit attribution. Stay informed, stay secure! 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:53:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1c4YwdtfpKv_8HJ6NPtBX3yRYedO91OFP" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760475205941</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 14, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>'s daily intel! 🚀 This episode unpacks critical active threats: over 100 SonicWall SSLVPN accounts compromised via stolen credentials. The Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters group has leaked data from 6 million Qantas and 7.3 million Vietnam Airlines customers, alongside Gap and Fujifilm. 🏥 Medusa ransomware is behind a breach impacting 1.2 million SimonMed Imaging patients, and Clop ransomware exploited an Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) in a Harvard University incident.</p>

<p>Discover emerging TTPs and critical vulnerabilities. 🤖 We analyse ChaosBot, a new Rust-based backdoor leveraging Discord for C2, alongside a destructive Chaos-C++ ransomware variant. The Astaroth banking trojan now employs GitHub steganography for C2 resilience. 🚨 On the vulnerability front, Microsoft has restricted IE Mode in Edge due to active exploitation of unpatched IE Chakra JavaScript engine zero-days. Oracle released an emergency patch for CVE-2025-61884, an unauthenticated info disclosure flaw in E-Business Suite, following active exploitation of CVE-2025-61882 by Clop.</p>

<p>Beyond the headlines, we examine the expanding RondoDox botnet, weaponising over 50 vulnerabilities with an 'exploit shotgun' approach, and a 100,000+ IP botnet actively targeting RDP services in the US. ⚖️ Regulatory updates include Ofcom's first fine under the UK Online Safety Act and an Austrian DPA ruling against Microsoft 365 Education's data tracking. Plus, the Dutch government's intervention in Nexperia and Ukraine's steps towards a dedicated military Cyber Force.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15p1aG71MRKMvcm-yzyIEMXZpftacFtT7" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760388733482</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 13, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your 24-Hour Cyber Brief</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Get the essential intel for cyber security analysts. Today, we're dissecting critical vulnerabilities and active threat campaigns from the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>First, a deep dive into Oracle's E-Business Suite. Oracle has issued an urgent alert for <b>CVE-2025-61884</b> (CVSS 7.5), a high-severity flaw allowing unauthenticated, remote HTTP access to compromise Oracle Configurator. This vulnerability grants attackers unauthorised access to critical data across versions 12.2.3 through 12.2.14. We also revisit the recently exploited zero-day, <b>CVE-2025-61882</b>, leveraged by Cl0p-linked threat actors to deploy malware families including GOLDVEIN.JAVA, SAGEGIFT, SAGELEAF, and SAGEWAVE.</p>

<p>Next, we pivot to a pervasive smishing campaign targeting New Yorkers. Fraudulent text messages impersonating the Department of Taxation and Finance are luring recipients with fake "Inflation Refunds" to steal sensitive personal and financial data for identity theft and fraud. Official warnings confirm New York State's actual refund initiative is automatic, with agencies explicitly stating they will not contact taxpayers via text, phone, or email for these refunds.</p>

<p>Tune in for a concise summary of active cyber events, new techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Vbh_E3C3rViyCm6k0kbbk7YBa2qct6hs" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760302191000</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 12, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Get the daily rundown on critical cyber security developments! Today, we're dissecting a widespread compromise impacting **SonicWall SSL VPN devices**, where threat actors are rapidly authenticating into over 100 accounts, potentially leveraging valid credentials and exploiting known flaws, including **CVE-2024-40766**, linked to Akira ransomware campaigns. We'll cover crucial mitigation advice for organisations.</p>

<p>🛠️ Next, we delve into new threat research revealing threat actors weaponising the open-source DFIR tool **Velociraptor** in ransomware attacks. The group Storm-2603 exploits **SharePoint vulnerabilities** for initial access, deploying an outdated Velociraptor version susceptible to **CVE-2025-6264** for privilege escalation and endpoint takeover. We detail their lateral movement tactics, including GPO modifications and disabling real-time protection.</p>

<p>⚖️ We also cover the legal fallout from the **PowerSchool breach**, where a 19-year-old faces a seven-year prison term for accessing 60 million student and 9 million teacher records and demanding a 30 Bitcoin ransom. Plus, significant leadership changes within **US Cyber Command and the NSA**, as President Trump opts not to nominate Army Lt. Gen. William Hartman.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 20:50:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1k8CGshTVQilWhXPGyKb7fshVOxmyxEwA" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760215848185</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 11, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing** 🚨</p>
<p>Your daily dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments! Unpacking critical incidents, we detail the Cl0p ransomware group's exploitation of an Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882), compromising dozens of organisations for RCE and data exfiltration. Explore the FBI and French authorities' takedown of BreachForums, operated by ShinyHunters and Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters, just before a threatened Salesforce data leak. Plus, we cover the significant data breach at UK trade union Prospect, exposing sensitive member data, and Microsoft's warning about the "payroll pirate" Storm-2657 group targeting US university payroll systems with sophisticated AiTM phishing.</p>

<p>🔬 **New Threats & Techniques:** Discover ClayRat, a new Android spyware mimicking popular apps and propagating via SMS, capable of extensive data theft and remote control. We also expose the "Beamglea" credential phishing campaign, leveraging 175 malicious npm packages as redirect infrastructure to harvest Microsoft credentials.</p>

<p>🍎 **Vulnerabilities & Updates:** Apple has dramatically expanded its bug bounty programme, now offering up to $2 million for zero-click RCEs. Stay informed on Windows 11 23H2 Home and Pro editions reaching end of servicing on November 11, 2025. We also touch on Google Chrome's new feature to automatically revoke notification permissions for inactive websites, the halted trial of officers accused of Baltic Sea cable damage, and the amusing tale of pro-Russian hacktivists TwoNet falling for a Forescout honeypot.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:52:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A77AethkFcSdI4zkJyR88eYJKh61JXmG" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760129539362</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 10, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential 24-hour cyber security update! 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks critical active threats and exploited vulnerabilities. We dive into the widespread <b>SonicWall cloud backup breach</b>, confirming all customers had firewall configuration files accessed via brute-force. Plus, <b>Discord clarifies its third-party incident</b>, revealing 70,000 government IDs exposed through a compromised Zendesk agent. 🛡️</p>

<p>Catch up on the relentless <b>Clop ransomware group</b>, actively exploiting a zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle E-Business Suite, chaining multiple vulnerabilities for pre-authenticated RCE. Discover how "Payroll Pirates" (Storm-2657) are targeting US universities and other organisations, using phishing to divert salaries via compromised HR platforms. We also explore Russian hackers' increasing use of <b>AI in cyberattacks</b> against Ukraine, from phishing to advanced malware like WRECKSTEEL. 💸</p>

<p>Further analysis covers the new <b>RondoDox botnet's "exploit shotgun" approach</b> against 56 n-day vulnerabilities, and how China-based Storm-2603 is weaponising the Velociraptor DFIR tool in LockBit and Babuk ransomware attacks. Understand why <b>token theft is a primary cause of SaaS breaches</b>, often bypassing MFA, and the evolving threat from pro-Russian hacktivist group TwoNet, now targeting critical infrastructure with old XSS exploits. Finally, a critical authentication bypass (CVE-2025-5947) in the <b>Service Finder WordPress theme</b> is under active exploitation, granting unauthenticated admin access. 💥</p>

<p>Stay informed on the proposed PACT Act, aiming to extend vital cyber threat information sharing protections. Get the facts, fast. 🚀</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:52:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ERPUDjBSc0vBGgDTRhisSPQZABqFrzZM" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760043175852</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 9, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Salesforce refused a ransom from "Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters" for data stolen via social engineering and compromised OAuth tokens. Qilin ransomware hit Japanese giant Asahi, while UK police arrested suspects over the Kido nursery doxing. A US law firm reported a China-linked zero-day breach targeting attorney emails for national security intelligence.</p>
<p>🔬 New threat research highlights OpenAI disrupting Russian, North Korean, and Chinese actors misusing ChatGPT for malware and phishing. Ukraine's CERT-UA details Russian AI-driven attacks and "Steal & Go" tactics, including exploitation of Roundcube's CVE-2023-43770. China-linked actors used Nezha, Ghost RAT, and AntSword in politically motivated espionage across Asia, and the "Crimson Collective" targeted AWS cloud environments for data theft and extortion. A new FileFix variant employs cache smuggling to deliver malicious ZIPs.</p>
<p>💥 Critical vulnerabilities in focus include a severe command injection (CVE-2025-53967) in <code>figma-developer-mcp</code> allowing RCE, now patched. Active exploitation of CVE-2025-5947, a critical authentication bypass in the Service Finder WordPress theme, enabled unauthenticated admin logins with over 13,800 attempts recorded.</p>
<p>🌐 Broader developments cover Ursula Von der Leyen's warning on Russia's "hybrid warfare" against Europe, Germany's opposition to the EU's "Chat Control" legislation, and Docker's new unlimited access to Hardened Images for startups and SMBs, offering secure software bundles with near-zero CVEs.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ly46MAmDPC0Aa2H8f93hT5L9wcVbFA9a" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759956732462</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 8, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Catch up on the latest cyber incidents impacting global giants and sensitive data. 🚨 **Jaguar Land Rover** faces a "cyber shockwave" post-attack, while **Doctors Imaging Group** discloses a year-late breach affecting 171,000+ patients. **Discord** users' sensitive info was exposed via a third-party, and **Avnet** confirms a data breach with claims of 1.3TB exfiltrated. The **Red Hat** breach escalates with ShinyHunters joining extortion efforts, leaking customer network details. Plus, **DraftKings** battles credential stuffing attacks.

On the vulnerability front, the notorious **Clop ransomware group** has been actively exploiting a critical zero-day, `CVE-2025-61882`, in **Oracle E-Business Suite** since August 2025. 💥 This RCE flaw (CVSS 9.8) allowed unauthenticated attackers to gain control, leading to massive data theft and reported $50M extortion demands. Oracle has patched, and CISA has added it to their Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue.

New threat research reveals the evolution of **XWorm malware** to version 6.0, now packed with 35+ plugins for extensive data theft and ransomware capabilities. 🐛 Meanwhile, **North Korean hackers (Lazarus Group)** set a new record, stealing over $2 billion in cryptocurrency in 2025, primarily funding nuclear weapons development and shifting tactics from DeFi exploits to social engineering.

The impact of AI on cybersecurity is rapidly expanding. 🤖 A LayerX report highlights **AI tools as the leading uncontrolled channel for corporate data exfiltration**, with 77% of employees copy-pasting sensitive data into unmanaged GenAI accounts. OpenAI's latest report confirms threat actors are leveraging AI to *enhance existing hacking methods* – from malware development to spearphishing – rather than creating entirely new ones.

In regulatory news, **Russia implements a mandatory 24-hour mobile internet blackout** for foreign SIM cards upon entry, citing national security. 🇷🇺 On a brighter note, **Google launches a dedicated AI Vulnerability Reward Program**, offering up to $30,000 for critical flaws in its AI systems. However, Google has controversially stated it will *not* fix **ASCII smuggling attacks in Gemini**, dismissing the LLM manipulation as a social engineering issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1el9x9qtjTd7DawPVY7rtIiyzva7kXRiG" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759870311700</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 7, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Exploits & Breaches Unpacked:</b> Dive into the latest active cyber events, including Clop ransomware's exploitation of a new Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) for unauthenticated RCE, with public exploit code now available. We also cover Medusa ransomware (Storm-1175) leveraging a Fortra GoAnywhere MFT deserialisation flaw (CVE-2025-10035), and a Zimbra Collaboration zero-day (CVE-2025-27915) used against the Brazilian military. Immediate patching is crucial as agencies worldwide issue urgent warnings. 🛡️</p>

<p>💥 <b>Major Incidents & Campaigns:</b> Get the lowdown on the Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' crowdsourced extortion scheme and their OAuth token abuse impacting Zscaler. We analyse Discord's data breach via a compromised third-party vendor, the significant production halt at Jaguar Land Rover due to a cyberattack, and a suspected China-linked cyber-espionage campaign targeting European institutions. Plus, a leaked report suggests FEMA's CISO and CIO were fired following a June breach. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>🔬 <b>New Threats & Vulnerabilities:</b> Explore the resurgence of the XWorm backdoor, now featuring a ransomware module and extensive plugins. We detail "RediShell" (CVE-2025-49844), a 13-year-old use-after-free vulnerability in Redis allowing authenticated RCE, and a critical flaw (CVE-2025-59489) in the Unity game engine affecting multiple platforms. Also, a significant surge in scanning attacks targeting Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect portals has been observed. 💻</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Industry & Regulatory Watch:</b> Stay informed on the European Commission's controversial "Chat Control" proposals, with Signal threatening to exit the EU market if passed. LinkedIn is suing ProAPIs Inc. for alleged data scraping, while House Democrats question DHS over an ICE contract with Israeli spyware company Paragon Solutions. We also cover Georgia Tech's $875K settlement for cybersecurity failures, Wiz's $4.5M "Zeroday Cloud" hacking competition, and China's severe crackdown on cybercrime. ⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:52:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1sHSH-3U5dSbN_UYv88PRhQKRXoVboCdR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759783957431</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 6, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Security Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Stay ahead of the curve with today's critical cyber developments. We're diving deep into an actively exploited zero-day vulnerability, <b>CVE-2025-27915</b>, impacting Zimbra Collaboration Suite versions 9.0, 10.0, and 10.1. Discover how malicious iCalendar files 🗓️ delivered sophisticated JavaScript payloads to steal credentials, emails, and sensitive data from a Brazilian military organisation, leveraging the Zimbra SOAP API for exfiltration and mail forwarding. Learn about the TTPs linked to UNC1151 and the urgent patches released on January 27th. ✅</p>
<p>Then, we'll unpack the resolution of ParkMobile's 2021 data breach class action lawsuit. Understand the $32.8 million settlement, the $1 in-app credit compensation for 22 million affected users, and the extensive data types exposed. Plus, get the latest on ParkMobile's current warnings regarding ongoing SMS phishing (smishing) attacks 📱 targeting their customer base. Stay informed, stay secure. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:50:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=17f9SvRYx3J2qNRoqUPvKdkNXZ6rH8ilp" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759697405674</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 5, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>stdout: Daily InfoSec Briefing</h3>

Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 Your daily deep dive into the latest in cybersecurity.

This episode unpacks a significant <b>Discord data breach</b> affecting PII, government IDs, and partial billing information, stemming from a compromised third-party provider. Understand the financial motivations and the critical implications for identity theft and crypto scams. 🕵️‍♂️

Next, we dissect "<b>CometJacking</b>," a novel prompt injection technique targeting Perplexity's agentic AI browser, Comet. Discover how malicious URLs can siphon sensitive data from connected services like email and calendar, bypassing traditional protections through trivial Base64 encoding. Learn why researchers are flagging new AI-native security risks, despite vendor claims of "no security impact." 🤖

Finally, we examine a nearly 500% surge in scanning activity targeting <b>Palo Alto Networks login portals</b>. GreyNoise reports this mirrors pre-CVE disclosure patterns seen with recent Cisco ASA zero-days, urging organisations to ensure their software is running the latest versions. Don't get caught out! 🚨]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:50:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1oyvQ0L4wZvzmB34psxKxAqRkYRP0Pqj1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759611003220</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 4, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>🚨 Cyber Alert: stdout Daily Briefing 🚨</h3>
<p>Tracking significant active threats and breaches impacting global organisations over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The notorious <b>ShinyHunters</b> group, also known as "Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters," has launched a data leak site, claiming 1 billion records from 39 companies (including FedEx and Google) via Salesforce breaches, demanding a ransom. Meanwhile, a group linked to <b>Clop ransomware</b> is extorting Oracle E-Business Suite customers, exploiting critical RCE flaws and bypassing SSO/MFA. <b>Red Hat</b> confirms a breach of its consulting GitLab by "Crimson Collective," exposing architectural diagrams and authentication tokens. Japanese giant <b>Asahi Group Holdings</b> suffered a ransomware attack, and <b>Renault/Dacia UK</b> customers were impacted by a third-party data breach. The US Courts also detail ongoing upgrades following a major breach.</p>
<p>Uncover new threat intelligence: Meet <b>"Cavalry Werewolf,"</b> a new actor targeting Russian sectors with FoalShell and StallionRAT via phishing. The <b>Rhadamanthys info stealer</b> evolves with advanced fingerprinting and steganography for payload concealment. Researchers expose <b>"CommetJacking,"</b> a prompt-injection attack on Perplexity's Comet AI browser that exfiltrates sensitive data. Plus, insights into "PRISONBREAK," an Israeli-backed network using AI deepfakes for propaganda in Iran.</p>
<p>Stay informed on critical vulnerabilities, privacy shifts, and security innovations. Oracle urges patching for E-Business Suite RCEs, while Perplexity downplays its AI browser prompt injection. We also cover privacy concerns around <b>Flock Safety's "Raven"</b> gunshot detection, the UK's proposed digital ID, and the US Courts' response to their major breach. Finally, explore <b>Signal's new SPQR</b> for quantum resistance and <b>Google Workspace's end-to-end encryption</b> rollout for enterprise users.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:52:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1bSRLJTZ1WJwWaTHq3OpGSoxBK4lv82-g" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759528359247</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 3, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Intel Briefing** 🚨</p>

<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments. We unpack major active events, including the alleged <b>Crimson Collective breach of Red Hat's GitHub</b>, impacting customer IT blueprints and authentication tokens. Hear about the suspected ransomware attack disrupting <b>Asahi Group Holdings'</b> operations in Japan, and the social engineering incident that froze <b>Kodex Global's</b> domain. Plus, we cover the high-volume email extortion campaign targeting <b>Oracle E-Business Suite</b> customers by Clop-linked actors, and significant data breaches at <b>Allianz Life Insurance</b> (linked to Scattered Spider) and <b>Motility</b> (Pear ransomware).</p>

<p>🔎 On the vulnerability front, get the lowdown on <b>DrayTek's critical RCE flaw (CVE-2025-10547)</b> affecting Vigor routers, allowing unauthenticated remote code execution. ESET reveals two new Android spyware campaigns, <b>ProSpy and ToSpy</b>, actively targeting UAE users via fake messaging apps. We also highlight a massive <b>540% surge in AI vulnerabilities</b>, particularly prompt injection, reported by HackerOne.</p>

<p>🌍 Beyond the exploits, we examine the expanding global reach of <b>North Korean IT worker schemes</b>, now targeting diverse industries. Stay informed on regulatory shifts as a Dutch court rules against <b>Meta's profiled feeds</b> under the EU Digital Services Act, and EU Parliament members question the funding of commercial spyware. Finally, we cover <b>Georgia Tech's $875K settlement</b> for lax cybersecurity on federal research projects and Microsoft's move to discontinue inline SVG images in Outlook for enhanced security. </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:36:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1FYyGbRqK2MWgjrbEEcJcSg0zIZMMeWi6" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469803523</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 2, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! We're tracking significant breaches affecting millions, including <b>WestJet</b>, <b>Allianz Life</b>, and <b>Motility Software Solutions</b>, alongside a potential <b>US Air Force</b> SharePoint incident. Plus, discover how threat actors are exploiting <b>Milesight industrial routers</b> for phishing campaigns across Europe. 🚨</p>

<p>Unpack new, sophisticated threats: meet <b>Phantom Taurus</b>, a China-linked espionage group using the stealthy NET-STAR malware, and dissect new Android banking Trojans like <b>Klopatra</b> and <b>Datzbro</b> targeting seniors. We also cover North Korean IT workers expanding their fraudulent job applications and the <b>CABINETRAT</b> backdoor used in targeted attacks in Ukraine. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities, including a <b>Red Hat OpenShift AI</b> flaw (CVSS 9.9) allowing full cluster admin escalation, and the "WireTap" physical attack bypassing <b>Intel SGX</b> security. Our analysis also highlights the rise of Living Off the Land techniques in high-severity attacks and the ongoing pressure on security professionals to keep breaches confidential. 💥</p>

<p>Finally, we examine data privacy concerns with <b>Tile Bluetooth trackers</b> leaking identifying data and an <b>Adobe Analytics</b> bug exposing customer tracking. Stay informed on regulatory shifts like Google's upcoming Android developer ID verification impacting F-Droid, Imgur's UK exit, and the White House's push for quantum-resistant encryption. Plus, Google Drive rolls out new AI-powered ransomware detection. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:29:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=14eQPkiL_-Or3h_2cyAIJo_qgVG5lxIfJ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469375144</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 1, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Debrief!</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with <b>stdout</b>. We're unpacking critical vulnerabilities under active exploitation, major breaches, and evolving threat tradecraft.</p>

<p>This episode, we analyse critical vulnerabilities under active exploitation: widespread attacks on <b>Cisco ASA/FTD</b> (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362) deploying 'Line Viper' and 'RayInitiator' bootkits, and urgent CISA directives for patching critical flaws in <b>Fortra GoAnywhere MFT</b> (CVE-2025-10035) and <b>Sudo</b> (CVE-2025-32463) for privilege escalation. We also cover a <b>VMware zero-day</b> (CVE-2025-41244) actively exploited by Chinese state-sponsored UNC5174, alongside other critical VMware patches and CISA KEV additions. 🛠️</p>

<p>In breach news, UK authorities secure a landmark conviction in a <b>£5.5 billion Bitcoin fraud</b>, <b>WestJet</b> confirms a customer data breach, and <b>Asahi</b> reports system disruptions. INTERPOL's "Contender 3.0" operation nets 260 arrests targeting romance scams and sextortion. 💰</p>

<p>Explore new threat tradecraft with the <b>MatrixPDF toolkit</b> creating interactive phishing lures, and uncover North Korea's expanding illicit IT worker scheme. We also dissect the "Gemini Trifecta" – three high-severity vulnerabilities in <b>Google's Gemini AI</b>. 🤖</p>

<p>Plus, we cover the EU's <b>Cyber Resilience Act</b> clarifications, CISA's funding cuts to the Center for Internet Security, and the impending expiration of key US cybersecurity legislation. Data privacy takes centre stage with FTC action against the <b>Sendit app</b>, a $1.35M fine for <b>Tractor Supply Co.</b>, and the UK's push for nationwide <b>Live Facial Recognition</b>. Finally, Google rolls out AI ransomware detection for Drive, and Afghanistan faces a nationwide internet blackout. 🌍</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_ACKjFSWlTnfBnzokyMcj_jcTE0-bmSk" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469014844</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Dive into the last 24 hours of critical cyber developments! 🚨 We're unpacking major breaches, including <b>Harrods' 430,000 customer records</b> exposed via a third-party supplier, and <b>Jaguar Land Rover's £1.5 billion recovery loan</b> after a production-halting cyberattack. Discover how a federal agency was compromised by an <b>unpatched GeoServer vulnerability</b>, Cloudflare mitigated a <b>record-breaking 22.2 Tbps DDoS attack</b>, and ransomware groups are actively exploiting <b>stolen AWS keys</b> to exfiltrate data. Plus, we cover the impact of a <b>data centre fire in South Korea</b> and cyberattacks marring <b>Moldova's elections</b>.</p>

<p>🛠️ Uncover the latest threat intelligence and new techniques: China-linked <b>ArcaneDoor exploited two Cisco firewall zero-days</b> (CVE-2025-20362, CVE-2025-20333) with novel malware, while Iran-linked <b>Nimbus Manticore expanded critical infrastructure targeting</b> using evolving malware and signed code. We detail aggressive <b>Akira ransomware campaigns</b> hitting MFA-protected SonicWall VPNs, the "significantly more dangerous" <b>LockBit 5.0</b>, and the alarming npm supply chain risk from the "postmark-mcp" package silently stealing emails.</p>

<p>⚠️ We also highlight critical vulnerabilities in <b>Supermicro BMCs</b> and the Streamlit framework. Hear about the Medusa ransomware gang's audacious attempt to recruit a BBC journalist as an insider threat, and the broader implications of geopolitical cyber tensions, including alleged Russian espionage. Stay ahead with the essential facts and takeaways from the frontline of information security. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:55:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Jsbr6jGmOTUH6ejGTKDLB_Smw6NsqTDU" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759182945602</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, September 29, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 In this edition of stdout, we dive deep into the latest <b>Akira ransomware</b> activity. Threat actors are actively exploiting <b>SonicWall SSL VPN devices</b>, leveraging an improper access control flaw (<b>CVE-2024-40766</b>) to gain initial access.</p>

<p>🔒 Discover how attackers are bypassing <b>one-time password multi-factor authentication (OTP MFA)</b> by utilising previously stolen credentials and OTP seeds, allowing persistent access even after patches. We unpack their post-exploitation tactics, including rapid internal network scanning, Impacket SMB/RDP usage, Active Directory enumeration, and targeting <b>Veeam Backup & Replication servers</b> to extract sensitive MSSQL and PostgreSQL credentials.</p>

<p>⚙️ Learn about their sophisticated evasion techniques, specifically <b>Bring-Your-Own-Vulnerable-Driver (BYOVD) attacks</b>. They're abusing Microsoft's <code>consent.exe</code> to sideload malicious DLLs, loading vulnerable drivers to effectively disable endpoint protection.</p>

<p>⚠️ <b>Critical takeaway:</b> Administrators are strongly advised to reset <b>all VPN credentials</b> on any device that previously utilised vulnerable firmware, as stolen accounts can still grant initial access.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1EiwHy8KK1GB4ByKW0i1691b0EQDW6Kr9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759096178496</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, September 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **Critical Threat Briefing: stdout Daily** 🚨</p>
<p>Dive deep into the latest cyber security developments. Today, we're tracking a year-long Chinese state-sponsored espionage campaign, <b>RedNovember</b> (TAG-100/Storm-2077), actively exploiting critical vulnerabilities in internet-facing appliances including Ivanti Connect Secure, Cisco ASA, FortiGate, and Palo Alto GlobalProtect VPNs. Discover their use of the Go-based <b>Pantegana</b> backdoor, Cobalt Strike, and SparkRAT. Plus, CISA and Cisco warn of ongoing <b>ArcaneDoor</b> activity targeting Cisco ASA/FTD firewalls with ROM modifications for persistence. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>Further Chinese-linked threats emerge with a new <b>PlugX</b> variant (Korplug/SOGU) targeting Asian telecommunications and manufacturing, leveraging DLL side-loading. We also cover Mustang Panda's continued use of the advanced <b>Bookworm</b> RAT against ASEAN networks. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>On the malware front, a new malvertising campaign is pushing the <b>Oyster backdoor</b> via fake Microsoft Teams installers. Learn how SEO poisoning, fraudulent certificates, and scheduled tasks are establishing persistence and remote access in corporate networks. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the concerning trend of minors being recruited for intelligence gathering, following Dutch arrests related to attempts to spy on Europol for Russia. We also touch on Alibaba's ambitious $53 billion global AI infrastructure plan and the geopolitical hurdles it faces, including Nvidia GPU access and data sovereignty concerns for new AI datacentres. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:51:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1qQDAwvXI1OIgPB5_3Yb0PcE5ad4x5w0g" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759009861519</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, September 27, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>&#x1F514; Dive into the latest cyber developments with stdout! 🇦🇺 This episode unpacks significant breaches, including **Volvo North America's** employee data theft via a ransomware attack on its HR provider, impacting 1.5 million individuals. 🚨 We also cover **Salesforce** facing lawsuits over customer data exposure from stolen OAuth tokens, and **Union County, Ohio's** ransomware incident compromising sensitive resident data. Plus, hear about two 17-year-olds arrested in the Netherlands for alleged pro-Russian cyber espionage.</p>

<p>&#x1F4BB; Uncover critical new threat research: **Microsoft Threat Intelligence** details an updated, highly obfuscated **macOS XCSSET** variant with enhanced browser targeting and crypto clipboard hijacking. **Trend Micro** warns of **LockBit 5.0**, a "significantly more dangerous" ransomware strain simultaneously targeting Windows, Linux, and VMware ESXi environments. 💥 We also break down the "ForcedLeak" attack against **Salesforce's Agentforce AI**, exploiting a DNS misconfiguration for indirect prompt injection and sensitive data exfiltration.</p>

<p>&#x26A0;&#xFE0F; Crucially, we delve into actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities. **Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT** (CVE-2025-10035) saw unauthenticated command injection exploited a week before public disclosure, leading to RCE and backdoor accounts. UK and US agencies have issued urgent directives for **Cisco ASA/FTD** zero-days (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362), chained for remote control by the state-sponsored **ArcaneDoor campaign** (UAT4356). Discover the sophisticated **RayInitiator** and **LINE VIPER** malware families deployed for persistence and evasion.</p>

<p>&#x2696;&#xFE0F; Stay informed on regulatory shifts: the **US Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015** faces expiration, and President Trump has approved a plan to restructure **TikTok's US operations** to address national security concerns. Finally, we touch on the **UK ICO's** hefty fines for illegal automated marketing calls, **Interpol's** major cybercrime crackdown in Africa, and **Microsoft Edge's** upcoming feature to revoke malicious sideloaded extensions. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TLnc4vCjXvkm0Sg3K9jgiTIpc464LHc4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758923523382</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, September 26, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>stdout: Daily Cyber Security Briefing</b> 🚀</p>
<p>stdout delivers your essential daily update for Cyber Security Analysts, diving deep into the last 24 hours of noteworthy developments, focusing on active threats, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>🚨 <b>Active Breaches & Attacks:</b> Kido International suffered a ransomware attack by the Radiant Group, leaking sensitive children's data. The Co-operative Group (UK) reports an £80M profit loss from a Scattered Spider attack that stole 6.5 million member records. A US federal agency was compromised via a GeoServer RCE (CVE-2024-36401), leading to web shells and lateral movement. Plus, an arrest linked to the "incredibly basic" HardBit ransomware affecting European airports.</p>

<p>🛠️ <b>Emerging Threats & Techniques:</b> North Korean groups are escalating malware capabilities with AkdoorTea, TsunamiKit, and Tropidoor, targeting crypto developers. Supply chain attacks are rampant: Shai-Hulud worm infected 500+ npm packages, malicious Rust packages stole crypto keys, and an unofficial npm package exfiltrated emails. Learn about AsyncRAT via ScreenConnect, StealC from game patches, Elons ransomware on Oracle DBS, and Android BankBot. Plus, new insights into LNK Stomping and the decade-old BiDi Swap URL spoofing vulnerability.</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Patches:</b> Cisco issues urgent warnings and patches for actively exploited zero-days (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362) in ASA/FTD, with a CISA emergency directive. Salesforce patched a critical "ForcedLeak" flaw (CVSS 9.4) in Agentforce AI, allowing CRM data exfiltration. OnePlus OxygenOS has a permission bypass (CVE-2025-10184) for SMS/MMS data, and SonicWall is expediting EOL for SMA 100 devices after rootkit malware discoveries.</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Threat Landscape & Geopolitics:</b> Discussions on "AI security" vs. "AI safety" and how AI coding assistants increase security findings. Russian state-backed Storm-1679 targets Moldovan elections with disinformation, and PyPI warns of ongoing phishing attacks. Also, updates on data privacy (Google/Flo, TikTok Canada), the EU's new Entry/Exit System, and law enforcement successes against dark web markets and financial crime.</p>

<p>💡 <b>CTEM Insights:</b> An overview of Continuous Threat Exposure Management, emphasising prioritisation based on business impact and validation through breach and attack simulation.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1UXaff5Dr3bvzVzOsg2vcCoXIBZen9d5A" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758837259619</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, September 25, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Dive!** 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks the last 24 hours in infosec, from major arrests to critical exploits. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>Catch up on the UK arrest linked to the **Collins Aerospace MUSE ransomware attack** impacting European airports, and Boyd Gaming's employee data breach. A 19-year-old has been apprehended as a core figure in the notorious **Scattered Spider** group, linked to 120 attacks and $89.5M in crypto. Interpol's Operation HAECHI VI seized over $439M from cyber-enabled financial crimes. 💰</p>

<p>New threats include sophisticated **phishing campaigns** targeting Python developers via fake PyPI sites and abusing GitHub notifications to drain crypto wallets. Dive into detailed research on "Brickstorm" (UNC5221), a long-running Chinese cyberespionage campaign targeting legal, SaaS, and tech for IP theft and zero-day development, maintaining persistence for 400 days. Also, discover "RedNovember" (Storm-2077), another Chinese state-sponsored actor exploiting perimeter appliance vulnerabilities from Ivanti, Cisco, and Fortinet. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities are under active exploitation: a high-severity **Cisco IOS/IOS XE zero-day (CVE-2025-20352)** allowing RCE, and a command injection flaw in **Libraesva Email Security Gateway (CVE-2025-59689)** exploited by state-sponsored actors. We also discuss in-the-wild exploitation of a **Pandoc SSRF (CVE-2025-51591)** targeting AWS IMDS, new **Supermicro BMC firmware vulnerabilities** allowing persistent control, and an unpatched **OnePlus OxygenOS flaw (CVE-2025-10184)** exposing SMS data. 💥</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the broader impact of cyberattacks, including the **Jaguar Land Rover production halt** and the catastrophic collapse of KNP Logistics Group due to an Akira ransomware attack exploiting a single weak password. Plus, a quick look at the new Kali Linux 2025.3 release. Stay informed, stay secure! 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1DVy51Og5djBi1_yx6l2K62ni8MFty-5f" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758750799224</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, September 24, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 Your daily deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. Today, we're analysing a record-breaking 22.2 Tbps DDoS attack, a US federal agency breach via unpatched GeoServer RCE (CVE-2024-36401), and major disruptions impacting Jaguar Land Rover, Circle K, and Lotte Card's 3 million customers.</p>

<p>🔍 Discover new threats: Iran-backed Nimbus Manticore's novel DLL loading for MiniJunk/MiniBrowse, RevengeHotels leveraging AI-generated VenomRAT, and "Operation Rewrite" using BadIIS for SEO poisoning. Plus, a malicious npm package 'fezbox' employing steganographic QR codes to steal browser cookies.</p>

<p>🩹 Critical vulnerabilities and patches: SolarWinds' third hotfix for a Web Help Desk RCE patch bypass (CVE-2025-26399), SonicWall's update to remove the OVERSTEP rootkit, and an emergency fix for Libraesva's Email Security Gateway (CVE-2025-59689) actively exploited by a suspected state entity. Rapid7 also disclosed an unpatched critical SQL injection in OnePlus OxygenOS (CVE-2025-10184) allowing SMS/MMS data access.</p>

<p>💡 Broader insights include 62% of cyber leaders reporting AI-driven attacks, the link between REST Media and Russia's Rybar disinformation, and GitHub's new mandatory 2FA and granular tokens for npm security. We also touch on the unsustainable model of open source infrastructure and the complexities of North Korean IT worker sanctions compliance.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Mj6Ihsr9xWRlykEv8X_JGvXqECmjCDMF" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758664360136</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 23, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>Daily stdout: Cyber Events, Exploits & Techniques</h3>
<p>Your daily deep dive into the latest in cybersecurity! 🚀 Today, we're unpacking significant disruptions, from European aviation chaos caused by a Collins Aerospace ransomware attack to Dallas Fort Worth International Airport's fibre optic woes. Catch up on the latest arrests linked to the 2023 Scattered Spider attacks on MGM and Caesars, costing over $100 million. 💸 Plus, Stellantis confirms a data leak via a compromised Salesforce provider, with ShinyHunters claiming 18 million records. Even France's Natural History Museum wasn't safe, losing gold nuggets after a ransomware attack disabled security. 🏛️ And a verified Steam game, 'BlockBlasters,' turned malicious, siphoning $150,000 from 261 accounts with a cryptodrainer.</p>

<p>Dive into cutting-edge threat research, including 'EDR-Freeze,' a novel user-mode technique that can indefinitely suspend EDR and antivirus processes without a kernel driver. 🥶 We also analyse new campaigns: ComicForm targeting Eurasian sectors with Formbook, and the pro-Russian SectorJ149 (UAC-0050) deploying Lumma Stealer, Formbook, and Remcos RAT against South Korean industries. 🕵️‍♂️ LastPass warns macOS users about fake software impersonating password managers, delivering the Atomic (AMOS) info-stealer, now with a backdoor component.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Microsoft patched a critical CVE-2025-55241 in Entra ID (CVSS 10.0), allowing global administrator impersonation. 🚨 The American Archive of Public Broadcasting also fixed an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) flaw that exposed private media for years. In the broader threat landscape, AT&T highlights Chinese Salt Typhoon's influence on 'living off the land' techniques, while the FBI warns of spoofed IC3 websites. 🌐 Lloyds Banking Group's AI implementation shows the tightrope walk between innovation and security, blocking platforms like Hugging Face.</p>

<p>Data privacy takes centre stage with patients advocating for stronger neural data rights as scientists decode inner speech from Brain Computer Interface (BCI) implants. 🧠 Regulatory hurdles loom as CISA 2015 faces expiration, potentially increasing cyber risk, and Senator Tom Cotton proposes an 18-month 'clean' reauthorization of FISA Section 702 amidst privacy concerns.</p>

<p>Finally, the US government mandates a transition to NIST's new post-quantum cryptography standards by 2030/2035 to counter 'harvest now, decrypt later' threats. 🔒 ICE HSI has acquired Magnet Forensics' Graykey software for device unlocking. Plus, Mozilla introduces a new Firefox feature allowing add-on developers to roll back to previous approved versions for quicker bug fixes. 🦊</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 02:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=195cnruZ0RndtX63l587pXN63yLhHjmZa" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758594958815</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, September 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 On this episode of stdout, we're diving deep into two critical cybersecurity developments:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Microsoft Entra ID Vulnerability (CVE-2025-55241):</strong> Discover how a critical flaw, leveraging undocumented "actor tokens" and a deprecated API, could have granted Global Administrator privileges across any Entra ID tenant globally. Learn about the stealthy exploitation potential and Microsoft's swift patch.</li>
</ul>

<p>🇰🇵 We then pivot to the evolving tactics of North Korean state-sponsored hacking groups, including Lazarus, ScarCruft (APT37), and Kimsuky (APT43). Expect insights into:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Sophisticated Social Engineering:</strong> How "ClickFix" lures in fake cryptocurrency job scams deliver malware like BeaverTail and InvisibleFerret, with expanded targeting beyond software developers.</li>
    <li><strong>ScarCruft's Shift:</strong> A notable move from pure espionage to financially motivated and potentially destructive operations, deploying VCD ransomware for the first time, alongside new tools like the Rust-based CHILLYCHINO and FadeStealer. 💸</li>
    <li><strong>Kimsuky's Innovation:</strong> Abuse of GitHub repositories for malware delivery and data exfiltration, plus their alarming use of OpenAI's ChatGPT to forge deepfake military ID cards in spear-phishing campaigns targeting South Korean defence entities. 🤖</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:51:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A0I0n_EPVK_8tVhUQ9LzMDNsIM9o0F1v" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758491463480</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, September 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 stdout uncovers a critical <b>zero-click vulnerability</b>, codenamed <i>ShadowLeak</i>, in OpenAI ChatGPT's Deep Research agent. Crafted emails leveraging <b>indirect prompt injection</b> could exfiltrate sensitive Gmail inbox data directly from OpenAI's cloud infrastructure, bypassing traditional client-side defences. This flaw, now patched, highlights risks with enabled third-party integrations. 📧</p>

<p>Next, we expose a widespread campaign targeting macOS users with the potent <b>Atomic Stealer malware</b>. Threat actors are deploying <b>fake GitHub repositories</b> impersonating legitimate tools like LastPass and 1Password, using <b>SEO poisoning</b> to push malicious downloads. This campaign underscores persistent social engineering and supply chain compromise tactics. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, a significant regulatory crackdown: the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) has shut down the <b>TradeOgre cryptocurrency exchange</b>, seizing over $40 million. This marks Canada's first crypto exchange shutdown, driven by failures in FINTRAC registration and Know Your Customer (KYC) policies, making it a conduit for cybercrime money laundering. 💰</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 21:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1tMHgZfBPEoSMn5FdtmT3JrJqstl-MKiy" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758405025397</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, September 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cybersecurity with "stdout"! We're breaking down 12 critical topics for technical analysts, focusing on active cyber events, exploited vulnerabilities, and emerging threat techniques. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>This episode, we cover the <b>arrests of two Scattered Spider affiliates</b> in the UK, linked to over $115 million in ransoms and a US federal court breach. We also track a <b>cyberattack on Russia's Pulkovo Airport</b> and an Iran-nexus group, UNC1549, infiltrating 11 European telecommunications companies via LinkedIn lures and the MINIBIKE backdoor. ✈️</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Fortra warns of a <b>max-severity deserialisation flaw (CVE-2025-10035)</b> in GoAnywhere MFT, mirroring a past Clop zero-day. CISA details malware exploiting <b>Ivanti EPMM zero-days (CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428)</b>, potentially by China-nexus groups. Plus, discover a critical, now-mitigated <b>Microsoft Entra ID flaw (CVE-2025-55241)</b> that could have granted global admin access, and OpenAI's patch for <b>ChatGPT's "ShadowLeak"</b>, allowing Gmail secret exfiltration. 💥</p>

<p>New threat research reveals <b>collaboration between Russian state-sponsored groups Gamaredon and Turla</b>, with Gamaredon providing initial access for Turla's Kazuar backdoor. Uncover China's "AI persona army" for information warfare and the surge in <b>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platforms like Lighthouse and Lucid</b>, driving 17,500+ phishing domains. We also explore how researchers tricked ChatGPT into solving CAPTCHAs, raising questions about their long-term effectiveness. 🤖</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, MI6 launches a <b>dark web portal "Silent Courier"</b> for informant recruitment, the FBI warns of fake IC3 portals, and the future of the CVE Program is debated amidst funding concerns. Stay ahead with stdout! 💡</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1j3GmxORR1uzJylpdZTURpYCcZjQRru00" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758318799585</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, September 19, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats and vulnerabilities impacting the digital landscape. This episode unpacks a massive alleged data theft by **ShinyHunters**, claiming 1.5 billion Salesforce records via a Salesloft supply chain attack, impacting major organisations like Google and Palo Alto Networks. We also cover a confirmed ransomware attack on venture capital firm **Insight Partners** affecting over 12,000 individuals, and a critical breach of **SonicWall's cloud backup service** exposing firewall configurations for a segment of its user base. The healthcare sector remains a prime target, with three separate breaches exposing data for over 850,000 Americans. 🏥</p>

<p>Stay informed on active threat actors and emerging techniques: two alleged **Scattered Spider** members have been charged in connection with the Transport for London attack. Discover how the Russian troll farm **CopyCop (Storm-1516)** is leveraging self-hosted LLMs to generate fake news across 200+ sites, and learn about malicious `sisaws` and `secmeasure` packages in PyPI delivering the **SilentSync RAT**. China-backed **TA415 (APT41)** is actively targeting US government and academic organisations with sophisticated phishing, while the **SystemBC botnet** compromises 1,500 commercial VPS daily for malicious traffic. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities and essential patches: Google has issued an urgent update for a **sixth Chrome zero-day (CVE-2025-10585)** actively exploited in the wild. WatchGuard released security updates for a critical **Firebox RCE (CVE-2025-9242)**, and OpenAI patched a "ShadowLeak" zero-click vulnerability in **ChatGPT's Deep Research agent**. Plus, all PyPI tokens stolen in the recent **GhostAction supply chain attack** have been invalidated. 🔒</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on Cloudflare's self-inflicted outage, Brazil's new **Digital ECA law** for child data protection, the confirmation of Katherine Sutton as the Pentagon's new Assistant Secretary of Defence for Cyber Policy, and how federal agencies are increasingly incorporating AI into cyber defences. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fMFzF4_YDJnVctKBy8YGziTDZb5NZDa8" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758282372409</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, September 18, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout delivers your daily intel. Today, we unpack the ongoing fallout from the Colt Technology Services and Jaguar Land Rover ransomware attacks, a brute-force breach impacting SonicWall's MySonicWall.com, and a sophisticated ransomware incident at Insight Partners. New threat research highlights Microsoft and Cloudflare's takedown of the RaccoonO365 Phishing-as-a-Service, the resurgence of Scattered Spider targeting the financial sector via social engineering and Azure AD SSPR, and how groups like Kimsuky and RevengeHotels are leveraging AI for deepfakes and refined malware. We also delve into 'Phoenix', a new Rowhammer attack (CVE-2025-6202) affecting DDR5 memory, and the resentencing of BreachForums founder 'Pompompurin'.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=12l35AcBToFxS0D7tA1yVYBmKT3GM8ZBI" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758177075763</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the last 24 hours in cyber security. We dive into the FBI's FLASH alert on UNC6040/UNC6395 (ShinyHunters/Scattered Spider) compromising Salesforce via vishing and OAuth token exploits, alongside ongoing disruption at Jaguar Land Rover and a ransomware attack forcing a Texas school district closure. Discover how Akira ransomware bypassed MFA in a SonicWall VPN breach using plaintext recovery codes, and the largest npm supply chain compromise to date, impacting billions of downloads after a maintainer was phished. We also cover new SEO poisoning campaigns distributing novel malware, Mustang Panda's updated TONESHELL and geofenced SnakeDisk worm, and Kimsuky spies leveraging ChatGPT for fake IDs. Plus, a new Rowhammer attack variant, "Phoenix," bypasses DDR5 defences to achieve root privileges, and Microsoft warns about SMBv1 connection issues. Stay informed on these critical developments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1oMEIaRwMA553EYRQUweD9Yk_FCWlstCk" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758175389469</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, September 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the latest in cyber security: Jaguar Land Rover's operations remain suspended following a 'Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' attack, with the group also creating a fraudulent account in Google's LERS portal. We detail 'Shai-Hulud,' a self-propagating npm worm actively stealing credentials, and the 'FileFix' social engineering technique delivering the StealC infostealer via fake Facebook alerts and steganography. Explore the massive 'SlopAds' ad fraud operation exploiting Android apps, plus the new 'Phoenix' RowHammer variant bypassing DDR5 memory protections. Apple has backported patches for an actively exploited Image I/O zero-day. Also, China's stricter incident reporting mandates, Microsoft's removal of WMIC, and Check Point's acquisition of AI security platform Lakera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 04:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Ycw0BHzmaCvuT0Ce0tLUJErkxyOqJBPR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758171526797</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
