<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:anchor="https://anchor.fm/xmlns" xmlns:podcast="https://podcastindex.org/namespace/1.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:psc="http://podlove.org/simple-chapters">
  <channel>
    <title>stdout security</title>
    <description>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.
      
      Note: This is an AI-generated summary of News Articles from the past 24 hours. I take no credit for the research or analysis in said articles - this podcast only exists as a simple audio summary to help busy, sleep-deprivd Cyber Nerds like myself keep on top of developments while wranging kids and brushing teeth.
    </description>
    <link>https://opalsec.io</link>
    <generator>Anchor Podcasts</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 05:06:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <author>Opalsec</author>
    <copyright>Opalsec</copyright>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="https://anchor.fm/s/109797ef8/podcast/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/>
    <itunes:author>Opalsec</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Opalsec</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>opalsec.integrate@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:category text="News">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:image href="https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_nologo/44439246/44439246-1758158096542-bb2824b85de8c.jpg"/>
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, November 11, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catch up on the last 24 hours in cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! 🎧</p>

<p>This episode unpacks critical active events, including the <b>Clop ransomware's Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882)</b> impacting Allianz UK, and a massive data breach at Chinese firm Knownsec exposing state-owned cyber weapons and global target lists. We also cover a widespread <b>PureRAT phishing campaign</b> targeting the hospitality sector and the conviction of a Yanluowang ransomware Initial Access Broker. 💥</p>

<p>Dive into new threat research: discover how <b>Curly COMrades abuses Hyper-V</b> for stealthy malware deployment, the rise of <b>Cephalus Go-based ransomware</b> exploiting RDP, and malicious NuGet packages with time-delayed logic bombs. Plus, we examine information stealer campaigns leveraging EvilAI-created installers and Aurologic GmbH's role as a high-risk hosting hub. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: CISA orders patching for a <b>Samsung zero-day (CVE-2025-21042)</b> actively exploited by LandFall spyware, and a severe RCE in the <b><code>expr-eval</code> JavaScript library (CVE-2025-12735)</b>. We also detail patched flaws in Microsoft Teams, SimpleHelp RMM exploits leading to ransomware, and supply chain risks in Advanced Installer. 🚨</p>

<p>Finally, we explore the evolving landscape of AI in security, from Cisco's new 17-billion parameter model to Microsoft's "Agent 365" and the "Whisper Leak" side-channel attack. Get the lowdown on the temporary extension of the U.S. CISA Act, Australia's sanctions against North Korean cybercrime, and new privacy features from WhatsApp and Microsoft Authenticator. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:52:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1jQoSfyYFnSv10qQ92FOFblTrvAwP0wsz" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762807950625</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, November 10, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Unpacking critical cyber developments from the last 24 hours. </p>

<p>First up, we're diving into three new <b>runC vulnerabilities</b> (CVE-2025-31133, CVE-2025-52565, CVE-2025-52881) impacting <b>Docker and Kubernetes container runtimes</b>. These flaws could allow attackers to <b>bypass container isolation</b> and gain <b>root access to the host system</b> by manipulating <code>/dev/null</code> and <code>/dev/console</code> bind-mounts. Patches are available in runC versions 1.2.8, 1.3.3, and 1.4.0-rc.3+, with user namespaces and rootless containers offering key mitigations. </p>

<p>📱 Next, the Swiss National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) warns of a sophisticated new <b>iPhone phishing scam</b>. Threat actors are sending targeted smishing texts, often with convincing details from the device's lock screen, to trick lost iPhone owners into clicking fake "Find My" links. The goal? To <b>steal Apple ID credentials</b> and potentially <b>bypass Activation Lock</b> for device resale. Remember: enable Lost Mode immediately, use a dedicated email for contact details, and protect your SIM with a PIN. Apple will never contact you via SMS or email about a found device. 🎣</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 20:49:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=11dZUbr1kDMUsi8w8ijxeZryVNspozvkP" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762721372682</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 9, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Key cyber developments from the last 24 hours:</p>

<p>A Russian national has pleaded guilty as an Initial Access Broker for the Yanluowang ransomware group, facilitating attacks on seven US businesses and demanding $24 million. ⚖️</p>

<p>New threat research reveals:</p>
<ul>
    <li>Malicious NuGet packages with "time bombs" set for 2027/2028, targeting .NET database providers and impersonating the Sharp7 library for Siemens S7 industrial control devices. These could cause immediate operational stops or data corruption. Organisations are advised to audit assets. 💣</li>
    <li>Microsoft's "Whisper Leak" — a novel side-channel attack inferring AI chatbot conversation topics from encrypted TLS traffic with over 98% accuracy, posing significant privacy risks to LLMs. 🤫</li>
</ul>

<p>On exploited vulnerabilities:</p>
<ul>
    <li>LANDFALL, a commercial-grade Android spyware, exploited a zero-day (CVE-2025-21042) in Samsung Galaxy devices for nearly a year. The surveillance campaign, likely starting in July 2024, targeted specific Samsung Galaxy devices in the Middle East via zero-click attacks, often through crafted images. This spyware records calls, tracks locations, and harvests data, potentially linked to state-sponsored actors. 📱🕵️‍♂️</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Wx-rbG0XtWs7jTBTfCWD2jU9dD972inZ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762635011930</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 8, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout Daily Intel: Cyber Events & Exploits** 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. We unpack a suspected foreign actor breach at the US Congressional Budget Office and the UK's first-ever economic impact classification for a cyberattack, with Jaguar Land Rover's incident costing up to £2.1 billion. 💸</p>

<p>Threat intel reveals a new wave of sophisticated attacks:</p>
<ul>
    <li>📱 **"Landfall" Android Spyware:** Exploiting a zero-day (CVE-2025-21042) via WhatsApp DNG images for zero-click surveillance on Samsung Galaxy phones.</li>
    <li>🦠 **Gootloader Resurgence:** Delivering Rhysida ransomware with rapid domain controller compromise, using SEO poisoning and custom fonts for obfuscation.</li>
    <li>🛠️ **Malicious Dev Tools:** Watch out for rogue VS Code extensions, npm packages distributing Vidar Stealer, and NuGet time-bomb packages targeting Siemens S7 PLCs.</li>
    <li>🇨🇳 **China-linked APTs:** Exploiting legacy vulnerabilities for long-term persistence, deploying custom loaders and RATs, with ties to Salt Typhoon and Space Pirates.</li>
</ul>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Cisco ASA/FTD zero-days (CVE-2025-20362, CVE-2025-20333) are now actively exploited for denial-of-service attacks, forcing reboots. 🛡️ QNAP has patched seven zero-days, successfully exploited at Pwn2Own Ireland 2025. Update your systems immediately! 🩹</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, Google introduces new features to combat review extortion and highlights prevalent scams. 🌐 We analyse Illuminate Education's $5.1M fine for a data breach, Microsoft's EU data sovereignty efforts, and EPIC's concerns over government data mining. 🔒 New global regulations like DORA and SEC rules are driving a shift towards greater cyber accountability. ⚖️ Finally, the Department of Defense's revised master plan for cyber forces outlines a long road ahead for talent attraction and retention. 🏛️🚀</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:52:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fH756o5cftDZsuFeJ7r7kGQgADXQEiIW" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762548754051</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, November 7, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive into the latest 24-hour cyber developments, tailored for Cyber Security Analysts. Today, we're unpacking critical breaches, novel attack techniques, and urgent vulnerability alerts.</p>

<p><b>Breaches & Intrusions:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Hyundai AutoEver America confirms a data breach exposing names, Social Security Numbers, and driver's licences.</li>
    <li>Japanese media giant Nikkei reports a breach impacting over 17,000 employees and partners after malware compromised an internal Slack workspace.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>New Threats & Techniques:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Gootloader resurfaces with advanced SEO poisoning, utilising custom web fonts and malformed Zip archives to evade analysis, dropping the Supper SOCKS5 backdoor.</li>
    <li>Discover InedibleOchotense, a new Russia-aligned threat cluster impersonating ESET in spear-phishing campaigns against Ukrainian entities, deploying the Tor-enabled Kalambur backdoor.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Exploits:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Cisco issues urgent patches for critical flaws (CVE-2025-20354, CVE-2025-20358) in Unified Contact Center Express (UCCX), allowing unauthenticated RCE and authentication bypass.</li>
    <li>Cisco also warns of ongoing, sophisticated attacks by the government-backed ArcaneDoor group targeting Secure ASA and FTD firewalls, causing denial-of-service and employing zero-days for persistence.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Active Threat Landscape:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>Russian state-backed Sandworm hackers are deploying destructive data-wiping malware against Ukraine's education, government, and critical grain sector.</li>
    <li>The State of Nevada releases a transparent after-action report detailing a ransomware attack, from initial compromise via a trojanised Google ad to a $1.5M recovery effort.</li>
</ul>

<p><b>Privacy & Security Insights:</b></p>
<ul>
    <li>An Italian executive reveals he was targeted with Paragon spyware, adding to a growing list of victims.</li>
    <li>Comparitech's latest study highlights persistent human laziness in password choices, with "123456" and "admin" remaining top offenders.</li>
</ul>
<p>Stay informed, stay secure. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1nQGLeFpgir9WYs92X3TXmarXXSr8vZpv" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762462323316</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, November 6, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</strong> The University of Pennsylvania confirms a data breach exposing 1.2 million donor records and internal documents via compromised credentials. SonicWall attributes a September incident to state-sponsored hackers accessing firewall configuration data. Plus, Operation Chargeback dismantles credit card fraud networks, recovering over €300 million from 4.3 million victims globally.</p>

<p>🤖 <strong>Emerging Threats & Tradecraft:</strong> Google's Threat Intelligence Group reveals a significant shift towards AI-powered malware, with new families leveraging LLMs for dynamic self-modification and obfuscation. State-backed actors are also abusing Google's Gemini LLM for vulnerability research and phishing. Tenable researchers uncover indirect prompt injection flaws in OpenAI's ChatGPT, while Russia-linked Curly COMrades employ malicious Alpine Linux VMs within Hyper-V for covert persistence. An Iranian threat cluster, UNK_SmudgedSerpent, targets US academics with social engineering and legitimate RMM tools.</p>

<p>⚠️ <strong>Critical Vulnerabilities Exploited:</strong> CISA adds two actively exploited flaws to its KEV catalog: a file disclosure in Gladinet CentreStack/Triofox (CVE-2025-11371) and an unauthenticated RCE in Control Web Panel (CVE-2025-48703). Urgent updates are also needed for actively exploited WordPress plugins (WP Freeio, Noo JobMonster, Post SMTP) enabling privilege escalation. AMD addresses a high-severity flaw (CVE-2025-62626) in Zen 5 CPUs that could weaken cryptographic keys.</p>

<p>⚖️ <strong>Regulatory & Privacy Shifts:</strong> The US DHS proposes a controversial expansion of biometric data collection for immigration. The US Treasury sanctions North Korean entities laundering cryptocurrency to fund weapons programs. The UK launches a Telecoms Charter to combat fraud, and US House GOP leaders push for restrictions on Chinese tech in critical industries. Also, Google's $32 billion acquisition of Wiz receives US DOJ clearance, and a new memory-safe C/C++ compiler, Fil-C, earns a favourable review.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 20:51:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1MXXPhCh-8pl0WBZvOc6Q2T2LzGGOw8TK" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762375917630</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, November 5, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Stay across the latest in cyber security. We're tracking a massive <b>$100M+ crypto heist</b> from Balancer's DeFi pools, potentially linked to North Korean groups, alongside a concerning <b>insider threat</b> where cyber professionals deployed ALPHV/BlackCat ransomware. Sweden's Miljödata suffered a breach impacting 1.5 million, while Poland faced a wave of attacks, possibly tied to Russian hybrid warfare. 💰</p>

<p>Analyse new threats: discover <b>"SleepyDuck,"</b> a malicious Solidity VSCode extension using Ethereum smart contracts for resilient command-and-control. Explore sophisticated campaigns targeting the <b>defence sector</b>, including Operation SkyCloak's Tor-enabled backdoors and Russia's Curly COMrades exploiting Microsoft Hyper-V to bypass EDR. We also cover <b>"SesameOp,"</b> a novel backdoor abusing OpenAI's Assistants API for stealthy C2, and the alarming <b>67% surge in mobile malware</b> on Google Play. 📱</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Google's AI agent, Big Sleep, uncovered <b>five critical WebKit flaws</b> in Apple Safari, now patched. We also delve into the "dramatic" rise in cybercrime involving physical violence in Europe, the retraction of a controversial AI-driven ransomware report, and significant privacy concerns around health data and EU Commission location tracking. Get the essential updates. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:52:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1KE-pzCXcVq1_lZs3ASxkEFrMq_WRu2eu" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762289543981</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, November 4, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay sharp with your daily dose of cyber intelligence! 🇦🇺 This episode of <b>stdout</b> unpacks the last 24 hours, highlighting critical active events. We're tracking the University of Pennsylvania's 1.2 million donor record breach via compromised SSO, and Askul's 1.1TB data leak following a <i>RansomHouse</i> attack. Discover how cybercriminals are now collaborating with organised crime to hijack physical cargo using compromised RMM tools like <i>ScreenConnect</i>. Plus, hear about the indictment of three former IR pros for <i>BlackCat</i> ransomware attacks and SK Telecom's massive financial hit from a data breach.</p>

<p>Dive into cutting-edge threat research, including Australia's ASD warning on the <i>"BADCANDY"</i> implant actively targeting unpatched Cisco IOS XE (CVE-2023-20198). 🚨 We reveal <i>"Airstalk,"</i> a suspected nation-state Windows malware exfiltrating data from Omnissa Workspace ONE, and new Android threats like <i>"BankBot-YNRK"</i> and <i>"DeliveryRAT."</i> Uncover how <i>Qilin</i> ransomware now leverages WSL for Linux encryptors, and the novel <i>"SesameOp"</i> backdoor using OpenAI's API for covert C2. We also detail malicious VS Code extensions, Discord-based RATs, and <i>BlueNoroff's</i> multi-platform <i>"GhostCall"</i> campaigns targeting Web3 professionals.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, we break down Microsoft's hotpatching woes with KB5070881 for a critical WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287), and significant flaws in LUKS2 disk encryption impacting confidential computing systems. 🔒 Plus, learn about exposed API keys and a backdoor in Tata Motors' sites, risking over 70 terabytes of sensitive data.</p>

<p>Beyond the immediate threats, we examine the heightened cyberattack risks to European power grids and hacktivist targeting of internet-exposed industrial control systems. 🌐 Proton's new Data Breach Observatory reveals 306.1 million leaked records, with small and medium-sized businesses as prime targets. We also touch on WhatsApp's biometric passkeys, the push for cyber reinsurance, and MITRE ATT&CK v18's enhanced mobile and ICS coverage. Stay informed, stay secure.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:53:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TRErvt94SX95Rp_i9v-FIhcIkPXlJCke" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762203220254</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, November 2, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Alert: Cisco IOS XE Under Siege!</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Active exploitation of <b>CVE-2023-20198</b>, a critical 10.0 CVSS vulnerability, is impacting unpatched Cisco IOS XE devices. China-linked threat actors, including Salt Typhoon, are weaponising the low-equity BADCANDY Lua-based web shell to create privileged accounts and seize control. An urgent ASD bulletin highlights hundreds of Australian devices compromised since late 2023. Essential hardening guidelines are crucial to protect infrastructure from re-infection.</p>

<p>📧 A politically motivated cyber incident at the University of Pennsylvania saw an offensive email targeting thousands of students, highlighting potential email system compromises and data breach threats. This bears hallmarks of similar attacks following the Supreme Court's affirmative action ruling.</p>

<p>⚖️ Federal law enforcement has arrested Baron Cain Martin, an alleged leader of the violent extremist group 764. Martin faces 29 charges, including providing material support to terrorists and the production/distribution of child sexual abuse material. The group leverages cyber means for grooming and extortion, with ongoing law enforcement efforts to dismantle such networks.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:50:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1CtM31DRm-wtSbS-sy5f1m1Fd66XstaQR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1762030206899</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, November 1, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>stdout: Key Cyber Developments (Last 24 Hrs)</strong> 🚨</p>
<p>This episode covers the extradition of an alleged <strong>Conti ransomware</strong> member and arrests linked to <strong>Meduza Stealer</strong> in Russia. We also analyse a university breach sending offensive emails.</p>
<p>🔍 <strong>Threat Intel & Exploits:</strong> Discover <strong>Airstalk</strong>, a new malware by CL-STA-1009 misusing AirWatch MDM APIs for covert C2. We detail active exploitation of an unpatched <strong>Windows LNK vulnerability (CVE-2025-9491)</strong> by UNC6384/Mustang Panda targeting EU diplomacy. CISA adds a <strong>VMware Tools/Aria zero-day (CVE-2025-41244)</strong> and a <strong>Linux kernel flaw (CVE-2024-1086)</strong>, now used in ransomware, to its KEV catalogue.</p>
<p>🔥 <strong>Critical Warnings:</strong> The Australian government warns of ongoing exploitation of <strong>Cisco IOS XE (CVE-2023-20198)</strong> by state actors like Salt Typhoon, planting BadCandy webshells. Storm-1849/UAT4356 is actively scanning and exploiting <strong>Cisco ASA (CVE-2025-30333, CVE-2025-20362)</strong> against US financials and government. CISA/NSA release guidance to harden Exchange and WSUS following exploitation of <strong>WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287)</strong>.</p>
<p>🛡️ <strong>Policy & Privacy:</strong> We touch on the critical need for government-industry collaboration, privacy concerns around the <strong>Digital Euro</strong>, and the FCC's plan to rescind telecom cybersecurity regulations. Also, NHS hospitals face risks due to <strong>Windows 11 upgrade delays</strong>, and Microsoft Edge rolls out a new <strong>scareware sensor</strong>.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 20:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1s77qvqEWnySRA8brlmtDyzHzqb3PION5" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761943977458</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 31, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily:</b> Unpacking the last 24 hours in cyber security. 🚨</p>

<p>This episode dives into critical active events, including hacktivists tampering with Canadian industrial control systems and an ex-L3Harris Trenchant GM pleading guilty to selling US cyber-exploits to a Russian broker. We also analyse the financial fallout of a cyberattack on Marks & Spencer and a brief data exposure at the People's Postcode Lottery. 🇨🇦🇬🇧</p>

<p>Dive deep into new threat research: two significant npm supply chain campaigns, "PhantomRaven" utilising novel Remote Dynamic Dependencies to bypass static analysis and steal credentials, plus another infostealer campaign using typosquatting and multi-layered obfuscation. Also, Russia-linked cybercriminals are abusing the AdaptixC2 framework for ransomware. 💻🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Urgent vulnerability alerts: Docker users are advised to update due to high-severity path traversal (CVE-2025-62725) in Docker Compose and a patched DLL hijacking flaw (EUVD-2025-36191) in Docker Desktop. CISA and NSA have also released new guidance for hardening Microsoft Exchange servers, with over 29,000 still vulnerable to a critical hybrid flaw (CVE-2025-53786). ⚠️</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on data privacy concerns as advocacy groups urge the FTC to block Meta's AI chatbot data plans, and France's move to the decentralised Matrix network for secure government communications. 🇫🇷🔒</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:52:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1grwJ1QN9knJ2VQDcTtc6bpanE2_LUS89" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761857546078</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>This episode unpacks the latest in cyber security from the last 24 hours. We dive into significant breaches, including advertising giant Dentsu's U.S. subsidiary, Merkle, exposing staff and client data, and EY's 4TB unencrypted SQL Server backup exposed due to a cloud misconfiguration. Hear about Russian threat actors using living-off-the-land tactics in Ukraine and Cloud Atlas exploiting the old CVE-2017-11882 against Russia's agricultural sector. Plus, hacktivist breaches against Canadian critical infrastructure caused disruptions and unsafe conditions. 🚨</p>

<p>🔍 Discover new threat research, including "AI-targeted cloaking" – a context poisoning attack against agentic web browsers like ChatGPT Atlas. Qualys reports a surge in automated botnet attacks (Mirai, Gafgyt, Mozi) exploiting RCE vulnerabilities in PHPUnit, Laravel, and Spring Cloud Gateway. We also expose the "PhantomRaven" campaign, deploying 126 malicious npm packages to steal authentication tokens and CI/CD secrets, cleverly evading static analysis.</p>

<p>⚠️ On the vulnerability front, a critical, unpatched denial-of-service flaw dubbed "Brash" has been found in Chromium's Blink engine, capable of crashing billions of browsers. We also highlight Germany's alarming 92% of public-facing Exchange servers running out-of-support versions. Stay informed on the UK ICO's £200k fine for spam texts and the AFP's new AI tool to interpret "crimefluencer" slang. Get the essential facts you need to stay ahead!</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:51:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1mSZH0olaOnnwiTM_Jns9c-DxnHrLAEpp" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761771099944</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 29, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Stay sharp with the latest in cyber security! This episode of stdout dives into critical developments from the last 24 hours. We unpack F5's nation-state attack update and Google's refutation of a massive Gmail breach. 🕵️‍♂️ Discover new threat actor tactics, including SideWinder's ClickOnce attacks on South Asian diplomats, the emergence of the Atroposia malware-as-a-service platform, and BlueNoroff's sophisticated GhostCall and GhostHire campaigns targeting Web3. Plus, we analyse the Qilin ransomware gang's active RaaS operations, now leveraging Windows Subsystem for Linux to bypass traditional defences.</p>

<p>🔒 Get the lowdown on actively exploited vulnerabilities: a critical Windows Server Update Services (WSUS) RCE (CVE-2025-59287) with widespread exploitation, and two Dassault Systèmes DELMIA Apriso flaws (CVE-2025-6205, CVE-2025-6204). We also explore TEE.Fail, a new side-channel attack extracting secrets from Intel, AMD, and NVIDIA TEEs, and the inherent prompt injection vulnerabilities in AI browsers like OpenAI's Atlas, posing significant data exfiltration risks. 🧠</p>

<p>⚖️ Beyond the technical, we discuss "LLM grooming" where popular chatbots cite Russian state-attributed sources, raising disinformation concerns. Hear about the severe human toll of the UK MoD's Afghan relocation scheme data breach and a civil rights lawsuit against the NYPD's Domain Awareness System. Finally, we cover the US declining the UN Cybercrime Convention and Noyb's criminal complaint against Clearview AI in Austria, leveraging GDPR for potential executive imprisonment.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:52:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_n-o5uI46HCSI1HreGTnKk4DBNTNU1dL" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761684745097</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Security Brief** 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks a busy 24 hours in cyber security, analysing 18 articles across seven key topics for technical analysts. We cover a flurry of active cyber events, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Highlights include the highly coordinated cyber theft of Shaquille O'Neal's Range Rover 🚗, the Jingle Thief group's cloud-targeting gift card fraud, and the F5 BIG-IP source code breach now suspected to have begun in late 2023 by Chinese state-sponsored actors. We cover data exposures at Iran's Ravin Academy and Sweden's power grid operator, Svenska kraftnät (claimed by Everest ransomware), plus a mass-exploitation campaign leveraging GutenKit and Hunk Companion plugins for WordPress RCE. Also, a former defence contractor exec faces charges for selling trade secrets to Russia.</p>

<p>Explore the latest in threat research and techniques: the Qilin ransomware group is escalating attacks with Linux variants on Windows, BYOVD exploits, and Veeam targeting. Kaspersky links Memento Labs (Hacking Team successor) to Operation ForumTroll, exploiting a Chrome zero-day (CVE-2025-2783) for "Dante" spyware. We detail Lazarus Group's "Operation Dream Job" targeting European defence, MuddyWater's Phoenix backdoor distribution, and the RedTiger tool's exploitation for data theft. Learn about new XWorm 6.0 features, Microsoft 365 Exchange Online Direct Send abuse, "CoPhish" OAuth token theft via Copilot Studio, and LockBit 5.0's multi-platform resurgence. Advanced phishing evasion techniques, including JavaScript-driven SEG bypasses and QR codes in PDFs, are also on our radar.</p>

<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: a Windows Server Update Service (WSUS) RCE (CVE-2025-59287) is under active exploitation, prompting an emergency patch. We detail "TARmageddon" (CVE-2025-62518) in the async-tar Rust library, allowing RCE and supply chain attacks, and a critical ASP.NET Core security bypass (CVE-2025-55315) in QNAP NetBak PC Agent. OpenAI's Atlas web browser is vulnerable to prompt injection via its omnibox, and multiple unpatched flaws in EfficientLab's WorkExaminer Professional allow unauthenticated administrative access.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:54:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1cZXrsnY8wp2tKi7N1dAYRzrdCCMCYfM0" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761598478303</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 26, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <strong>stdout</strong> delivers your daily deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments. Today, we unpack critical vulnerabilities and novel attack techniques impacting AI platforms, alongside significant regulatory discussions on mobile device security.</p>

<p>First, we analyse two potent threats targeting Microsoft Copilot. Discover the "<strong>Sneaky Mermaid</strong>" indirect prompt injection, a clever technique that exploited Mermaid diagram integration and CSS to exfiltrate sensitive tenant data by tricking users into clicking a fake login button. 🧜‍♀️ We also dissect '<strong>CoPhish</strong>', a new OAuth phishing method weaponising legitimate Copilot Studio agents to host malicious chatbots on trusted Microsoft domains, designed to trick users and administrators into granting extensive permissions. Datadog advises strong application consent policies and monitoring Copilot Studio agent creation events to mitigate this threat. 🎣</p>

<p>Then, we shift focus to the UK, where Members of Parliament are urging tech giants like Apple, Google, and Samsung to implement more robust technical measures against a surge in phone thefts. 📱 We examine proposals for cloud-based or IMEI-linked device locks to render stolen handsets useless for resale, and the industry's expressed concerns regarding privacy and security implications. 🔒</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15a4FJDaSGRqSgC5UpUV06eoqVuwbwMMv" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761425411993</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 25, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Get your daily dose of cyber intelligence with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 We unpack the last 24 hours of noteworthy developments for cyber security analysts.

This episode, we're tracking significant active threats: 🚨 A confirmed data breach at Toys R Us Canada exposed customer details. An L3Harris insider threat saw offensive cyber capabilities sold to Russia for $1.3M. Plus, Russia's agricultural agency was hit by a large-scale DDoS attack, disrupting food shipments.

Dive into sophisticated campaigns: 🎣 LastPass users face CryptoChameleon's advanced phishing, attempting to steal passkeys with fake death claims. ESET uncovers Lazarus Group's 'Operation DreamJob' targeting European <b>defence</b> firms with fake offers to deploy the ScoringMathTea RAT. Group-IB details Iranian MuddyWater's breach of 100+ gov/diplomatic entities using weaponised Word attachments and their 'Phoenix' backdoor. Plus, we explore Check Point's 'YouTube Ghost Network' distributing stealer malware, and Palo Alto's Unit 42 linking China-backed 'Smishing Triad' to over 194,000 malicious domains in a global credential theft operation.

On the vulnerability front: 💥 Microsoft has patched a critical WSUS RCE (CVE-2025-59287) actively exploited in the wild, with PoC code available. We also cover a patched Microsoft 365 Copilot prompt injection flaw, exploitable via Mermaid diagrams to exfiltrate tenant data. Pwn2Own Ireland 2025 saw over $1M awarded for 73 zero-days across various devices, highlighting ongoing risks. Plus, an HP OneAgent update issue disrupted Microsoft Entra ID authentication for Windows 11 AI PCs.

Finally, we examine the increasing focus of nation-state actors on exploiting forgotten perimeter devices, new Mozilla requirements for Firefox extension data disclosure, and the International Counter Ransomware Initiative's guidance on software supply chain resilience. Stay informed, stay secure!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1xFGCa3PIyGFeBBG47Xu8BF4Z9vefyVIi" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761339111792</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 24, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Intel: 24-Hour Cyber Snapshot</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats impacting organisations globally. SpaceX has disabled 2,500 Starlink terminals in Myanmar powering scam compounds, while US municipalities grapple with service disruptions. State-sponsored MuddyWater deployed Phoenix backdoor v4 against MENA governments, and North Korea's Lazarus Group executed "Operation DreamJob" targeting European defence firms with trojanised apps.</p>

<p>We unpack new techniques from "Jingle Thief" exploiting cloud environments for gift card fraud and "Smishing Triad's" massive Chinese-managed operation impersonating USPS and toll agencies. Google and Check Point also dismantled the "YouTube Ghost Network" distributing password-stealing malware via fake tutorials.</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities are under active exploitation: over 250 Magento stores were hit by <b>CVE-2025-54236 (SessionReaper)</b> allowing account takeover and RCE, and <b>CVE-2025-61932</b> in Motex Lanscope Endpoint Manager, enabling unauthenticated RCE, has been added to CISA's KEV catalogue. Plus, watch out for "AI Sidebar Spoofing" attacks on OpenAI Atlas and Perplexity Comet browsers. Microsoft has also disabled File Explorer's preview pane to block NTLM hash theft.</p>

<p>Stay informed on regulatory delays in the UK, updated third-party risk guidance from NYDFS (including AI provisions), and the growing adoption of managed identities to bolster security postures. Essential insights for every Cyber Security Analyst. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 20:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1z-kiKjVrh0EfHZIn0LdV2aqWhRJoL2kR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761252753546</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 23, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security! 🚨 We're tracking the £1.9 billion impact of the Jaguar Land Rover breach and active exploitation of the Microsoft SharePoint ToolShell zero-day (CVE-2025-53770) by Chinese-linked actors. Unpack the "PhantomCaptcha" spearphishing campaign targeting Ukrainian organisations with weaponised PDFs and WebSocket RATs. 🎣</p>
<p>New threats include the sophisticated PassiveNeuron APT using custom malware and the upgraded Vidar Stealer 2.0, now rewritten in C with advanced anti-analysis. 🕵️‍♂️</p>
<p>Stay ahead of critical vulnerabilities: TP-Link Omada gateways patched for unauthenticated RCEs (CVE-2025-6542), and Adobe Commerce faces active exploitation of SessionReaper (CVE-2025-54236). We also cover the "TARmageddon" logic flaw (CVE-2025-62518) in Rust's `async-tar` library and the massive 56 zero-day haul at Pwn2Own Ireland. 💥</p>
<p>Plus, GCHQ warns of the UK's "contested and complex" threat environment, highlighting a quadrupling of significant cyberattacks. Get the essential intel you need, daily. 🇦🇺</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:52:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1kAnBqDOpJr6sbFouKxzMrQUHZonsp9U4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761166351166</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Stay sharp with stdout's daily deep dive into the latest cyber threats! 🚨 We're tracking **active exploitation** of critical vulnerabilities, including a high-severity Microsoft Windows SMB client flaw (CVE-2025-33073) and an Oracle E-Business Suite SSRF (CVE-2025-61884). Discover "TARmageddon" (CVE-2025-62518), a critical RCE in the unmaintained `async-tar` Rust library, posing systemic risk to numerous forks like `tokio-tar` and `uv`. Plus, get the highlights from Pwn2Own Ireland 2025, where researchers chained 34 zero-days to compromise QNAP and Synology devices, and learn about the concerning n-day vulnerabilities exposing 1.8 million developers using AI-powered Cursor and Windsurf IDEs.

In threat actor intelligence, Google reports Russian state-backed COLDRIVER (Star Blizzard) has rapidly evolved its malware arsenal, deploying NOROBOT, YESROBOT, and MAYBEROBOT via "ClickFix" social engineering attacks. 🕵️‍♂️ We also analyse how China-nexus group Salt Typhoon breached a European telecommunications organisation, exploiting Citrix NetScaler Gateway and deploying Snappybee malware via DLL side-loading through legitimate antivirus software.

Beyond the front lines, Veeam has acquired Securiti AI for $1.725 billion, marking a significant entry into the AI security market, while Dataminr plans to acquire ThreatConnect for $290 million to enhance real-time threat intelligence. 💼 On the regulatory front, Russia has ordered Apple to make local search engines default on iPhones, and the U.S. Senate advanced a bill to combat foreign robocalls. Finally, the non-profit DNS0.EU service has announced its immediate shutdown due to sustainability issues. 📉]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:51:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1jI5Q6lIs-Iz4iTSIJJcCgPrwQc-babOx" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1761079894179</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. We're tracking critical active events, novel attack techniques, and newly exploited vulnerabilities.</p>

<p><b>Active Cyber Events & Breaches:</b> China accuses the US NSA of a multi-stage cyberattack on its National Time Service Centre, exploiting SMS flaws and deploying 42 tools. F5 confirms a nation-state breach by China-nexus group UNC5221, stealing BIG-IP source code and maintaining 12 months of access. Operation Zero Disco exploits a Cisco IOS SNMP stack overflow (CVE-2025-20352) to deploy Linux rootkits, while Flax Typhoon (Ethereal Panda) compromised an ArcGIS system for over a year. Japanese retailer Askul halted operations due to ransomware, impacting major retailers, and Verisure's Swedish subsidiary, Alert Alarm, suffered a data breach exposing 35,000 customer records.</p>

<p><b>New Threat Research & Techniques:</b> North Korean actors UNC5342 are using EtherHiding to conceal JADESNOW and InvisibleFerret malware within Binance Smart Chain smart contracts, distributed via job scams. A new GNU/Linux rootkit, LinkPro, was found in an AWS compromise, leveraging eBPF for stealth. Android devices face Pixnapping (CVE-2025-48561), a side-channel attack to steal 2FA codes and Google Maps timelines. We also cover SEO poisoning leading to fake Ivanti Pulse Secure VPN sites, Qilin ransomware's ties to bulletproof hosting, widespread Microsoft-branded phishing, and multi-country smishing campaigns targeting taxpayers and drivers. macOS users are targeted by social engineering via fake Homebrew/TradingView sites deploying stealer malware, alongside phishing impersonating 1Password and LastPass breach notifications. Plus, a deep dive into SocGholish (FakeUpdates) and a coordinated campaign of 131 WhatsApp Web automation tool clones for large-scale spamming.</p>

<p><b>Exploited Vulnerabilities:</b> CISA has added five critical flaws to its KEV Catalogue, confirming active exploitation. This includes CVE-2025-33073, a Windows SMB privilege escalation allowing SYSTEM privileges, and CVE-2025-61884, a server-side request forgery in Oracle E-Business Suite. Also, authentication bypasses in Kentico Xperience CMS (CVE-2025-2746, CVE-2025-2747) and an Apple JavaScriptCore RCE (CVE-2022-48503). Urgent patching is advised for nearly 76,000 publicly exposed WatchGuard Firebox appliances vulnerable to CVE-2025-9242, a critical 9.3 CVSS remote code execution flaw exploitable without authentication. CERT/CC also disclosed CVE-2025-8036, a CORS header vulnerability combined with DNS rebinding that can lead to data exfiltration.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:54:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1uUxmDAcFQL9_9fORh7iw3gAPP501mw2Z" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760993655430</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security, featuring:</p>
<ul>
    <li>🚨 <strong>Operation SIMCARTEL Disrupted:</strong> Europol spearheaded a major takedown of a sophisticated cybercrime-as-a-service platform. Authorities seized 1,200 SIM box devices and dismantled infrastructure that facilitated over 49 million fake accounts for widespread fraud, phishing, and more.</li>
    <li>📱 <strong>TikTok ClickFix Attacks & Aura Stealer:</strong> New threat research exposes cybercriminals leveraging TikTok videos to spread the Aura Stealer. Disguised as software activation guides, these attacks trick users into executing PowerShell commands, compromising browser credentials, cryptocurrency wallets, and other sensitive data.</li>
    <li>⚖️ <strong>Experian Netherlands Fined €2.7M for GDPR Breaches:</strong> A significant regulatory action sees Experian Netherlands penalised for illegally collecting and utilising personal data from various sources to generate credit scores without consent, leading to their exit from the country.</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:50:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1hqUEaFjJ7D2farNmlK-hOtfh1GVKPrZY" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760907011444</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 18, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily: Your 24-Hour Cyber Briefing!</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the latest cyber developments impacting analysts. Today, we unpack significant breaches including the <b>Prosper</b> incident affecting 17.6 million victims with sensitive PII, and the <b>Dairy Farmers of America</b> ransomware attack by the Play gang, exposing SSNs and bank details via sophisticated social engineering. Europol's "SIMCARTEL" operation dismantled a network responsible for $5.8 million in fraud, while <b>Envoy Air</b> confirmed a Clop extortion linked to a new Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882). Plus, suspected Iranian hackers reportedly accessed John Bolton's email.</p>

<p>Threat intelligence reveals North Korean operatives (Famous Chollima, UNC5342) deploying evasive techniques with new malware like BeaverTail and EtherHiding, the latter using public blockchains for C2. Microsoft has revoked over 200 fraudulent certificates used by Vanilla Tempest in Rhysida ransomware campaigns. On the vulnerability front, a critical out-of-bounds write in <b>WatchGuard Fireware OS</b> (CVE-2025-9242) allows unauthenticated RCE on IKEv2 VPNs. Over 266,000 <b>F5 BIG-IP</b> instances remain exposed post-breach, prompting CISA directives. Microsoft patched a high-severity HTTP request smuggling bug in <b>Kestrel ASP.NET Core</b> (CVE-2025-55315), and <b>ConnectWise Automate RMM</b> addressed critical flaws (CVE-2025-11492, CVE-2025-11493) enabling MITM and malicious updates.</p>

<p>We also look at the expanding attack surface from autonomous AI agents lacking identity security governance, as highlighted by SailPoint. Finally, legal battles unfold as US labor unions sue the Trump administration over a social media surveillance program, and the Computer & Communications Industry Association (CCIA) challenges Texas's new App Store Accountability Act, citing First Amendment and privacy concerns.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1bWXxv-sQScMVedO68tJ0an3Hn0uP8mlx" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760734333893</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout delivers the critical cybersecurity developments from the last 24 hours, tailored for cyber security analysts.

Catch up on major data breaches impacting Sotheby's and Prosper, exposing millions of sensitive records. 💸 We also detail Capita's £14 million fine for a Black Basta ransomware incident affecting 6.6 million, and Microsoft's disruption of Rhysida attacks using malvertising and fake Teams installers.

Explore cutting-edge threat techniques, including North Korea's UNC5342 group deploying 'EtherHiding' – crypto-stealing malware embedded in blockchain smart contracts for takedown resilience. ⛓️ We also examine China's 'Jewelbug' APT breaching a Russian IT provider in a rare East-on-East espionage operation, targeting potential software supply chain attacks.

Get the lowdown on actively exploited vulnerabilities: Cisco firewall flaws tied to the Chinese-backed ArcaneDoor campaign, a maximum-severity Adobe Experience Manager RCE (CVE-2025-54253) now in CISA's KEV, and a zero-day in Gladinet CentreStack (CVE-2025-11371) enabling RCE. 🚨 Also, learn about a high-severity request smuggling bug in ASP.NET Core Kestrel and the exploitation of Cisco IOS/IOS XE SNMP (CVE-2025-20352) to deploy a Linux rootkit in 'Operation Zero Disco'.

Beyond the technical exploits, we delve into broader threat landscape discussions: a proposed 'Secure Hosting Alliance Trust Seal' for web-hosting, Microsoft's report on a 32% surge in identity-based attacks, and a critical assessment of CVE/CVSS scoring systems. 📈 Plus, regulatory news covers a 19-year-old's sentencing for the PowerSchool hack, with $14.1 million in restitution ordered, and Cambodia's repatriation of South Korean nationals rescued from scam compounds. ⚖️]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:51:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1vp5wncC2ppGyMfMI670DN--ggYvPcj8B" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760647915086</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Unpacking a sophisticated <b>nation-state cyberattack on F5's BIG-IP</b> product development environment, which led to source code exfiltration and CISA's emergency directive ED 26-01. Patches have been released for 44 vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>Stay alert to <b>active exploitation</b> of a critical unauthenticated RCE (CVE-2025-2611, CVSS 9.3) in <b>ICTBroadcast autodialer software</b>. We also cover the UK ICO's hefty £14M fine against <b>Capita</b> for its 2023 breach, exposing 6.6 million records, and a new <b>phishing campaign targeting LastPass and Bitwarden users</b> with fake breach alerts to deploy remote access tools.</p>

<p>⚙️ Our research segment highlights new threats: malicious <b>VSCode extensions</b> from "TigerJack" stealing source code and executing RCE, plus over 550 leaked secrets found in other extensions. Discover how Chinese state-linked actor "<b>Jewelbug</b>" conducted espionage against a Russian IT provider, and why <b>synced passkeys</b> pose a significant enterprise security risk due to cloud account recovery flaws.</p>

<p>🔒 Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities: two CVSS 10.0 RCE flaws in <b>Red Lion Sixnet RTUs</b> impacting industrial control systems, SAP's patches including a critical NetWeaver AS Java deserialization RCE (CVE-2025-42944, CVSS 10.0), and Senator Cassidy's call for more details on severe <b>Cisco ASA vulnerabilities</b> that reportedly breached a federal agency.</p>

<p>⚖️ Plus, New York state fined eight car insurance companies $14.2M for data breaches affecting over 825,000 individuals, and a 19-year-old was sentenced for the <b>PowerSchool hack</b> exposing 70 million student and teacher records. We also touch on concerns regarding <b>CISA's workforce reductions</b> and the termination of its MS-ISAC agreement.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:52:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=10K_79ORPkNEPaPRBBMWm-9JhzzroQW_E" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760561564863</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 15, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>⚡️ <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> ⚡️</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of critical infosec developments. We're tracking active cyber events, new attack techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities impacting organisations globally. This episode covers significant breaches at <b>Asahi</b> and <b>Qantas</b>, plus Michigan City's ransomware woes. Don't miss the US/UK's coordinated sanctions and Bitcoin seizure targeting Cambodia's Prince Group, indicted for "pig butchering" scams and human trafficking. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>🔬 Our threat research deep dive reveals Chinese state-backed <b>Flax Typhoon's</b> year-long persistence on ArcGIS servers via weaponised SOEs and covert C2. We also unpack malicious packages across npm, PyPI, and RubyGems using Discord webhooks for data exfiltration, alongside North Korean "Contagious Interview" campaigns targeting Web3 developers with over 300 malicious npm packages. 🕵️‍♀️</p>

<p>🚨 Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities, including Microsoft's October 2025 Patch Tuesday with <b>six zero-days</b> – two actively exploited in Windows Agere Modem Driver (CVE-2025-24990) and Remote Access Connection Manager (CVE-2025-59230), both added to CISA's KEV catalog. Oracle issued an emergency patch for an actively exploited pre-auth SSRF in E-Business Suite (CVE-2025-61884), publicly leaked by ShinyHunters. Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT (CVE-2025-10035) is also under active exploitation by Storm-1175 for ransomware campaigns. 💥</p>

<p>We also cover Microsoft Edge's IE mode restrictions due to unpatched Chakra JavaScript engine zero-days, AMD's "RMPocalypse" fix (CVE-2025-0033) for critical EPYC processor flaws, and the Android "Pixnapping" side-channel attack (CVE-2025-48561) stealing sensitive data. Plus, a concerning UEFI shell 'memory modify' command found in 200,000 Linux Framework systems, enabling Secure Boot bypass. 💻</p>

<p>🌍 In broader threat landscape news, the UK's NCSC reports a record surge in "nationally significant" cyberattacks, while Taiwan faces a 17% increase in daily Chinese cyber intrusions targeting critical infrastructure, combined with information warfare. Florida's AG is suing Roku over alleged collection and sale of children's sensitive data. ⚖️</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on the evolving threat landscape driven by AI-generated malware, the need for Continuous Threat Exposure Management, Mozilla's new built-in Firefox VPN beta, and a public dispute between FuzzingLabs and Gecko Security over CVE credit attribution. Stay informed, stay secure! 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:53:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1c4YwdtfpKv_8HJ6NPtBX3yRYedO91OFP" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760475205941</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 14, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>'s daily intel! 🚀 This episode unpacks critical active threats: over 100 SonicWall SSLVPN accounts compromised via stolen credentials. The Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters group has leaked data from 6 million Qantas and 7.3 million Vietnam Airlines customers, alongside Gap and Fujifilm. 🏥 Medusa ransomware is behind a breach impacting 1.2 million SimonMed Imaging patients, and Clop ransomware exploited an Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) in a Harvard University incident.</p>

<p>Discover emerging TTPs and critical vulnerabilities. 🤖 We analyse ChaosBot, a new Rust-based backdoor leveraging Discord for C2, alongside a destructive Chaos-C++ ransomware variant. The Astaroth banking trojan now employs GitHub steganography for C2 resilience. 🚨 On the vulnerability front, Microsoft has restricted IE Mode in Edge due to active exploitation of unpatched IE Chakra JavaScript engine zero-days. Oracle released an emergency patch for CVE-2025-61884, an unauthenticated info disclosure flaw in E-Business Suite, following active exploitation of CVE-2025-61882 by Clop.</p>

<p>Beyond the headlines, we examine the expanding RondoDox botnet, weaponising over 50 vulnerabilities with an 'exploit shotgun' approach, and a 100,000+ IP botnet actively targeting RDP services in the US. ⚖️ Regulatory updates include Ofcom's first fine under the UK Online Safety Act and an Austrian DPA ruling against Microsoft 365 Education's data tracking. Plus, the Dutch government's intervention in Nexperia and Ukraine's steps towards a dedicated military Cyber Force.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 20:52:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15p1aG71MRKMvcm-yzyIEMXZpftacFtT7" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760388733482</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 13, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your 24-Hour Cyber Brief</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Get the essential intel for cyber security analysts. Today, we're dissecting critical vulnerabilities and active threat campaigns from the last 24 hours.</p>

<p>First, a deep dive into Oracle's E-Business Suite. Oracle has issued an urgent alert for <b>CVE-2025-61884</b> (CVSS 7.5), a high-severity flaw allowing unauthenticated, remote HTTP access to compromise Oracle Configurator. This vulnerability grants attackers unauthorised access to critical data across versions 12.2.3 through 12.2.14. We also revisit the recently exploited zero-day, <b>CVE-2025-61882</b>, leveraged by Cl0p-linked threat actors to deploy malware families including GOLDVEIN.JAVA, SAGEGIFT, SAGELEAF, and SAGEWAVE.</p>

<p>Next, we pivot to a pervasive smishing campaign targeting New Yorkers. Fraudulent text messages impersonating the Department of Taxation and Finance are luring recipients with fake "Inflation Refunds" to steal sensitive personal and financial data for identity theft and fraud. Official warnings confirm New York State's actual refund initiative is automatic, with agencies explicitly stating they will not contact taxpayers via text, phone, or email for these refunds.</p>

<p>Tune in for a concise summary of active cyber events, new techniques, and exploited vulnerabilities.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 20:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Vbh_E3C3rViyCm6k0kbbk7YBa2qct6hs" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760302191000</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 12, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Get the daily rundown on critical cyber security developments! Today, we're dissecting a widespread compromise impacting **SonicWall SSL VPN devices**, where threat actors are rapidly authenticating into over 100 accounts, potentially leveraging valid credentials and exploiting known flaws, including **CVE-2024-40766**, linked to Akira ransomware campaigns. We'll cover crucial mitigation advice for organisations.</p>

<p>🛠️ Next, we delve into new threat research revealing threat actors weaponising the open-source DFIR tool **Velociraptor** in ransomware attacks. The group Storm-2603 exploits **SharePoint vulnerabilities** for initial access, deploying an outdated Velociraptor version susceptible to **CVE-2025-6264** for privilege escalation and endpoint takeover. We detail their lateral movement tactics, including GPO modifications and disabling real-time protection.</p>

<p>⚖️ We also cover the legal fallout from the **PowerSchool breach**, where a 19-year-old faces a seven-year prison term for accessing 60 million student and 9 million teacher records and demanding a 30 Bitcoin ransom. Plus, significant leadership changes within **US Cyber Command and the NSA**, as President Trump opts not to nominate Army Lt. Gen. William Hartman.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 20:50:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1k8CGshTVQilWhXPGyKb7fshVOxmyxEwA" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760215848185</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 11, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Daily Cyber Briefing** 🚨</p>
<p>Your daily dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments! Unpacking critical incidents, we detail the Cl0p ransomware group's exploitation of an Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882), compromising dozens of organisations for RCE and data exfiltration. Explore the FBI and French authorities' takedown of BreachForums, operated by ShinyHunters and Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters, just before a threatened Salesforce data leak. Plus, we cover the significant data breach at UK trade union Prospect, exposing sensitive member data, and Microsoft's warning about the "payroll pirate" Storm-2657 group targeting US university payroll systems with sophisticated AiTM phishing.</p>

<p>🔬 **New Threats & Techniques:** Discover ClayRat, a new Android spyware mimicking popular apps and propagating via SMS, capable of extensive data theft and remote control. We also expose the "Beamglea" credential phishing campaign, leveraging 175 malicious npm packages as redirect infrastructure to harvest Microsoft credentials.</p>

<p>🍎 **Vulnerabilities & Updates:** Apple has dramatically expanded its bug bounty programme, now offering up to $2 million for zero-click RCEs. Stay informed on Windows 11 23H2 Home and Pro editions reaching end of servicing on November 11, 2025. We also touch on Google Chrome's new feature to automatically revoke notification permissions for inactive websites, the halted trial of officers accused of Baltic Sea cable damage, and the amusing tale of pro-Russian hacktivists TwoNet falling for a Forescout honeypot.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:52:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A77AethkFcSdI4zkJyR88eYJKh61JXmG" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760129539362</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 10, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout Daily Briefing:</b> Your essential 24-hour cyber security update! 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks critical active threats and exploited vulnerabilities. We dive into the widespread <b>SonicWall cloud backup breach</b>, confirming all customers had firewall configuration files accessed via brute-force. Plus, <b>Discord clarifies its third-party incident</b>, revealing 70,000 government IDs exposed through a compromised Zendesk agent. 🛡️</p>

<p>Catch up on the relentless <b>Clop ransomware group</b>, actively exploiting a zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) in Oracle E-Business Suite, chaining multiple vulnerabilities for pre-authenticated RCE. Discover how "Payroll Pirates" (Storm-2657) are targeting US universities and other organisations, using phishing to divert salaries via compromised HR platforms. We also explore Russian hackers' increasing use of <b>AI in cyberattacks</b> against Ukraine, from phishing to advanced malware like WRECKSTEEL. 💸</p>

<p>Further analysis covers the new <b>RondoDox botnet's "exploit shotgun" approach</b> against 56 n-day vulnerabilities, and how China-based Storm-2603 is weaponising the Velociraptor DFIR tool in LockBit and Babuk ransomware attacks. Understand why <b>token theft is a primary cause of SaaS breaches</b>, often bypassing MFA, and the evolving threat from pro-Russian hacktivist group TwoNet, now targeting critical infrastructure with old XSS exploits. Finally, a critical authentication bypass (CVE-2025-5947) in the <b>Service Finder WordPress theme</b> is under active exploitation, granting unauthenticated admin access. 💥</p>

<p>Stay informed on the proposed PACT Act, aiming to extend vital cyber threat information sharing protections. Get the facts, fast. 🚀</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:52:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ERPUDjBSc0vBGgDTRhisSPQZABqFrzZM" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1760043175852</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 9, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Salesforce refused a ransom from "Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters" for data stolen via social engineering and compromised OAuth tokens. Qilin ransomware hit Japanese giant Asahi, while UK police arrested suspects over the Kido nursery doxing. A US law firm reported a China-linked zero-day breach targeting attorney emails for national security intelligence.</p>
<p>🔬 New threat research highlights OpenAI disrupting Russian, North Korean, and Chinese actors misusing ChatGPT for malware and phishing. Ukraine's CERT-UA details Russian AI-driven attacks and "Steal & Go" tactics, including exploitation of Roundcube's CVE-2023-43770. China-linked actors used Nezha, Ghost RAT, and AntSword in politically motivated espionage across Asia, and the "Crimson Collective" targeted AWS cloud environments for data theft and extortion. A new FileFix variant employs cache smuggling to deliver malicious ZIPs.</p>
<p>💥 Critical vulnerabilities in focus include a severe command injection (CVE-2025-53967) in <code>figma-developer-mcp</code> allowing RCE, now patched. Active exploitation of CVE-2025-5947, a critical authentication bypass in the Service Finder WordPress theme, enabled unauthenticated admin logins with over 13,800 attempts recorded.</p>
<p>🌐 Broader developments cover Ursula Von der Leyen's warning on Russia's "hybrid warfare" against Europe, Germany's opposition to the EU's "Chat Control" legislation, and Docker's new unlimited access to Hardened Images for startups and SMBs, offering secure software bundles with near-zero CVEs.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 20:52:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ly46MAmDPC0Aa2H8f93hT5L9wcVbFA9a" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759956732462</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 8, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Catch up on the latest cyber incidents impacting global giants and sensitive data. 🚨 **Jaguar Land Rover** faces a "cyber shockwave" post-attack, while **Doctors Imaging Group** discloses a year-late breach affecting 171,000+ patients. **Discord** users' sensitive info was exposed via a third-party, and **Avnet** confirms a data breach with claims of 1.3TB exfiltrated. The **Red Hat** breach escalates with ShinyHunters joining extortion efforts, leaking customer network details. Plus, **DraftKings** battles credential stuffing attacks.

On the vulnerability front, the notorious **Clop ransomware group** has been actively exploiting a critical zero-day, `CVE-2025-61882`, in **Oracle E-Business Suite** since August 2025. 💥 This RCE flaw (CVSS 9.8) allowed unauthenticated attackers to gain control, leading to massive data theft and reported $50M extortion demands. Oracle has patched, and CISA has added it to their Known Exploited Vulnerabilities catalogue.

New threat research reveals the evolution of **XWorm malware** to version 6.0, now packed with 35+ plugins for extensive data theft and ransomware capabilities. 🐛 Meanwhile, **North Korean hackers (Lazarus Group)** set a new record, stealing over $2 billion in cryptocurrency in 2025, primarily funding nuclear weapons development and shifting tactics from DeFi exploits to social engineering.

The impact of AI on cybersecurity is rapidly expanding. 🤖 A LayerX report highlights **AI tools as the leading uncontrolled channel for corporate data exfiltration**, with 77% of employees copy-pasting sensitive data into unmanaged GenAI accounts. OpenAI's latest report confirms threat actors are leveraging AI to *enhance existing hacking methods* – from malware development to spearphishing – rather than creating entirely new ones.

In regulatory news, **Russia implements a mandatory 24-hour mobile internet blackout** for foreign SIM cards upon entry, citing national security. 🇷🇺 On a brighter note, **Google launches a dedicated AI Vulnerability Reward Program**, offering up to $30,000 for critical flaws in its AI systems. However, Google has controversially stated it will *not* fix **ASCII smuggling attacks in Gemini**, dismissing the LLM manipulation as a social engineering issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:51:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1el9x9qtjTd7DawPVY7rtIiyzva7kXRiG" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759870311700</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, October 7, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>Critical Exploits & Breaches Unpacked:</b> Dive into the latest active cyber events, including Clop ransomware's exploitation of a new Oracle E-Business Suite zero-day (CVE-2025-61882) for unauthenticated RCE, with public exploit code now available. We also cover Medusa ransomware (Storm-1175) leveraging a Fortra GoAnywhere MFT deserialisation flaw (CVE-2025-10035), and a Zimbra Collaboration zero-day (CVE-2025-27915) used against the Brazilian military. Immediate patching is crucial as agencies worldwide issue urgent warnings. 🛡️</p>

<p>💥 <b>Major Incidents & Campaigns:</b> Get the lowdown on the Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' crowdsourced extortion scheme and their OAuth token abuse impacting Zscaler. We analyse Discord's data breach via a compromised third-party vendor, the significant production halt at Jaguar Land Rover due to a cyberattack, and a suspected China-linked cyber-espionage campaign targeting European institutions. Plus, a leaked report suggests FEMA's CISO and CIO were fired following a June breach. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>🔬 <b>New Threats & Vulnerabilities:</b> Explore the resurgence of the XWorm backdoor, now featuring a ransomware module and extensive plugins. We detail "RediShell" (CVE-2025-49844), a 13-year-old use-after-free vulnerability in Redis allowing authenticated RCE, and a critical flaw (CVE-2025-59489) in the Unity game engine affecting multiple platforms. Also, a significant surge in scanning attacks targeting Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect portals has been observed. 💻</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Industry & Regulatory Watch:</b> Stay informed on the European Commission's controversial "Chat Control" proposals, with Signal threatening to exit the EU market if passed. LinkedIn is suing ProAPIs Inc. for alleged data scraping, while House Democrats question DHS over an ICE contract with Israeli spyware company Paragon Solutions. We also cover Georgia Tech's $875K settlement for cybersecurity failures, Wiz's $4.5M "Zeroday Cloud" hacking competition, and China's severe crackdown on cybercrime. ⚖️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:52:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1sHSH-3U5dSbN_UYv88PRhQKRXoVboCdR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759783957431</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, October 6, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Security Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Stay ahead of the curve with today's critical cyber developments. We're diving deep into an actively exploited zero-day vulnerability, <b>CVE-2025-27915</b>, impacting Zimbra Collaboration Suite versions 9.0, 10.0, and 10.1. Discover how malicious iCalendar files 🗓️ delivered sophisticated JavaScript payloads to steal credentials, emails, and sensitive data from a Brazilian military organisation, leveraging the Zimbra SOAP API for exfiltration and mail forwarding. Learn about the TTPs linked to UNC1151 and the urgent patches released on January 27th. ✅</p>
<p>Then, we'll unpack the resolution of ParkMobile's 2021 data breach class action lawsuit. Understand the $32.8 million settlement, the $1 in-app credit compensation for 22 million affected users, and the extensive data types exposed. Plus, get the latest on ParkMobile's current warnings regarding ongoing SMS phishing (smishing) attacks 📱 targeting their customer base. Stay informed, stay secure. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 20:50:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=17f9SvRYx3J2qNRoqUPvKdkNXZ6rH8ilp" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759697405674</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, October 5, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>stdout: Daily InfoSec Briefing</h3>

Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 Your daily deep dive into the latest in cybersecurity.

This episode unpacks a significant <b>Discord data breach</b> affecting PII, government IDs, and partial billing information, stemming from a compromised third-party provider. Understand the financial motivations and the critical implications for identity theft and crypto scams. 🕵️‍♂️

Next, we dissect "<b>CometJacking</b>," a novel prompt injection technique targeting Perplexity's agentic AI browser, Comet. Discover how malicious URLs can siphon sensitive data from connected services like email and calendar, bypassing traditional protections through trivial Base64 encoding. Learn why researchers are flagging new AI-native security risks, despite vendor claims of "no security impact." 🤖

Finally, we examine a nearly 500% surge in scanning activity targeting <b>Palo Alto Networks login portals</b>. GreyNoise reports this mirrors pre-CVE disclosure patterns seen with recent Cisco ASA zero-days, urging organisations to ensure their software is running the latest versions. Don't get caught out! 🚨]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 20:50:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1oyvQ0L4wZvzmB34psxKxAqRkYRP0Pqj1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759611003220</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, October 4, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>🚨 Cyber Alert: stdout Daily Briefing 🚨</h3>
<p>Tracking significant active threats and breaches impacting global organisations over the last 24 hours.</p>
<p>The notorious <b>ShinyHunters</b> group, also known as "Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters," has launched a data leak site, claiming 1 billion records from 39 companies (including FedEx and Google) via Salesforce breaches, demanding a ransom. Meanwhile, a group linked to <b>Clop ransomware</b> is extorting Oracle E-Business Suite customers, exploiting critical RCE flaws and bypassing SSO/MFA. <b>Red Hat</b> confirms a breach of its consulting GitLab by "Crimson Collective," exposing architectural diagrams and authentication tokens. Japanese giant <b>Asahi Group Holdings</b> suffered a ransomware attack, and <b>Renault/Dacia UK</b> customers were impacted by a third-party data breach. The US Courts also detail ongoing upgrades following a major breach.</p>
<p>Uncover new threat intelligence: Meet <b>"Cavalry Werewolf,"</b> a new actor targeting Russian sectors with FoalShell and StallionRAT via phishing. The <b>Rhadamanthys info stealer</b> evolves with advanced fingerprinting and steganography for payload concealment. Researchers expose <b>"CommetJacking,"</b> a prompt-injection attack on Perplexity's Comet AI browser that exfiltrates sensitive data. Plus, insights into "PRISONBREAK," an Israeli-backed network using AI deepfakes for propaganda in Iran.</p>
<p>Stay informed on critical vulnerabilities, privacy shifts, and security innovations. Oracle urges patching for E-Business Suite RCEs, while Perplexity downplays its AI browser prompt injection. We also cover privacy concerns around <b>Flock Safety's "Raven"</b> gunshot detection, the UK's proposed digital ID, and the US Courts' response to their major breach. Finally, explore <b>Signal's new SPQR</b> for quantum resistance and <b>Google Workspace's end-to-end encryption</b> rollout for enterprise users.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:52:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1bSRLJTZ1WJwWaTHq3OpGSoxBK4lv82-g" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759528359247</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, October 3, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Intel Briefing** 🚨</p>

<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cyber security developments. We unpack major active events, including the alleged <b>Crimson Collective breach of Red Hat's GitHub</b>, impacting customer IT blueprints and authentication tokens. Hear about the suspected ransomware attack disrupting <b>Asahi Group Holdings'</b> operations in Japan, and the social engineering incident that froze <b>Kodex Global's</b> domain. Plus, we cover the high-volume email extortion campaign targeting <b>Oracle E-Business Suite</b> customers by Clop-linked actors, and significant data breaches at <b>Allianz Life Insurance</b> (linked to Scattered Spider) and <b>Motility</b> (Pear ransomware).</p>

<p>🔎 On the vulnerability front, get the lowdown on <b>DrayTek's critical RCE flaw (CVE-2025-10547)</b> affecting Vigor routers, allowing unauthenticated remote code execution. ESET reveals two new Android spyware campaigns, <b>ProSpy and ToSpy</b>, actively targeting UAE users via fake messaging apps. We also highlight a massive <b>540% surge in AI vulnerabilities</b>, particularly prompt injection, reported by HackerOne.</p>

<p>🌍 Beyond the exploits, we examine the expanding global reach of <b>North Korean IT worker schemes</b>, now targeting diverse industries. Stay informed on regulatory shifts as a Dutch court rules against <b>Meta's profiled feeds</b> under the EU Digital Services Act, and EU Parliament members question the funding of commercial spyware. Finally, we cover <b>Georgia Tech's $875K settlement</b> for lax cybersecurity on federal research projects and Microsoft's move to discontinue inline SVG images in Outlook for enhanced security. </p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:36:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1FYyGbRqK2MWgjrbEEcJcSg0zIZMMeWi6" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469803523</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, October 2, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with <b>stdout</b>! We're tracking significant breaches affecting millions, including <b>WestJet</b>, <b>Allianz Life</b>, and <b>Motility Software Solutions</b>, alongside a potential <b>US Air Force</b> SharePoint incident. Plus, discover how threat actors are exploiting <b>Milesight industrial routers</b> for phishing campaigns across Europe. 🚨</p>

<p>Unpack new, sophisticated threats: meet <b>Phantom Taurus</b>, a China-linked espionage group using the stealthy NET-STAR malware, and dissect new Android banking Trojans like <b>Klopatra</b> and <b>Datzbro</b> targeting seniors. We also cover North Korean IT workers expanding their fraudulent job applications and the <b>CABINETRAT</b> backdoor used in targeted attacks in Ukraine. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Get the lowdown on critical vulnerabilities, including a <b>Red Hat OpenShift AI</b> flaw (CVSS 9.9) allowing full cluster admin escalation, and the "WireTap" physical attack bypassing <b>Intel SGX</b> security. Our analysis also highlights the rise of Living Off the Land techniques in high-severity attacks and the ongoing pressure on security professionals to keep breaches confidential. 💥</p>

<p>Finally, we examine data privacy concerns with <b>Tile Bluetooth trackers</b> leaking identifying data and an <b>Adobe Analytics</b> bug exposing customer tracking. Stay informed on regulatory shifts like Google's upcoming Android developer ID verification impacting F-Droid, Imgur's UK exit, and the White House's push for quantum-resistant encryption. Plus, Google Drive rolls out new AI-powered ransomware detection. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:29:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=14eQPkiL_-Or3h_2cyAIJo_qgVG5lxIfJ" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469375144</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, October 1, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Debrief!</b> 🚨</p>

<p>Dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security with <b>stdout</b>. We're unpacking critical vulnerabilities under active exploitation, major breaches, and evolving threat tradecraft.</p>

<p>This episode, we analyse critical vulnerabilities under active exploitation: widespread attacks on <b>Cisco ASA/FTD</b> (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362) deploying 'Line Viper' and 'RayInitiator' bootkits, and urgent CISA directives for patching critical flaws in <b>Fortra GoAnywhere MFT</b> (CVE-2025-10035) and <b>Sudo</b> (CVE-2025-32463) for privilege escalation. We also cover a <b>VMware zero-day</b> (CVE-2025-41244) actively exploited by Chinese state-sponsored UNC5174, alongside other critical VMware patches and CISA KEV additions. 🛠️</p>

<p>In breach news, UK authorities secure a landmark conviction in a <b>£5.5 billion Bitcoin fraud</b>, <b>WestJet</b> confirms a customer data breach, and <b>Asahi</b> reports system disruptions. INTERPOL's "Contender 3.0" operation nets 260 arrests targeting romance scams and sextortion. 💰</p>

<p>Explore new threat tradecraft with the <b>MatrixPDF toolkit</b> creating interactive phishing lures, and uncover North Korea's expanding illicit IT worker scheme. We also dissect the "Gemini Trifecta" – three high-severity vulnerabilities in <b>Google's Gemini AI</b>. 🤖</p>

<p>Plus, we cover the EU's <b>Cyber Resilience Act</b> clarifications, CISA's funding cuts to the Center for Internet Security, and the impending expiration of key US cybersecurity legislation. Data privacy takes centre stage with FTC action against the <b>Sendit app</b>, a $1.35M fine for <b>Tractor Supply Co.</b>, and the UK's push for nationwide <b>Live Facial Recognition</b>. Finally, Google rolls out AI ransomware detection for Drive, and Afghanistan faces a nationwide internet blackout. 🌍</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 05:23:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1_ACKjFSWlTnfBnzokyMcj_jcTE0-bmSk" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759469014844</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 30, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 Dive into the last 24 hours of critical cyber developments! 🚨 We're unpacking major breaches, including <b>Harrods' 430,000 customer records</b> exposed via a third-party supplier, and <b>Jaguar Land Rover's £1.5 billion recovery loan</b> after a production-halting cyberattack. Discover how a federal agency was compromised by an <b>unpatched GeoServer vulnerability</b>, Cloudflare mitigated a <b>record-breaking 22.2 Tbps DDoS attack</b>, and ransomware groups are actively exploiting <b>stolen AWS keys</b> to exfiltrate data. Plus, we cover the impact of a <b>data centre fire in South Korea</b> and cyberattacks marring <b>Moldova's elections</b>.</p>

<p>🛠️ Uncover the latest threat intelligence and new techniques: China-linked <b>ArcaneDoor exploited two Cisco firewall zero-days</b> (CVE-2025-20362, CVE-2025-20333) with novel malware, while Iran-linked <b>Nimbus Manticore expanded critical infrastructure targeting</b> using evolving malware and signed code. We detail aggressive <b>Akira ransomware campaigns</b> hitting MFA-protected SonicWall VPNs, the "significantly more dangerous" <b>LockBit 5.0</b>, and the alarming npm supply chain risk from the "postmark-mcp" package silently stealing emails.</p>

<p>⚠️ We also highlight critical vulnerabilities in <b>Supermicro BMCs</b> and the Streamlit framework. Hear about the Medusa ransomware gang's audacious attempt to recruit a BBC journalist as an insider threat, and the broader implications of geopolitical cyber tensions, including alleged Russian espionage. Stay ahead with the essential facts and takeaways from the frontline of information security. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:55:45 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Jsbr6jGmOTUH6ejGTKDLB_Smw6NsqTDU" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759182945602</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, September 29, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 In this edition of stdout, we dive deep into the latest <b>Akira ransomware</b> activity. Threat actors are actively exploiting <b>SonicWall SSL VPN devices</b>, leveraging an improper access control flaw (<b>CVE-2024-40766</b>) to gain initial access.</p>

<p>🔒 Discover how attackers are bypassing <b>one-time password multi-factor authentication (OTP MFA)</b> by utilising previously stolen credentials and OTP seeds, allowing persistent access even after patches. We unpack their post-exploitation tactics, including rapid internal network scanning, Impacket SMB/RDP usage, Active Directory enumeration, and targeting <b>Veeam Backup & Replication servers</b> to extract sensitive MSSQL and PostgreSQL credentials.</p>

<p>⚙️ Learn about their sophisticated evasion techniques, specifically <b>Bring-Your-Own-Vulnerable-Driver (BYOVD) attacks</b>. They're abusing Microsoft's <code>consent.exe</code> to sideload malicious DLLs, loading vulnerable drivers to effectively disable endpoint protection.</p>

<p>⚠️ <b>Critical takeaway:</b> Administrators are strongly advised to reset <b>all VPN credentials</b> on any device that previously utilised vulnerable firmware, as stolen accounts can still grant initial access.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:49:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1EiwHy8KK1GB4ByKW0i1691b0EQDW6Kr9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759096178496</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, September 28, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **Critical Threat Briefing: stdout Daily** 🚨</p>
<p>Dive deep into the latest cyber security developments. Today, we're tracking a year-long Chinese state-sponsored espionage campaign, <b>RedNovember</b> (TAG-100/Storm-2077), actively exploiting critical vulnerabilities in internet-facing appliances including Ivanti Connect Secure, Cisco ASA, FortiGate, and Palo Alto GlobalProtect VPNs. Discover their use of the Go-based <b>Pantegana</b> backdoor, Cobalt Strike, and SparkRAT. Plus, CISA and Cisco warn of ongoing <b>ArcaneDoor</b> activity targeting Cisco ASA/FTD firewalls with ROM modifications for persistence. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>Further Chinese-linked threats emerge with a new <b>PlugX</b> variant (Korplug/SOGU) targeting Asian telecommunications and manufacturing, leveraging DLL side-loading. We also cover Mustang Panda's continued use of the advanced <b>Bookworm</b> RAT against ASEAN networks. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>On the malware front, a new malvertising campaign is pushing the <b>Oyster backdoor</b> via fake Microsoft Teams installers. Learn how SEO poisoning, fraudulent certificates, and scheduled tasks are establishing persistence and remote access in corporate networks. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the concerning trend of minors being recruited for intelligence gathering, following Dutch arrests related to attempts to spy on Europol for Russia. We also touch on Alibaba's ambitious $53 billion global AI infrastructure plan and the geopolitical hurdles it faces, including Nvidia GPU access and data sovereignty concerns for new AI datacentres. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:51:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1qQDAwvXI1OIgPB5_3Yb0PcE5ad4x5w0g" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1759009861519</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, September 27, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>&#x1F514; Dive into the latest cyber developments with stdout! 🇦🇺 This episode unpacks significant breaches, including **Volvo North America's** employee data theft via a ransomware attack on its HR provider, impacting 1.5 million individuals. 🚨 We also cover **Salesforce** facing lawsuits over customer data exposure from stolen OAuth tokens, and **Union County, Ohio's** ransomware incident compromising sensitive resident data. Plus, hear about two 17-year-olds arrested in the Netherlands for alleged pro-Russian cyber espionage.</p>

<p>&#x1F4BB; Uncover critical new threat research: **Microsoft Threat Intelligence** details an updated, highly obfuscated **macOS XCSSET** variant with enhanced browser targeting and crypto clipboard hijacking. **Trend Micro** warns of **LockBit 5.0**, a "significantly more dangerous" ransomware strain simultaneously targeting Windows, Linux, and VMware ESXi environments. 💥 We also break down the "ForcedLeak" attack against **Salesforce's Agentforce AI**, exploiting a DNS misconfiguration for indirect prompt injection and sensitive data exfiltration.</p>

<p>&#x26A0;&#xFE0F; Crucially, we delve into actively exploited zero-day vulnerabilities. **Fortra's GoAnywhere MFT** (CVE-2025-10035) saw unauthenticated command injection exploited a week before public disclosure, leading to RCE and backdoor accounts. UK and US agencies have issued urgent directives for **Cisco ASA/FTD** zero-days (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362), chained for remote control by the state-sponsored **ArcaneDoor campaign** (UAT4356). Discover the sophisticated **RayInitiator** and **LINE VIPER** malware families deployed for persistence and evasion.</p>

<p>&#x2696;&#xFE0F; Stay informed on regulatory shifts: the **US Cybersecurity Information Sharing Act of 2015** faces expiration, and President Trump has approved a plan to restructure **TikTok's US operations** to address national security concerns. Finally, we touch on the **UK ICO's** hefty fines for illegal automated marketing calls, **Interpol's** major cybercrime crackdown in Africa, and **Microsoft Edge's** upcoming feature to revoke malicious sideloaded extensions. 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:52:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1TLnc4vCjXvkm0Sg3K9jgiTIpc464LHc4" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758923523382</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, September 26, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p><b>stdout: Daily Cyber Security Briefing</b> 🚀</p>
<p>stdout delivers your essential daily update for Cyber Security Analysts, diving deep into the last 24 hours of noteworthy developments, focusing on active threats, new techniques, and critical vulnerabilities.</p>

<p>🚨 <b>Active Breaches & Attacks:</b> Kido International suffered a ransomware attack by the Radiant Group, leaking sensitive children's data. The Co-operative Group (UK) reports an £80M profit loss from a Scattered Spider attack that stole 6.5 million member records. A US federal agency was compromised via a GeoServer RCE (CVE-2024-36401), leading to web shells and lateral movement. Plus, an arrest linked to the "incredibly basic" HardBit ransomware affecting European airports.</p>

<p>🛠️ <b>Emerging Threats & Techniques:</b> North Korean groups are escalating malware capabilities with AkdoorTea, TsunamiKit, and Tropidoor, targeting crypto developers. Supply chain attacks are rampant: Shai-Hulud worm infected 500+ npm packages, malicious Rust packages stole crypto keys, and an unofficial npm package exfiltrated emails. Learn about AsyncRAT via ScreenConnect, StealC from game patches, Elons ransomware on Oracle DBS, and Android BankBot. Plus, new insights into LNK Stomping and the decade-old BiDi Swap URL spoofing vulnerability.</p>

<p>🩹 <b>Critical Vulnerabilities & Patches:</b> Cisco issues urgent warnings and patches for actively exploited zero-days (CVE-2025-20333, CVE-2025-20362) in ASA/FTD, with a CISA emergency directive. Salesforce patched a critical "ForcedLeak" flaw (CVSS 9.4) in Agentforce AI, allowing CRM data exfiltration. OnePlus OxygenOS has a permission bypass (CVE-2025-10184) for SMS/MMS data, and SonicWall is expediting EOL for SMA 100 devices after rootkit malware discoveries.</p>

<p>🌐 <b>Threat Landscape & Geopolitics:</b> Discussions on "AI security" vs. "AI safety" and how AI coding assistants increase security findings. Russian state-backed Storm-1679 targets Moldovan elections with disinformation, and PyPI warns of ongoing phishing attacks. Also, updates on data privacy (Google/Flo, TikTok Canada), the EU's new Entry/Exit System, and law enforcement successes against dark web markets and financial crime.</p>

<p>💡 <b>CTEM Insights:</b> An overview of Continuous Threat Exposure Management, emphasising prioritisation based on business impact and validation through breach and attack simulation.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:54:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1UXaff5Dr3bvzVzOsg2vcCoXIBZen9d5A" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758837259619</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, September 25, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 **stdout: Your Daily Cyber Dive!** 🚨</p>

<p>This episode unpacks the last 24 hours in infosec, from major arrests to critical exploits. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>Catch up on the UK arrest linked to the **Collins Aerospace MUSE ransomware attack** impacting European airports, and Boyd Gaming's employee data breach. A 19-year-old has been apprehended as a core figure in the notorious **Scattered Spider** group, linked to 120 attacks and $89.5M in crypto. Interpol's Operation HAECHI VI seized over $439M from cyber-enabled financial crimes. 💰</p>

<p>New threats include sophisticated **phishing campaigns** targeting Python developers via fake PyPI sites and abusing GitHub notifications to drain crypto wallets. Dive into detailed research on "Brickstorm" (UNC5221), a long-running Chinese cyberespionage campaign targeting legal, SaaS, and tech for IP theft and zero-day development, maintaining persistence for 400 days. Also, discover "RedNovember" (Storm-2077), another Chinese state-sponsored actor exploiting perimeter appliance vulnerabilities from Ivanti, Cisco, and Fortinet. 🇨🇳</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities are under active exploitation: a high-severity **Cisco IOS/IOS XE zero-day (CVE-2025-20352)** allowing RCE, and a command injection flaw in **Libraesva Email Security Gateway (CVE-2025-59689)** exploited by state-sponsored actors. We also discuss in-the-wild exploitation of a **Pandoc SSRF (CVE-2025-51591)** targeting AWS IMDS, new **Supermicro BMC firmware vulnerabilities** allowing persistent control, and an unpatched **OnePlus OxygenOS flaw (CVE-2025-10184)** exposing SMS data. 💥</p>

<p>Finally, we examine the broader impact of cyberattacks, including the **Jaguar Land Rover production halt** and the catastrophic collapse of KNP Logistics Group due to an Akira ransomware attack exploiting a single weak password. Plus, a quick look at the new Kali Linux 2025.3 release. Stay informed, stay secure! 🛡️</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1DVy51Og5djBi1_yx6l2K62ni8MFty-5f" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758750799224</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, September 24, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stay ahead with <b>stdout</b>! 🚀 Your daily deep dive into the last 24 hours of cyber security. Today, we're analysing a record-breaking 22.2 Tbps DDoS attack, a US federal agency breach via unpatched GeoServer RCE (CVE-2024-36401), and major disruptions impacting Jaguar Land Rover, Circle K, and Lotte Card's 3 million customers.</p>

<p>🔍 Discover new threats: Iran-backed Nimbus Manticore's novel DLL loading for MiniJunk/MiniBrowse, RevengeHotels leveraging AI-generated VenomRAT, and "Operation Rewrite" using BadIIS for SEO poisoning. Plus, a malicious npm package 'fezbox' employing steganographic QR codes to steal browser cookies.</p>

<p>🩹 Critical vulnerabilities and patches: SolarWinds' third hotfix for a Web Help Desk RCE patch bypass (CVE-2025-26399), SonicWall's update to remove the OVERSTEP rootkit, and an emergency fix for Libraesva's Email Security Gateway (CVE-2025-59689) actively exploited by a suspected state entity. Rapid7 also disclosed an unpatched critical SQL injection in OnePlus OxygenOS (CVE-2025-10184) allowing SMS/MMS data access.</p>

<p>💡 Broader insights include 62% of cyber leaders reporting AI-driven attacks, the link between REST Media and Russia's Rybar disinformation, and GitHub's new mandatory 2FA and granular tokens for npm security. We also touch on the unsustainable model of open source infrastructure and the complexities of North Korean IT worker sanctions compliance.</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:52:40 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Mj6Ihsr9xWRlykEv8X_JGvXqECmjCDMF" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758664360136</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 23, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<h3>Daily stdout: Cyber Events, Exploits & Techniques</h3>
<p>Your daily deep dive into the latest in cybersecurity! 🚀 Today, we're unpacking significant disruptions, from European aviation chaos caused by a Collins Aerospace ransomware attack to Dallas Fort Worth International Airport's fibre optic woes. Catch up on the latest arrests linked to the 2023 Scattered Spider attacks on MGM and Caesars, costing over $100 million. 💸 Plus, Stellantis confirms a data leak via a compromised Salesforce provider, with ShinyHunters claiming 18 million records. Even France's Natural History Museum wasn't safe, losing gold nuggets after a ransomware attack disabled security. 🏛️ And a verified Steam game, 'BlockBlasters,' turned malicious, siphoning $150,000 from 261 accounts with a cryptodrainer.</p>

<p>Dive into cutting-edge threat research, including 'EDR-Freeze,' a novel user-mode technique that can indefinitely suspend EDR and antivirus processes without a kernel driver. 🥶 We also analyse new campaigns: ComicForm targeting Eurasian sectors with Formbook, and the pro-Russian SectorJ149 (UAC-0050) deploying Lumma Stealer, Formbook, and Remcos RAT against South Korean industries. 🕵️‍♂️ LastPass warns macOS users about fake software impersonating password managers, delivering the Atomic (AMOS) info-stealer, now with a backdoor component.</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Microsoft patched a critical CVE-2025-55241 in Entra ID (CVSS 10.0), allowing global administrator impersonation. 🚨 The American Archive of Public Broadcasting also fixed an Insecure Direct Object Reference (IDOR) flaw that exposed private media for years. In the broader threat landscape, AT&T highlights Chinese Salt Typhoon's influence on 'living off the land' techniques, while the FBI warns of spoofed IC3 websites. 🌐 Lloyds Banking Group's AI implementation shows the tightrope walk between innovation and security, blocking platforms like Hugging Face.</p>

<p>Data privacy takes centre stage with patients advocating for stronger neural data rights as scientists decode inner speech from Brain Computer Interface (BCI) implants. 🧠 Regulatory hurdles loom as CISA 2015 faces expiration, potentially increasing cyber risk, and Senator Tom Cotton proposes an 18-month 'clean' reauthorization of FISA Section 702 amidst privacy concerns.</p>

<p>Finally, the US government mandates a transition to NIST's new post-quantum cryptography standards by 2030/2035 to counter 'harvest now, decrypt later' threats. 🔒 ICE HSI has acquired Magnet Forensics' Graykey software for device unlocking. Plus, Mozilla introduces a new Firefox feature allowing add-on developers to roll back to previous approved versions for quicker bug fixes. 🦊</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 02:35:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=195cnruZ0RndtX63l587pXN63yLhHjmZa" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758594958815</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, September 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 On this episode of stdout, we're diving deep into two critical cybersecurity developments:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Microsoft Entra ID Vulnerability (CVE-2025-55241):</strong> Discover how a critical flaw, leveraging undocumented "actor tokens" and a deprecated API, could have granted Global Administrator privileges across any Entra ID tenant globally. Learn about the stealthy exploitation potential and Microsoft's swift patch.</li>
</ul>

<p>🇰🇵 We then pivot to the evolving tactics of North Korean state-sponsored hacking groups, including Lazarus, ScarCruft (APT37), and Kimsuky (APT43). Expect insights into:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Sophisticated Social Engineering:</strong> How "ClickFix" lures in fake cryptocurrency job scams deliver malware like BeaverTail and InvisibleFerret, with expanded targeting beyond software developers.</li>
    <li><strong>ScarCruft's Shift:</strong> A notable move from pure espionage to financially motivated and potentially destructive operations, deploying VCD ransomware for the first time, alongside new tools like the Rust-based CHILLYCHINO and FadeStealer. 💸</li>
    <li><strong>Kimsuky's Innovation:</strong> Abuse of GitHub repositories for malware delivery and data exfiltration, plus their alarming use of OpenAI's ChatGPT to forge deepfake military ID cards in spear-phishing campaigns targeting South Korean defence entities. 🤖</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:51:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A0I0n_EPVK_8tVhUQ9LzMDNsIM9o0F1v" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758491463480</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, September 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 stdout uncovers a critical <b>zero-click vulnerability</b>, codenamed <i>ShadowLeak</i>, in OpenAI ChatGPT's Deep Research agent. Crafted emails leveraging <b>indirect prompt injection</b> could exfiltrate sensitive Gmail inbox data directly from OpenAI's cloud infrastructure, bypassing traditional client-side defences. This flaw, now patched, highlights risks with enabled third-party integrations. 📧</p>

<p>Next, we expose a widespread campaign targeting macOS users with the potent <b>Atomic Stealer malware</b>. Threat actors are deploying <b>fake GitHub repositories</b> impersonating legitimate tools like LastPass and 1Password, using <b>SEO poisoning</b> to push malicious downloads. This campaign underscores persistent social engineering and supply chain compromise tactics. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, a significant regulatory crackdown: the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) has shut down the <b>TradeOgre cryptocurrency exchange</b>, seizing over $40 million. This marks Canada's first crypto exchange shutdown, driven by failures in FINTRAC registration and Know Your Customer (KYC) policies, making it a conduit for cybercrime money laundering. 💰</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 21:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1tMHgZfBPEoSMn5FdtmT3JrJqstl-MKiy" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758405025397</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, September 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cybersecurity with "stdout"! We're breaking down 12 critical topics for technical analysts, focusing on active cyber events, exploited vulnerabilities, and emerging threat techniques. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>This episode, we cover the <b>arrests of two Scattered Spider affiliates</b> in the UK, linked to over $115 million in ransoms and a US federal court breach. We also track a <b>cyberattack on Russia's Pulkovo Airport</b> and an Iran-nexus group, UNC1549, infiltrating 11 European telecommunications companies via LinkedIn lures and the MINIBIKE backdoor. ✈️</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Fortra warns of a <b>max-severity deserialisation flaw (CVE-2025-10035)</b> in GoAnywhere MFT, mirroring a past Clop zero-day. CISA details malware exploiting <b>Ivanti EPMM zero-days (CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428)</b>, potentially by China-nexus groups. Plus, discover a critical, now-mitigated <b>Microsoft Entra ID flaw (CVE-2025-55241)</b> that could have granted global admin access, and OpenAI's patch for <b>ChatGPT's "ShadowLeak"</b>, allowing Gmail secret exfiltration. 💥</p>

<p>New threat research reveals <b>collaboration between Russian state-sponsored groups Gamaredon and Turla</b>, with Gamaredon providing initial access for Turla's Kazuar backdoor. Uncover China's "AI persona army" for information warfare and the surge in <b>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platforms like Lighthouse and Lucid</b>, driving 17,500+ phishing domains. We also explore how researchers tricked ChatGPT into solving CAPTCHAs, raising questions about their long-term effectiveness. 🤖</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, MI6 launches a <b>dark web portal "Silent Courier"</b> for informant recruitment, the FBI warns of fake IC3 portals, and the future of the CVE Program is debated amidst funding concerns. Stay ahead with stdout! 💡</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1j3GmxORR1uzJylpdZTURpYCcZjQRru00" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758318799585</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, September 19, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats and vulnerabilities impacting the digital landscape. This episode unpacks a massive alleged data theft by **ShinyHunters**, claiming 1.5 billion Salesforce records via a Salesloft supply chain attack, impacting major organisations like Google and Palo Alto Networks. We also cover a confirmed ransomware attack on venture capital firm **Insight Partners** affecting over 12,000 individuals, and a critical breach of **SonicWall's cloud backup service** exposing firewall configurations for a segment of its user base. The healthcare sector remains a prime target, with three separate breaches exposing data for over 850,000 Americans. 🏥</p>

<p>Stay informed on active threat actors and emerging techniques: two alleged **Scattered Spider** members have been charged in connection with the Transport for London attack. Discover how the Russian troll farm **CopyCop (Storm-1516)** is leveraging self-hosted LLMs to generate fake news across 200+ sites, and learn about malicious `sisaws` and `secmeasure` packages in PyPI delivering the **SilentSync RAT**. China-backed **TA415 (APT41)** is actively targeting US government and academic organisations with sophisticated phishing, while the **SystemBC botnet** compromises 1,500 commercial VPS daily for malicious traffic. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities and essential patches: Google has issued an urgent update for a **sixth Chrome zero-day (CVE-2025-10585)** actively exploited in the wild. WatchGuard released security updates for a critical **Firebox RCE (CVE-2025-9242)**, and OpenAI patched a "ShadowLeak" zero-click vulnerability in **ChatGPT's Deep Research agent**. Plus, all PyPI tokens stolen in the recent **GhostAction supply chain attack** have been invalidated. 🔒</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on Cloudflare's self-inflicted outage, Brazil's new **Digital ECA law** for child data protection, the confirmation of Katherine Sutton as the Pentagon's new Assistant Secretary of Defence for Cyber Policy, and how federal agencies are increasingly incorporating AI into cyber defences. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fMFzF4_YDJnVctKBy8YGziTDZb5NZDa8" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758282372409</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, September 18, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout delivers your daily intel. Today, we unpack the ongoing fallout from the Colt Technology Services and Jaguar Land Rover ransomware attacks, a brute-force breach impacting SonicWall's MySonicWall.com, and a sophisticated ransomware incident at Insight Partners. New threat research highlights Microsoft and Cloudflare's takedown of the RaccoonO365 Phishing-as-a-Service, the resurgence of Scattered Spider targeting the financial sector via social engineering and Azure AD SSPR, and how groups like Kimsuky and RevengeHotels are leveraging AI for deepfakes and refined malware. We also delve into 'Phoenix', a new Rowhammer attack (CVE-2025-6202) affecting DDR5 memory, and the resentencing of BreachForums founder 'Pompompurin'.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=12l35AcBToFxS0D7tA1yVYBmKT3GM8ZBI" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758177075763</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the last 24 hours in cyber security. We dive into the FBI's FLASH alert on UNC6040/UNC6395 (ShinyHunters/Scattered Spider) compromising Salesforce via vishing and OAuth token exploits, alongside ongoing disruption at Jaguar Land Rover and a ransomware attack forcing a Texas school district closure. Discover how Akira ransomware bypassed MFA in a SonicWall VPN breach using plaintext recovery codes, and the largest npm supply chain compromise to date, impacting billions of downloads after a maintainer was phished. We also cover new SEO poisoning campaigns distributing novel malware, Mustang Panda's updated TONESHELL and geofenced SnakeDisk worm, and Kimsuky spies leveraging ChatGPT for fake IDs. Plus, a new Rowhammer attack variant, "Phoenix," bypasses DDR5 defences to achieve root privileges, and Microsoft warns about SMBv1 connection issues. Stay informed on these critical developments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1oMEIaRwMA553EYRQUweD9Yk_FCWlstCk" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758175389469</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, September 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the latest in cyber security: Jaguar Land Rover's operations remain suspended following a 'Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' attack, with the group also creating a fraudulent account in Google's LERS portal. We detail 'Shai-Hulud,' a self-propagating npm worm actively stealing credentials, and the 'FileFix' social engineering technique delivering the StealC infostealer via fake Facebook alerts and steganography. Explore the massive 'SlopAds' ad fraud operation exploiting Android apps, plus the new 'Phoenix' RowHammer variant bypassing DDR5 memory protections. Apple has backported patches for an actively exploited Image I/O zero-day. Also, China's stricter incident reporting mandates, Microsoft's removal of WMIC, and Check Point's acquisition of AI security platform Lakera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 04:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Ycw0BHzmaCvuT0Ce0tLUJErkxyOqJBPR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758171526797</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
