<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:anchor="https://anchor.fm/xmlns" xmlns:podcast="https://podcastindex.org/namespace/1.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:psc="http://podlove.org/simple-chapters">
  <channel>
    <title>stdout security</title>
    <description><p>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.</p>
      <p><strong>Note:</strong> This is an AI-generated summary of News Articles from the past 24 hours. I take no credit for the research or analysis in said articles - this podcast only exists as a simple audio summary to help busy, sleep-deprivd Cyber Nerds like myself keep on top of developments while wranging kids and brushing teeth. </p>
    </description>
    <link>https://opalsec.io</link>
    <generator>Anchor Podcasts</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 05:06:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <author>Opalsec</author>
    <copyright>Opalsec</copyright>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <atom:link href="https://anchor.fm/s/109797ef8/podcast/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/>
    <itunes:author>Opalsec</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Bite-sized, daily Cyber Security wrap-ups to get you prepped for your day.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Opalsec</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>opalsec.integrate@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:category text="News">
      <itunes:category text="Tech News"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:image href="https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_nologo/44439246/44439246-1758158096542-bb2824b85de8c.jpg"/>
                                    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Monday, September 22, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 On this episode of stdout, we're diving deep into two critical cybersecurity developments:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Microsoft Entra ID Vulnerability (CVE-2025-55241):</strong> Discover how a critical flaw, leveraging undocumented "actor tokens" and a deprecated API, could have granted Global Administrator privileges across any Entra ID tenant globally. Learn about the stealthy exploitation potential and Microsoft's swift patch.</li>
</ul>

<p>🇰🇵 We then pivot to the evolving tactics of North Korean state-sponsored hacking groups, including Lazarus, ScarCruft (APT37), and Kimsuky (APT43). Expect insights into:</p>

<ul>
    <li><strong>Sophisticated Social Engineering:</strong> How "ClickFix" lures in fake cryptocurrency job scams deliver malware like BeaverTail and InvisibleFerret, with expanded targeting beyond software developers.</li>
    <li><strong>ScarCruft's Shift:</strong> A notable move from pure espionage to financially motivated and potentially destructive operations, deploying VCD ransomware for the first time, alongside new tools like the Rust-based CHILLYCHINO and FadeStealer. 💸</li>
    <li><strong>Kimsuky's Innovation:</strong> Abuse of GitHub repositories for malware delivery and data exfiltration, plus their alarming use of OpenAI's ChatGPT to forge deepfake military ID cards in spear-phishing campaigns targeting South Korean defence entities. 🤖</li>
</ul>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:51:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1A0I0n_EPVK_8tVhUQ9LzMDNsIM9o0F1v" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758491463480</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Sunday, September 21, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 stdout uncovers a critical <b>zero-click vulnerability</b>, codenamed <i>ShadowLeak</i>, in OpenAI ChatGPT's Deep Research agent. Crafted emails leveraging <b>indirect prompt injection</b> could exfiltrate sensitive Gmail inbox data directly from OpenAI's cloud infrastructure, bypassing traditional client-side defences. This flaw, now patched, highlights risks with enabled third-party integrations. 📧</p>

<p>Next, we expose a widespread campaign targeting macOS users with the potent <b>Atomic Stealer malware</b>. Threat actors are deploying <b>fake GitHub repositories</b> impersonating legitimate tools like LastPass and 1Password, using <b>SEO poisoning</b> to push malicious downloads. This campaign underscores persistent social engineering and supply chain compromise tactics. 💻</p>

<p>Finally, a significant regulatory crackdown: the Royal Canadian Mounted Police (RCMP) has shut down the <b>TradeOgre cryptocurrency exchange</b>, seizing over $40 million. This marks Canada's first crypto exchange shutdown, driven by failures in FINTRAC registration and Know Your Customer (KYC) policies, making it a conduit for cybercrime money laundering. 💰</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 21:50:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1tMHgZfBPEoSMn5FdtmT3JrJqstl-MKiy" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758405025397</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Saturday, September 20, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>🚨 <b>stdout: Your Daily Cyber Briefing</b> 🚨</p>
<p>Dive deep into the last 24 hours of cybersecurity with "stdout"! We're breaking down 12 critical topics for technical analysts, focusing on active cyber events, exploited vulnerabilities, and emerging threat techniques. 🇦🇺</p>

<p>This episode, we cover the <b>arrests of two Scattered Spider affiliates</b> in the UK, linked to over $115 million in ransoms and a US federal court breach. We also track a <b>cyberattack on Russia's Pulkovo Airport</b> and an Iran-nexus group, UNC1549, infiltrating 11 European telecommunications companies via LinkedIn lures and the MINIBIKE backdoor. ✈️</p>

<p>On the vulnerability front, Fortra warns of a <b>max-severity deserialisation flaw (CVE-2025-10035)</b> in GoAnywhere MFT, mirroring a past Clop zero-day. CISA details malware exploiting <b>Ivanti EPMM zero-days (CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428)</b>, potentially by China-nexus groups. Plus, discover a critical, now-mitigated <b>Microsoft Entra ID flaw (CVE-2025-55241)</b> that could have granted global admin access, and OpenAI's patch for <b>ChatGPT's "ShadowLeak"</b>, allowing Gmail secret exfiltration. 💥</p>

<p>New threat research reveals <b>collaboration between Russian state-sponsored groups Gamaredon and Turla</b>, with Gamaredon providing initial access for Turla's Kazuar backdoor. Uncover China's "AI persona army" for information warfare and the surge in <b>Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) platforms like Lighthouse and Lucid</b>, driving 17,500+ phishing domains. We also explore how researchers tricked ChatGPT into solving CAPTCHAs, raising questions about their long-term effectiveness. 🤖</p>

<p>Beyond the exploits, MI6 launches a <b>dark web portal "Silent Courier"</b> for informant recruitment, the FBI warns of fake IC3 portals, and the future of the CVE Program is debated amidst funding concerns. Stay ahead with stdout! 💡</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:53:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1j3GmxORR1uzJylpdZTURpYCcZjQRru00" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758318799585</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Friday, September 19, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dive into the latest cyber threats and vulnerabilities impacting the digital landscape. This episode unpacks a massive alleged data theft by **ShinyHunters**, claiming 1.5 billion Salesforce records via a Salesloft supply chain attack, impacting major organisations like Google and Palo Alto Networks. We also cover a confirmed ransomware attack on venture capital firm **Insight Partners** affecting over 12,000 individuals, and a critical breach of **SonicWall's cloud backup service** exposing firewall configurations for a segment of its user base. The healthcare sector remains a prime target, with three separate breaches exposing data for over 850,000 Americans. 🏥</p>

<p>Stay informed on active threat actors and emerging techniques: two alleged **Scattered Spider** members have been charged in connection with the Transport for London attack. Discover how the Russian troll farm **CopyCop (Storm-1516)** is leveraging self-hosted LLMs to generate fake news across 200+ sites, and learn about malicious `sisaws` and `secmeasure` packages in PyPI delivering the **SilentSync RAT**. China-backed **TA415 (APT41)** is actively targeting US government and academic organisations with sophisticated phishing, while the **SystemBC botnet** compromises 1,500 commercial VPS daily for malicious traffic. 🕵️‍♂️</p>

<p>Critical vulnerabilities and essential patches: Google has issued an urgent update for a **sixth Chrome zero-day (CVE-2025-10585)** actively exploited in the wild. WatchGuard released security updates for a critical **Firebox RCE (CVE-2025-9242)**, and OpenAI patched a "ShadowLeak" zero-click vulnerability in **ChatGPT's Deep Research agent**. Plus, all PyPI tokens stolen in the recent **GhostAction supply chain attack** have been invalidated. 🔒</p>

<p>Finally, we touch on Cloudflare's self-inflicted outage, Brazil's new **Digital ECA law** for child data protection, the confirmation of Katherine Sutton as the Pentagon's new Assistant Secretary of Defence for Cyber Policy, and how federal agencies are increasingly incorporating AI into cyber defences. 🌐</p>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:46:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1fMFzF4_YDJnVctKBy8YGziTDZb5NZDa8" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758282372409</guid>
    </item>
<item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Thursday, September 18, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout delivers your daily intel. Today, we unpack the ongoing fallout from the Colt Technology Services and Jaguar Land Rover ransomware attacks, a brute-force breach impacting SonicWall's MySonicWall.com, and a sophisticated ransomware incident at Insight Partners. New threat research highlights Microsoft and Cloudflare's takedown of the RaccoonO365 Phishing-as-a-Service, the resurgence of Scattered Spider targeting the financial sector via social engineering and Azure AD SSPR, and how groups like Kimsuky and RevengeHotels are leveraging AI for deepfakes and refined malware. We also delve into 'Phoenix', a new Rowhammer attack (CVE-2025-6202) affecting DDR5 memory, and the resentencing of BreachForums founder 'Pompompurin'.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=12l35AcBToFxS0D7tA1yVYBmKT3GM8ZBI" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758177075763</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Tuesday, September 16, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the last 24 hours in cyber security. We dive into the FBI's FLASH alert on UNC6040/UNC6395 (ShinyHunters/Scattered Spider) compromising Salesforce via vishing and OAuth token exploits, alongside ongoing disruption at Jaguar Land Rover and a ransomware attack forcing a Texas school district closure. Discover how Akira ransomware bypassed MFA in a SonicWall VPN breach using plaintext recovery codes, and the largest npm supply chain compromise to date, impacting billions of downloads after a maintainer was phished. We also cover new SEO poisoning campaigns distributing novel malware, Mustang Panda's updated TONESHELL and geofenced SnakeDisk worm, and Kimsuky spies leveraging ChatGPT for fake IDs. Plus, a new Rowhammer attack variant, "Phoenix," bypasses DDR5 defences to achieve root privileges, and Microsoft warns about SMBv1 connection issues. Stay informed on these critical developments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 06:03:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1oMEIaRwMA553EYRQUweD9Yk_FCWlstCk" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758175389469</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily News Update: Wednesday, September 17, 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[stdout unpacks the latest in cyber security: Jaguar Land Rover's operations remain suspended following a 'Scattered Lapsus$ Hunters' attack, with the group also creating a fraudulent account in Google's LERS portal. We detail 'Shai-Hulud,' a self-propagating npm worm actively stealing credentials, and the 'FileFix' social engineering technique delivering the StealC infostealer via fake Facebook alerts and steganography. Explore the massive 'SlopAds' ad fraud operation exploiting Android apps, plus the new 'Phoenix' RowHammer variant bypassing DDR5 memory protections. Apple has backported patches for an actively exploited Image I/O zero-day. Also, China's stricter incident reporting mandates, Microsoft's removal of WMIC, and Check Point's acquisition of AI security platform Lakera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 04:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Ycw0BHzmaCvuT0Ce0tLUJErkxyOqJBPR" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg"/>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1758171526797</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
